<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize>
  <text id="Default_weapon_name">Dùi cui</text>
  <text id="Default_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
  <text id="Default_armor_name">Giáp</text>
  <text id="Default_armor_no">Mẫu B-05</text>
  <text id="OneBadManyGood_weapon_name">Thánh giá</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_weapon_no">Mẫu A-02</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_weapon_desc">Biết tức nghĩa đã hiểu.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Dựa theo quan sát và nguyên mẫu chúng ta thành công thực hiện tạo ra một món vũ khí.&#13;&#10;Đó là lý do tại sao chúng ta tập trung quán sát chúng.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Các lỗ rỗng mắt nhìn thấy tội lỗi và vương miện đầy gai đổ lỗi cho họ.&#13;&#10;Để dùng vũ khí, người đó phải hướng tới sự tàn sát cho mục đích tốt hơn.&#13;&#10;&#13;Thiết nghĩ nó không mạnh bằng các E.G.O khác, nó giúp người dùng có tâm trạng thoải mái.&#10;&#13;&#10;Tuy nhiên, sẽ không có sự thoải mái cho những kẻ bất công.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_weapon_specialDesc">5% hồi tức thời 10 SP khi tấn công với độ công lý lớn hơn 2</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_armor_no">Mẫu B-02</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_armor_desc">Súng và dao thường không ảnh hưởng đến Những bất thường.&#13;&#10;Nếu có thể lấy nguyên liệu khi Bất thường đang bất tỉnh, thì nó có thể được chiết suất và biến thành vũ khí.&#13;&#10;Kết quả khác nhau tùy thuộc vào người quan sát.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Vòng hoa đôi khi bảo vệ linh hồn của người nắm giữ.&#13;&#10;Tuy nhiên, thực tế gai nhọn làm đau linh hồn họ.&#13;&#10;Những người không có cảm giác tội lỗi không thể hưởng lợi từ phụ kiện này.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_armor_specialDesc">5% hồi tức thời 10 SP khi bị đánh bởi R, B</text>
	<text id="OneBadManyGood_gift_Desc">SP +2&#13;&#10;Tỷ lệ thành công của Bất thường tăng 10%</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_weapon_name">Cặp mắt đỏ</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_weapon_desc">Một con nhện có nhiều mắt và con cái của nó đầy cơn đói khát.&#13;&#10;Đôi mắt của nó phát sáng vào ban đêm để tìm thức ăn.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;E.G.O này sử dụng trực giác của nó để tăng cường khả năng theo dõi của vũ khí.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Nó phát ra một luồng sáng đỏ để tìm nạn nhân trong bóng tối.&#13;&#10;Tuy nhiên, người sở hữu có thể bị thao túng bởi nhện nếu nhìn vào mắt của nó quá lâu.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_weapon_specialDesc">Tốc độ di chuyển +5 khi đàn áp. Yêu cầu 2+ Sức bền </text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_armor_desc">Bản năng thợ săn của nó không thể bị đẩy lùi.&#13;&#10;Vũ khí dai dẳng và độc ác này không hề tỏ ra thương xót đối với bạn hay thù.&#13;&#10;Người sở hữu có thể bị thao túng bởi nhện nếu nhìn vào mắt của nó quá lâu.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Đôi mắt của nó nhìn thấy các mục tiêu ngay cả trong bóng tối.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_armor_specialDesc">Tốc độ di chuyển +5 khi đàn áp. Yêu cầu 2+ Sức bền </text>
	<text id="SpiderMom_gift_Desc">Tỷ lệ thành công +3 tốc độ làm việc +3</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_weapon_name">Sừng</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_weapon_desc">Cô gái với đôi mắt màu xanh lá cây yêu dahlias và tình yêu của cô là cho tôi.&#13;&#10;Nhưng khi những cái sừng đáng sợ mọc trên trán cô, sự hận thù của nàng cũng vậy. Cô ấy không thể hoàn thành lời tiên tri với dahlias yêu quý của cô ấy.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Một bông hoa nở trong sự thù hận chỉ ngày một héo đi thôi.&#13;&#10;Sừng của cô xuyên qua trái tim của kẻ thù của cô và nhuộm lên người màu đỏ của máu.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_armor_desc">Nhưng khi những cái sừng đáng sợ mọc trên trán cô, sự hận thù của nàng cũng vậy. Cô ấy không thể hoàn thành lời tiên tri với dahlias yêu quý của cô ấy.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Những bông hoa kể câu chuyện về niềm vui và nỗi buồn, nhưng cuối cùng, một cuộc đời đáng thương.&#13;&#10;Một bông hoa nở trong sự thù hận chỉ ngày một héo đi thôi.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Nó đã mất đi hương thơm của nó từ lâu.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="BeautyBeast_gift_Desc">HP +2 SP +2</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_weapon_name">Tiếng thét Wedge</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_weapon_no">Mẫu A-02</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_weapon_desc">Người phụ nữ xả tóc phàn nàn.&#13;&#10;Âm thanh viên đạn chia tách cả không khí gợi nhớ lại tiếng thét của cô ấy.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Người sử dụng phải cẩn thận khi sử dụng vũ khí này, vì tóc có thể làm rối tay người nắm giữ và kéo họ vào nỗi buồn vô tận.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Chỉ có nhân viên với tinh thần thép mới có thể sử dụng mà không có tác dụng phụ.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_weapon_specialDesc">&#13;&#10;SP giảm 5 với xác suất 50%&#13;&#10;khi sức bền và độ thân thiện của nhân viên dưới 3</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_armor_no">Mẫu B-02</text>
	<text id="LadyLookingAtWall_armor_desc">Tinh thần của cô ấy bị ràng buộc chặt chẽ với nó.&#13;&#10;Nếu viên đạn xuyên qua trái tim của kẻ thù, sự phẫn nộ sẽ phát triển ở đó.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Một trái tim ấm áp và cái đầu lạnh là cần thiết để chống lại điều này.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_weapon_name">Que diêm thứ tư</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_weapon_no">Mẫu A-03</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_weapon_desc">The fire roars and burns like the first flame.&#13;&#10;The fire will not go out until it has burned away the happiness, warmth, and other good things of the world.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The experiments with matches cannot complete without collaterals.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Those who are burned will feel infinite hatred toward the world until they lose consciousness.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_armor_desc">The core was burnt ashes from the first place.&#13;&#10;It appears charred, but it functions perfectly.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The ashy design evokes the blazing hatred against the good things in the world.&#13;&#10;Tuy nhiên, no one knows whether it is fireproof or not.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Matchgirl_gift_Desc">HP +4</text>
	<text id="StraitJacket_weapon_name">Regret</text>
	<text id="StraitJacket_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="StraitJacket_weapon_desc">A secret research project began in a basement, aiming to change the future of the mankind.&#13;&#10;The researchers even gave up their dignity, but sacrifices were to be made for the greater goal.&#13;&#10;Even Carmen condoned the project.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Enemies crushed by this regret can never return to their normal life.&#13;&#10;This weapon shall be wielded in remembrance of all who died but could not find eternal rest.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="StraitJacket_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="StraitJacket_armor_desc">A secret research project began in a basement, in hopes of changing the future of the mankind.&#13;&#10;No one cared about the death-row convict in a straightjacket who were experimented on.&#13;&#10;Now its straitjacket is nothing but an accessory, its hatred and anger remain.&#13;&#10;Employees who feel constricting pain while wearing this suit must be examined thoroughly.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_weapon_name">Somewhere Spear</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_weapon_no">Mẫu A-03</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_weapon_desc">Do not try to understand it, just use it.&#13;&#10;The spear often tries to guide its wielder to an endless spiritual realm, but the wielder must not be deceived.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Its gestalt was changed on every extraction, and was finally fixed after numerous attempts.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;There is a rumor of this spear emitting bright light when it hears an echo from another world.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_weapon_specialDesc">When used by an agent with Prudence Level 4 or lower, 10% probability of Max. SP increase by 40% for 30 secs</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_armor_no">Mẫu B-03</text>
	<text id="Cosmos_armor_desc">Do not try to understand it, just use it.&#13;&#10;They say that anyone who wears this E.G.O suit can see things that were forgotten.&#13;&#10;But one cannot be certain of what would be seen, as every employee sees something different.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Its gestalt changed on every extraction, and was finally fixed after numerous attempts.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Rudolph_weapon_name">Christmas</text>
	<text id="Rudolph_weapon_no">Mẫu A-02</text>
	<text id="Rudolph_weapon_desc">It is patched with heavy leather. No one knows where the leather came from though.&#13;&#10;The colorful leather pieces remind a festive holiday that was long forgotten.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The stitches are carefully woven, but for what or whom?&#13;&#10;It is not elegant, but you can feel the devotion of its creator.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Its true identity under the leather is classified, but its secrecy only makes the weapon all the more powerful.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Rudolph_armor_no">Mẫu B-02</text>
	<text id="Rudolph_armor_desc">The colorful leather pieces remind a festive holiday that was long forgotten.&#13;&#10;The origin of the material cannot be disclosed to unauthorized personnel.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It may still dream of becoming a good child.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The wielder may feel the urge to give out gifts to random people.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_weapon_name">Bloody Desire</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_weapon_desc">Even after its legs were cut off, its incredible conviction lead it to go to the woods and return.&#13;&#10;Most employees are familiar with its tragic past.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The ax's light weight can sometimes cause its wielder to forget the heavy responsibility that it comes with.&#13;&#10;The weapon is stronger when used by an employee with strong conviction.&#13;&#10;However, obsession doesn't stop when blinded by avarice.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_weapon_specialDesc">When Temperance is lower than level 3, Max. and Min. Attack Power raises, in inverse proportion to Temperance Level. Max. SP reduced by 4% when attacked.</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_armor_desc">Even after its legs were cut off, its incredible conviction went through the forest and returned.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The lovely lace is reminiscent of a girl with beautiful smile.&#13;&#10;Make sure to stay alert and not to repeat the tragedy.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Perhaps someday the bloody shoes will make their way to a grand ballroom.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="RedShoes_gift_Desc">HP +4&#13;&#10;Success Rate of Work and Block Speed decreases by 10, Attack Speed increases by 10 when the weapon is equipped with corresponding Abnormality</text>
	<text id="Helper_weapon_name">Grinder Mk4</text>
	<text id="Helper_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="Helper_weapon_desc">The sharp sawtooth of the grinder makes a clean cut through its enemy.&#13;&#10;It is easy to operate, but that doesn't make it an easy weapon to wield.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As machines have no value of their own, there is no clear boundary between good and evil.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This is precisely why this weapon is so reliable.&#13;&#10;Machine rebellion is no longer a threat in modern society.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Helper_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="Helper_armor_desc">This otherwise clean and neat coat is covered with bloodstains.&#13;&#10;Some employees take it as a badge of bravery.&#13;&#10;But the bloodstains were there from the beginning.&#13;&#10;It feels reminiscent of the disasters in the past and the future.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Machine rebellion is no longer a threat in modern society.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="Helper_gift_Desc">Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2&#13;&#10;Success Rate for Insight Work increases by 3%</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_weapon_name">Bear Paw</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_weapon_desc">Stuffing sticks out of the bear like forgotten innocence.&#13;&#10;It looks cute, a child may like to receive it as a gift&#13;&#10;It requires extra case as it is fragile and can tear..&#13;&#10;Some sympathetic employees felt sorry for it and asked for it to be repaired, however the outcome of repairing was unforeseeable so the proposal was rejected.&#13;&#10;Do not be fooled by its fluffy exterior.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_armor_desc">It may have been fluffy once, but now it just looks shabby.&#13;&#10;Repair requests were rejected.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Its warm memory of hugs was forgotten when it was thrown away.&#13;&#10;Stuffing sticks out of the bear like forgotten innocence.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="HappyTeddy_gift_Desc">SP +4&#13;&#10;Success Rate for Ecoscaping increases by 3%</text>
	<text id="LongBird_weapon_name">Justitia</text>
	<text id="LongBird_weapon_no">Mẫu A-04</text>
	<text id="LongBird_weapon_desc">It remembers the balance of the Long Bird that never forgot others' sins.&#13;&#10;This weapon may be able to not only cut flesh but trace of sins as well.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The employee who extracted this E.G.O weapon was the most just person in the company.&#13;&#10;Do not try to take off the bandage. It wants to hide the sad memories of the past.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Like its previous form, it seeks to bring peace.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="LongBird_armor_no">Mẫu B-04</text>
	<text id="LongBird_armor_desc">Just like anything else, it began with small hope.&#13;&#10;The desire for peace now only exists in fairy tales.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The employee who extracted this E.G.O suit was the most just person in the company.&#13;&#10;Do not try to take off the bandage. It wants to hide the sad memories of the past.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="LongBird_gift_Desc">Movment Speed +3 Attack Speed +3&#13;&#10;Success Rate of Suppression increases by 6%</text>
	<text id="SnowWhite_weapon_name">Green Stem</text>
	<text id="SnowWhite_weapon_no">Mẫu A-03</text>
	<text id="SnowWhite_weapon_desc">It sprouted stems and leaves after realizing nobody will come.&#13;&#10;But all stems crumble the moment they come out, due to the malice it bore since its creation.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Those who come in contact with the weapon die by its inherent evil.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Engineers who create this weapon must wear heavy protection to prevent getting influenced by the malice.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="SnowWhite_armor_no">Mẫu B-03</text>
	<text id="SnowWhite_armor_desc">It sprouted stems and leaves after realizing nobody will come.&#13;&#10;The surrounding stems only evoke pitiable convictions.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;A strong determination will ease the suffering.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Engineers could not remove poison from this E.G.O. equipment.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;</text>
  <text id="SnowWhite_gift_name">Those who know the severity of winter and the fragrance of roses</text>
  <text id="SnowWhite_gift_Desc">SP +6 &#13;&#10;Max. and Min. Attack Power increases by 5 when the weapon is equipped with corresponding Abnormality</text>
	<text id="QueenBee_weapon_name">Hornet</text>
	<text id="QueenBee_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="QueenBee_weapon_desc">Though the kingdom would leave its marks in history, who would remember the sacrifices made?&#13;&#10;The glory of the past still lingers.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Accuracy means nothing when the projectiles home into its targets.&#13;&#10;The only thing that's needed is the will.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The projectiles travel not only the space but the time as well to reach the target.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="QueenBee_armor_no">Mẫu B-03</text>
	<text id="QueenBee_armor_desc">Though the kingdom would ring throughout history, who would remember the sacrifices made?&#13;&#10;The glory of the past still lingers.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This E.G.O suit makes the bees recognize the wearer as one of them.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_weapon_name">Gold Rush</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_weapon_no">Mẫu A-01</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_weapon_desc">The fist from a time when avarice knew no bounds.&#13;&#10;It strikes enemies with full force. No special techniques are needed, it operates based on primal urges.&#13;&#10;Attacking with this weapon feels natural but it is easy to get carried away.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_weapon_specialDesc">10% probability of increasing Min. and Max. Attack Power by 5 when attacking for 12 secs. Debuff 50% of Temperance-related Stats for 120 secs</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_armor_no">Mẫu B-01</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_armor_desc">The amber gemstone shines, but it’s nothing but avarice materialized.&#13;&#10;Its beautiful gold patterns have mesmerized many an employee.&#13;&#10;The delusion may have come from the deepest subconscious.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="MagicalGirl2_gift_Desc">HP +6&#13;&#10;Success Rate of Instinct increases by 6%</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_weapon_name">Da Capo</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_weapon_no">Mẫu A-02</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_weapon_desc">A swinging scythe is silent and moderate just like a conductor.&#13;&#10;If the weapon could play music, it would play apocalypse.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The wielder of this E.G.O weapon hears some silent music that no one else can hear.&#13;&#10;The conductor does not rest until the finale.&#13;&#10;It would be wise to leave some audience alive until the finale to hear them applaud.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_armor_no">Mẫu B-02</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_armor_desc">A splendid tailcoat perfect for a symphony.&#13;&#10;Superb leadership is required to create a perfect ensemble.&#13;&#10;It would be wise to leave some audience alive until the finale to hear them applaud.&#13;&#10;</text>
	<text id="SilentOrchestra_gift_Desc">Success Rate +4 Work Speed +4&#13;&#10;Absorbs WHITE attacks when armor of corresponding Abnormality is equipped</text>
  <text id="Bald_weapon_name">Tough</text>
  <text id="Bald_weapon_desc">A glock with the power to shoot down a helicopter.&#13;&#10;It can only be used by people who has... no hair!&#13;&#10;It reminds you of the detective who fought evil so hard for 25 years until he he starts balding. </text>
  <text id="Bald_armor_desc">A leather jacket which looks better than it actually is.&#13;&#10;It can only be used by people who has... no hair!&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Anyone who wears this jacket will feel their head shine brighter.</text>
  <text id="Bald_armor_specialDesc">Only those employees with bald or round hair loss can wear the armor.</text>
  <text id="Wellcheers_weapon_name">Soda</text>
  <text id="Wellcheers_weapon_desc">A weapon extracted by a late employee who really liked shrimp.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The pistol is in vivid purple&#13;&#10;and it smells like grapes.</text>
  <text id="Wellcheers_armor_desc">A suit that feels like aluminum when touched.&#13;&#10;It’s quite light.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Some say it smells of salt when worn for a long time. </text>
  <text id="OldLady_weapon_name">Loneliness</text>
  <text id="OldLady_weapon_desc">The strong sense of loneliness still lingers even in the form of an E.G.O.&#13;&#10;Its bullets inflict damage to the victim's soul, not flesh.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It was a rusty weapon from the beginning. </text>
  <text id="OldLady_armor_desc">To hide soft inside, arm yourself with loneliness.&#13;&#10; Give everything or nothing.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This suit will protect the wearer’s fragile mind. </text>
  <text id="OldLady_gift_Desc">Success Rate +3 Work Speed +3</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_weapon_name">Beak</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_weapon_desc">This tiny bird packs some serious punch despite its size.&#13;&#10;Show no mercy to whomever stands on your way.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The jagged tip of the projectile delivers substantial pain to the victim. </text>
  <text id="SmallBird_armor_desc">Sleek without a dent,&#13;&#10;the suit was originally very small, barely wearable by a child. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10; As it is soaks up blood, it’s chest part wriggles as if it were alive.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_weapon_name">Reverberation</text>
  <text id="Alriune_weapon_desc">This E.G.O weapon smells like the Abnormality it came from.&#13;&#10;The wielder will feel like they are standing in an outlandish forest.&#13;&#10;The arrowhead is dull and sprouts flowers in vivid colors wherever it is struck.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This weapon will no longer be needed if the time comes when everyone's lust is s ubstituted with flowers.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_armor_desc">The sleek surface is tough as if it had been cured several times.&#13;&#10;It may crumble back into primal soil if it is exposed to a powerful White attack.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Any cracks will be filled with a pile of flowers. </text>
  <text id="Alriune_gift_Desc">SP +4 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="BloodBath_weapon_name">Wrist Cuter</text>
  <text id="BloodBath_weapon_desc">It bears blood marks as if it were gripped by the hands soaked in ever-lasting blood.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;To ease the pain on the victim, its sharp blade can cut through the bones like a hot knife through the butter. The victim of this weapon cannot regenerate itself.&#13;&#10;It will also permanently cut off the will to pursue happiness from the victim.</text>
  <text id="BloodBath_armor_desc">The flesh is clean-cut by a sharp tool, and blood strains on it show a grotesque pattern.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The suit itself holds deep sorrow and agony, which will shield the wearer against most White attacks.&#13;&#10;When worn by employees with low SP, it may cause recurring, sorrowful dreams.</text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_weapon_name">Frost Shard</text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_weapon_desc">The Snow Queen was beautiful, but where her heart should have been was empty and frozen.&#13;&#10;The edge of the spear is both straight and icy. Anyone damaged by it will lose themselves for a moment.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Since it is made of snow, it will disappear without a trace someday.&#13;&#10;Perhaps a day will come when her heart will be warmed by the weather, if you can believe it. </text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_armor_desc">To stay inside the snow palace, a warm cloak is a must.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Since the cloak is made of snow, it shall disappear without a trace someday.&#13;&#10;Perhaps a day will come when her heart will be warmed by the weather, if you can believe it.  </text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_weapon_specialDesc">Reduces movement speed of target by 30% for 3 seconds</text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_gift_name">The ones who know the cruelty of winter and the aroma of rose</text>
  <text id="SnowQueen_gift_desc">HP +6 SP +6&#13;&#10;The roses blossom and the Snow Palace falls. Not a single soul remembered the woman sleeping there.</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_weapon_name">Life for the Dare Devil</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_weapon_desc">An ancient sword.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Like its prototype hoped, it may be useless in the hands of the frightened. </text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_armor_desc">If an employee who accepts their death uses this, any attack can be deflected.&#13;&#10;But finding a person who does not fear death will be challenging in here. </text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_name_1">Inspired Courage</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_name_2">Reckless Courage</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_desc_1">Movment Speed +10 Attack Speed +10&#13;&#10;The courage grows and makes everything seem possible.</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_desc_2">HP -5 Movment Speed +10 Attack Speed +10&#13;&#10;The overflowing courage is constantly looking to kill.</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_desc_3">HP -10 Movment Speed +15 Attack Speed +15&#13;&#10;The courage that is endlessly sprouting may soon cut everything off.</text>
  <text id="ArmorCreature_gift_desc_4">HP -20 Movment Speed +20 Attack Speed +20&#13;&#10;The ever-growing courage gave rise to recklessness and devoured everything.</text>
  <text id="LittleWitch_weapon_name">Laetitia</text>
  <text id="LittleWitch_weapon_desc">It takes a lot of time, but its power cannot be ignored.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The crude design looks to have been made a long time ago.&#13;&#10;The small accessory remains like the hope of a small child that yearns for happiness. </text>
  <text id="LittleWitch_armor_desc">The ribbon on the coat represents a child’s yearn for happiness.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Since the kid could not leave her friend behind, she thought of a brilliant idea.</text>
  <text id="NamelessFetus_weapon_name">Crier</text>
  <text id="NamelessFetus_weapon_desc">What cry can be more powerful than that for primal desire.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As if every other thing is all meaningless, the sound of the cry numbs even the brain, making it impossible to think. </text>
  <text id="Nullthing_weapon_name">Mimicry</text>
  <text id="Nullthing_weapon_desc">It's form is sloppy, as if saying your yearning to imitate the form of a human should have ended at greed.&#13;&#10;When the otherworldly eyes stare at you, you will tremble.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;If pushed to the limit, you can wield it. It can deliver a powerful downswing that is impossible for a single human.</text>
  <text id="Nullthing_weapon_specialDesc">Restores HP by 25% of the damage done to the target.</text>
  <text id="Nullthing_armor_desc">To protect humans, you need the skin of a human. &#13;&#10;Even though it is not the skin of a human, the skin that is akin to it protects us.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Employees who wear it may lose whatever humanity they have left. </text>
  <text id="Freischutz_weapon_name">Magic Bullet</text>
  <text id="Freischutz_weapon_desc">Though unable to fully extract the power of the prototype, the magical power it holds is still potent.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The bullet crosses the corridor along the horizon.</text>
  <text id="Butterfly_weapon_name">Solemn Vow</text>
  <text id="Butterfly_weapon_desc">The atmosphere is grave. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;One represents the sadness of the dead, the other represents the fear of the quick.</text>
  <text id="Butterfly_armor_desc">Black is for those who mourn the dead.&#13;&#10;It requires solemnness and no accessories.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;When you see a shallow grave in the desert, mourn for the butterflies. </text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_gift_Desc">SP +2 Movment Speed +4 Attack Speed +4</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_weapon_name">A Sword Sharpened by Tears</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_weapon_desc">A sword suitable for quick thrusts.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Even someone not skilled in sword fights can rapidly puncture an enemy with this E.G.O.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Like chivalry, there is no such thing as foul play and mercy in combat. </text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_armor_desc">Tears fall like ashes, embroidered like constellations. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The wearer will think of sadness. Like the days when there’s nothing in particular in mind, but tears will pour out.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Perhaps sharing the burden will lighten your sorrow. </text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_gift_Desc">HP +5 SP +5</text>
  <text id="LookAtMe_armor_specialDesc">When you zoom in on an employee wearing that armor, employee's defense and Justice will rise 10.</text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_weapon_name">The Smile</text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_weapon_desc">Pale faces of nameless employees and a giant mouth are attached to it.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;When wielded, it devours a target with its monstrous mouth. Its hunger is insatiable. </text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_armor_desc">A familiar face is on it. The wearer suddenly feels the weight of death.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Enemy attacks will be blocked by the dead, protecting the user.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Sometimes you can hear the moaning of pain, but nothing can be done, so it’s better just to ignore it.</text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_armor_specialDesc">Recovering HP when passing over an employee's dead body.</text>
  <text id="DangoCreature_weapon_specialDesc">Each time Hp of attack target becomes 0, the Fortitude, Justice 3 rise.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Decrease the target’s movement speed when performing a normal attack.&#13;&#10;Decrease all enemy’s movement speed in that passage when performing a special attack.</text>
  <text id="ViscusSnake_armor_name">Shed Skin</text>
  <text id="ViscusSnake_armor_desc">Its slippery surface may disturb some employees, but its scales are multi-layered, suitable for protection.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Even when it is torn, its regenerative abilities will soon repair itself. </text>
  <text id="Shark_armor_name">Ecstasy</text>
  <text id="Shark_armor_desc">There are needle marks on the arm.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The colorful pattern makes it look like a fancy kid’s costume. </text>
  <text id="BlackSwan_weapon_name">Black Swan</text>
  <text id="BlackSwan_weapon_desc">Believing that it will turn white, the black swan wanted to lift the curse by weaving nettle. All that was left was a worn parasol it once treasured.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It yearned for a never-waking dream, but reality was cruel. </text>
  <text id="BlackSwan_armor_desc">In the full smoke they repeated a day like a phantom.&#13;&#10;Whenever she thought she was exhausted, she kept her heart in a brooch with memories.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Seaweeds under dirty lakes are as damp as black swan feathers.</text>
  <text id="BlackSwan_weapon_specialDesc">When attacked, the damage is reflected with a certain probability.</text>
  <text id="1.76mhz_armor_name">Noise</text>
  <text id="1.76mhz_armor_desc">Instead of a clear shape, it's form is an electromagnetic phenomenon.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;When this E.G.O is equipped, various screams will boom along with an eerie ringing. As if taking you to the very moment of the day that everyone forgot. </text>
  <text id="LookAtMe_armor_name">Gaze</text>
  <text id="LookAtMe_armor_desc">The eyes behind the door keeps gazing on its target. No one knows what it wants to see.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;At least there won’t be an ambush while you equip this. </text>
  <text id="BloodyTree_weapon_name">Heaven</text>
  <text id="BloodyTree_weapon_desc">It lives inside your eyes. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As soon as you open your wings toward to a long forgotten god, the heaven for you is digging.</text>
  <text id="Lumberjack_weapon_name">Logging</text>
  <text id="Lumberjack_weapon_desc">An ax suitable for cutting trees and humans.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As if honing the blade was done religiously, the blade is always shiny.</text>
  <text id="Fairy_weapon_name">Wingbeat</text>
  <text id="Fairy_weapon_desc">The weapon with the blessing of the fairies shines with a pale light.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Unlike the wing's adorable form, the E.G.O itself is heavy.</text>
  <text id="Fairy_armor_desc">The sprouting wings are as mischievous as fairy pranks.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It goes without saying but the wings don't allow you flight.&#13;&#10;Wearing this E.G.O may make it easier to receive the care of fairies. </text>
  <text id="Bunny_armor_name">Lantern</text>
  <text id="Bunny_armor_desc">The brilliantly shining luminous body seems perfect for illuminating the darkness.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It is also can be an excellent bait in the darkness.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;However, the teeth that extend from the armor are terrifying.</text>
  <text id="Censored_weapon_name">CENSORED</text>
  <text id="Censored_weapon_desc">(CENSORED) can be (CENSORED) but gives the audience a horrendous feeling.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Looking at the E.G.O for more than 3 seconds will make you sick. </text>
  <text id="Censored_weapon_specialDesc">Recover 40% of damage when being hit</text>
  <text id="Scarecrow_weapon_name">Harvest</text>
  <text id="Scarecrow_weapon_desc">The last legacy from the one yearned for wisdom.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The long rake cultivated the human brain instead of a field.&#13;&#10;How many wise people lost their lives to this rake?</text>
  <text id="Wraith_weapon_name">Diffraction</text>
  <text id="Wraith_weapon_desc">To see this E.G.O, strong concentration is required.&#13;&#10;You can ignore the ridiculous advice that you should see it with your mind.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It may be in your best interest to calculate the radius when you swing since it is invisible.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Many employees sustained injuries from when the E.G.O was swung.</text>
  <text id="GalaxyBoy_armor_name">Galaxy</text>
  <text id="GalaxyBoy_armor_desc">The pebble in your hand sparkles, sways, tickles,&#13;&#10;And it becomes the universe.&#13;&#10;"There is a universe inside of the pebble.When the boy cries, a star borns in it.  Am I part of your universe?"</text>
  <text id="GalaxyBoy_armor_specialDesc">Increase the recovering amount of friend's token</text>
  <text id="ShyThing_armor_name">Today’s Expression</text>
  <text id="ShyThing_armor_desc">Various facial expressions are layered over each other, as if they were cloth.&#13;&#10;Failure to reveal a facial expression may be a form of shyness.&#13;&#10;Let's hide your face when you feel like you cannot hide your feelings anymore.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_weapon_name">Sound of a Star</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_weapon_desc">The star shines from our despair.&#13;&#10;A small ball of nostalgia fires warm rays.&#13;&#10;In the light, everything is equal.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_weapon_specialDesc">Attack power change according to employee's current mentality</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_armor_desc">There's an area of the heart that is shining a mysterious light.&#13;&#10;Rather than flashing, it is gleaming.&#13;&#10;If you look carefully, you can see that we will have to return someday. </text>
  <text id="BlueStar_armor_specialDesc">Recover other employees in the same space certain time</text>
  <text id="Porccu_weapon_name">Pleasure</text>
  <text id="Porccu_weapon_desc">If you look for a pleasure that can not be tolerated, the end reaches the loss of self.&#13;&#10;If the powder falling from the thorns is known to the world, people may forever fall out of the swamp.</text>
  <text id="Porccu_weapon_specialDesc">Additional W damage for a certain amount of time</text>
  <text id="SingingMachine_weapon_name">Harmony</text>
  <text id="SingingMachine_weapon_desc">Even if it looks like a seemingly corrosive machine, the songs that come out of it captivate those who listen more than any other instrument.&#13;&#10;Instead, the user must dedicate himself.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Art is the gift of the devil from despair and suffering.&#13;&#10;Do not stop playing until your body breaks like powder.</text>
  <text id="SingingMachine_weapon_specialDesc">Weapon damage +30% by consuming hp when the employee's hp is 10% or more</text>
  <text id="RedHood_weapon_name">Crimson Scar</text>
  <text id="RedHood_weapon_desc">There’s nothing to fear in this place if as long as you hold iron in one hand and gunpowder in another.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Attacking in blind rage and without hesitation is more important than insecure courage.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Let’s hope this lovely fairy tale will come to an end someday.</text>
  <text id="RedHood_weapon_specialDesc">Weapon damage +50% when the employee's hp is 50% or less.&#13;&#10;However, if employee attack in that state, damage will be applied to other employees</text>
  <text id="RedHood_armor_desc">The only thing a mercenary with a red bandanna could love is the death of a wolf.&#13;&#10;It seems only darkness awaits at the path of those who feel alive from nothing but destruction.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Sometimes, it’s good to let go of old hatred, just like letting weight off your shoulders.</text>
  <text id="RedHood_armor_specialDesc">Movement Speed +30% when suppressing</text>
  <text id="RedHood_gift_Desc">HP +2 Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_weapon_name">Blue Scar</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_weapon_desc">Gauntlet that resembles the claws of a vicious wolf.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;These claws once ripped stomachs and cut the insides of many living creatures.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It cuts the target's flesh and makes it unable to stop its bleeding.</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_weapon_specialDesc">Additional R damage for a certain amount of time&#13;&#10;Weapon damage +50% when the employee's hp is 50% or less.&#13;&#10;However, if employee attack in that state, damage will be applied to other employees</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_armor_desc">There are many traces as if to alert of the history of the never ending battle.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As all wounds become nothing in the end, this equipment will make you feel dull from damages although it won’t protect you completely from them. </text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_gift_Desc">HP +4 Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_Special_name">Sheepskin</text>
  <text id="BigBadWolf_Special_gift_Desc">HP +9 SP -3.&#13;&#10;…That’s why I could slash the wolf’s belly and returned safely back here!</text>
  <text id="YoungPrince_weapon_name">Spore</text>
  <text id="YoungPrince_weapon_desc">A spear covered with spores and affection.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It reveals the minds of employees, shines like a star, and gradually becomes tamed.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Nostalgia is more miserable because it is invisible.</text>
  <text id="YoungPrince_weapon_specialDesc">Give Effect to the target by 25 % probability to make vulnerable to the W property</text>
  <text id="YoungPrince_armor_desc">If you only look at it with a big mushroom, it's the result of your hazy eyes.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;When the stars are lit up and the night is revealed, the true figure is revealed.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It is a blessing to me to recognize the hidden light.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_armor_name">Lamp</text>
  <text id="BigBird_armor_desc">The number of eyes of the big bird increased each time a forest creature was saved.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The armor shows its radiant pride.&#13;&#10;Dozens of those burning eyes are always looking toward one place.</text>
  <text id="BossBird_weapon_name">Twilight</text>
  <text id="BossBird_weapon_desc">Eyes that never close, a scale that could measure all sins, and a beak that could swallow everything protected the Black Forest in peace,&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;and those who could wield this could also bring peace.</text>
  <text id="BossBird_weapon_specialDesc">The employee with Fortitude, Prudence, Temperance, and Justice above 110 can equip.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Attack by all attack types (R, W, B, P)&#13;&#10;Attack with special attack pattern at regular intervals&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;If there is an employee wearing this equipment, Apocalypse bird will not appear.</text>
  <text id="BossBird_armor_desc">Efforts of three birds to defeat the beast became one.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It could stop countless incidents but you’d have to be prepared to step into the Black Forest.</text>
  <text id="BossBird_armor_specialDesc">The lower the HP of an employee with that weapon, the greater the damage.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;If targets stay in the same passage for more than 5 seconds, take B damage every 5 seconds.&#13;&#10;Effect of equipping all E.G.O of the Apocalypse bird: The damage type of special ability is extended to R, W, B, P&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;If there is an employee wearing this equipment, Apocalypse bird will not appear.</text>
  <text id="BossBird_Special_name">Through dark twilight</text>
  <text id="BossBird_Special_gift_Desc">HP +7 SP +7 Success Rate +7 Work Speed +7 Movment Speed +7 Attack Speed +7&#13;&#10;They withstood the twilight and faced the dawn. In the forest, did the birds' twitter stop?</text>
  <text id="Baku_weapon_name">Rapturous Dream</text>
  <text id="Baku_weapon_desc">We must be awake.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;No sweet dreams are allowed here.&#13;&#10;This weapon shall wake those who are soaked in such illusions.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The dawn will break, when the sound stops.</text>
  <text id="Baku_armor_desc">Its soft wool is warm. It makes you drowsy.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;As rapturous it is, the bigger disappointment it gives.&#13;&#10;The thirst is severe when the dawn breaks,&#13;&#10;I wait for you with my eyes closed.&#13;&#10;You, who will never come.</text>
  <text id="Baku_gift_Desc">SP +4</text>
  <text id="Sakura_weapon_name">Cherry Blossom</text>
  <text id="Sakura_weapon_desc">Petals scatter from the fan like afterimages, longing for the past view.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Spring breeze that dons cherry blossom petal, is cold and painful.&#13;&#10;Don’t miss me. I shall return as buds when winter leaves.</text>
  <text id="Sakura_armor_desc">This E.G.O makes hearts of those who look at it flutter.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Let us take a rest from life looking at those cherry blossoms. &#13;&#10;Sitting under the tree’s shadow makes you feel like these painful days are merely an illusion. </text>
  <text id="Sakura_gift_Desc">HP +2 Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2</text>
  <text id="MagicalGirl_weapon_name">In the name of love and hate</text>
  <text id="MagicalGirl_weapon_desc">A magical rod radiating with magical girl’s lovely energy.&#13;&#10;Bad people will be purified by its holy light and be born again.&#13;&#10;They will burn. They won’t want to wake up.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The love that wanted to protect everyone soon became an obsession that corrodes heart.&#13;&#10;Everything was over when she tried to make it right.</text>
  <text id="MagicalGirl_weapon_specialDesc">Attack with random attack type&#13;&#10;Depending on the type of attack, recover HP and SP of employees who hit by the projectile of the weapon</text>
  <text id="MagicalGirl_armor_desc">Magical dress infused with magical girl’s love and justice.&#13;&#10;Wearing it may ignite your spirit of justice and desire to protect the world,&#13;&#10;and you hear the sound of hatred, sinking deeper than love. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;What should we do?&#13;&#10;I made my mind to love everything in the world, but what’s left is a broken heart.</text>
  <text id="MagicalGirl_gift_Desc">Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2 Movment Speed +4 Attack Speed +4</text>
  <text id="Yin_weapon_name">Discord</text>
  <text id="Yin_weapon_desc">A falchion shadowed by the world. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Every life is trapped in the cycle of birth and death. &#13;&#10;The power of birth, and the power of death. There is no good or evil about those powers.&#13;&#10;They are just the way it was meant to be. </text>
  <text id="Yin_armor_desc">A coat shadowed by discord.This shadow protects the wearer from various harms. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;However, all the damage that is blocked by it could be inflicted on someone else. &#13;&#10;Everything must be balanced.</text>
  <text id="FireBird_weapon_name">Feather of Honor</text>
  <text id="FireBird_weapon_desc">The feather strikes with vivid flames. It is not weak, nor faint.&#13;&#10;The flames that pierce the body melts the frozen body and heart.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It is Fiery Bird’s wish that people don’t lose their passion forever.</text>
  <text id="FireBird_armor_desc">The fire cannot reach the heart.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It is bright as if it’s burning, but once you touch it, you will realize that it is not hot at all.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Burn yourself in awe.</text>
  <text id="DeathAngel_weapon_name">Paradise Lost</text>
  <text id="DeathAngel_weapon_desc"><i>I knocked on the door, and it opened.</i>&#13;&#10;<i>I am from the end, I am merely staying.</i>&#13;&#10;<i>I am the one who kindled the lantern to face the world.</i>&#13;&#10;<i>My loved ones, I shall show thou the best path from now on.</i></text>
  <text id="DeathAngel_armor_desc"><i>Thou shall not worry; I have heard your prayers.</i>&#13;&#10;<i>Have thou not yet realized that pain is nothing?</i>&#13;&#10;<i>Thou want me to prove the miracle.</i>&#13;&#10;<i>Thou shall believe in me and granted with life. I shall show you the power.</i></text>
  <text id="DeathAngel_weapon_specialDesc">Unable to recover HP,SP by regenerator when equipped with the weapon&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Decrease the target’s movement speed and recover HP,SP when performing a normal attack (The amount of damage and heal varies according to the number of targets)&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Create a shield that blocks every type of damage when performing a special attack. (However, special attacks are only carried out when the Abnormality is inside the facility.)</text>
  <text id="DeathAngel_armor_specialDesc">Defense increased if the Abnormality exists in the facility (R: 0.2 / W: 0.2 / B: 0.2 / P: 0.2)&#13;&#10;Immune to damages that are 5 or lower upon suppression.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;White Night’s E.G.O equipment effect: Absorb damages that are 10 or lower upon suppression.</text>
  <text id="PlaugeDoctor_weapon_name">Bless</text>
  <text id="PlaugeDoctor_gift_Desc">HP +6 SP +6 Success Rate +6 Work Speed +6 Movment Speed +6 Attack Speed +6</text>

  <text id="Dummy_weapon_name">Training standard E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Dummy_weapon_desc">E.G.O for manager education</text>
  <text id="Dummy_armor_desc">E.G.O for manager education</text>
  <text id="Dummy_gift_Desc">HP +2 SP +2</text>

  <text id="PinkCorps_weapon_name">Pinks</text>
  <text id="PinkCorps_weapon_desc">Pink is considered to be the color of warmth and love.&#13;&#10;But is it true?&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Can you practice love with a gun?</text>
  <text id="PinkCorps_armor_desc">Pink Uniform.&#13;&#10;Its pockets allow the wearer to carry various types of ammunition. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It soothes you.&#13;&#10;Pink provides psychological comfort to many people.</text>
  <text id="PinkCorps_gift_Desc">SP +5 Attack Speed +5&#13;&#10;Increases the damage of this Abnormality's weapon by 15% when the relevant Abnormality’s armor is equipped</text>
  <text id="Ppodae_weapon_name">CUTE!!!!!</text>
  <text id="Ppodae_weapon_desc">I thought, how can a weapon drawn from such a cute abnormality be any good?&#13;&#10;But I was wrong. The claw was durable and sharp.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Beware that the beast inside you may awake if you use this weapon too much.&#13;&#10;But the jelly-like paw pad feels much gud to touch. </text>
  <text id="FengYun_weapon_name">Amita</text>
  <text id="FengYun_weapon_desc">A cane used by monks when they go outside their temple.&#13;&#10;It is used to measure the depth of a body of water or drive animals or insects away.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The rings attached to the cane means the middle way and Six Paramitas.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;You can become Buddha by washing away anguish and delusions in your heart. I wanted to believe. </text>
  <text id="FengYun_armor_desc">An old and ragged cloth of a monk that shows his dedication. &#13;&#10;This plain and simple cloth with patches is a sign of the monk’s practice of asceticism.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;You can smell old dirt and fire if you put your nose close enough.</text>
  <text id="SlimeGirl_weapon_name">Adoration</text>
  <text id="SlimeGirl_weapon_desc">A big mug with mysterious slime inside. &#13;&#10;It’s a by-product of some horrid experiment that eventually failed.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;People who touch this slime complain strange sensation on their skin. But it won’t stop there.</text>
  <text id="SlimeGirl_weapon_specialDesc">Reduces the Movement Speed of the target by 30% for 5 seconds&#13;&#10;Additional B damage for a certain amount of time</text>
  <text id="SlimeGirl_armor_desc">It is not as unpleasant to wear as to look at. &#13;&#10;It gives you an illusion of comfort and bravery.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Be cautious because when the attachment gets too strong, it will hold onto the wearer and won’t let go.</text>
  <text id="Yggdrasil_weapon_name">Hypocrisy</text>
  <text id="Yggdrasil_weapon_desc">All things turn to dust someday.&#13;&#10;Thus, this evergreen crossbow is far from mother nature.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The tree is riddled with hypocrisy and deception,&#13;&#10;those who wear its blessing act on the name of bravery and faith.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;But beware that the nature does not know the difference between the blessing and curse.</text>
  <text id="Yggdrasil_armor_desc">All things turn to dust someday.&#13;&#10;Thus, this evergreen robe is far from mother nature.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;The tree is riddled with hypocrisy and deception,&#13;&#10;those who wear its blessing act on the name of bravery and faith.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;But beware that the nature does not know the difference between the blessing and curse.</text>
  <text id="Yggdrasil_armor_specialDesc">Heals a small amount of SP of the employees in the same area for every few moments</text>
  <text id="Piano_weapon_name">Moonlight</text>
  <text id="Piano_weapon_desc">A cane.&#13;&#10;One of the mementos that were in the place where the lady who offered soul to the moon left. &#13;&#10;The snake shaped ornament is loyal to the original owner’s taste.&#13;&#10;The spread snake’s mouth represents endless yearning for music.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;It temporarily invites the user to the world of trance.</text>
  <text id="Piano_weapon_specialDesc">Casts B type shields on every employee in the area when performing special attack</text>
  <text id="Piano_armor_desc">A classic, dark, mushroom-looking dress.&#13;&#10;You may take a step towards the truth of the moon that is so difficult to understand if you wear it.&#13;&#10;It temporarily invites the wearer to the world of trance.</text>

  <text id="LookAtMe_weapon_specialDesc">Additional B damage for a certain amount of time</text>
  <text id="ViscusSnake_weapon_specialDesc">Give Effect to the target by 25 % probability to make vulnerable to the R property</text>
  <text id="BigBird_weapon_specialDesc">Give Effect to the target by 25 % probability to make vulnerable to the B property</text>
  <text id="Freischutz_armor_specialDesc">Max. and Min. Attack Power +3 when the weapon from the same Abnormality is equipped</text>

  <text id="Freischutz_gift_Desc">HP -5 SP -5 Movment Speed +10 Attack Speed +10&#13;&#10;Max. and Min. Attack Power +3 when the weapon from the same Abnormality is equipped</text>
  <text id="NamelessFetus_gift_Desc">HP -2 SP -2 Movment Speed +6 Attack Speed +6&#13;&#10;Reduces W damage by 5%</text>
  <text id="Nullthing_gift_Desc">HP +10&#13;&#10;Increases an amount of HP healed by 5%</text>
  <text id="Yin_gift_Desc">HP -10 SP -10 Movment Speed +20 Attack Speed +20&#13;&#10;When attacked, heals as much as the damage taken by the chance of 8%</text>
  <text id="1.76mhz_gift_Desc">Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2&#13;&#10;SP -10, Attack Speed +10 when the weapon from the same Abnormality is equipped</text>
  <text id="GalaxyBoy_gift_Desc">Success Rate +3 Work Speed +3&#13;&#10;Heals a small amount of HP of the employee</text>
  <text id="SingingMachine_gift_Desc">HP +8 SP -4&#13;&#10;When attacked by W damage, recovery by 20% of damage and Attack Speed +10</text>

  <text id="ShyThing_gift_Desc">SP -2 Success Rate +4 Work Speed +4</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_gift_Desc">Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2</text>
  <text id="Ppodae_gift_Desc">HP +4 Success Rate -2 Work Speed -2</text>
  <text id="Cosmos_gift_Desc">Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="Bunny_gift_Desc">HP +5</text>
  <text id="StraitJacket_gift_Desc">HP +2 SP +2</text>
  <text id="BloodBath_gift_Desc">Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="Butterfly_gift_Desc">HP +1 SP +1 Success Rate +1 Work Speed +1 Movment Speed +1 Attack Speed +1</text>
  <text id="Scarecrow_gift_Desc">SP +4</text>
  <text id="Porccu_gift_Desc">SP +10 Success Rate -6 Work Speed -6</text>
  <text id="Rudolph_gift_Desc">HP -4 SP +8</text>
  <text id="Lumberjack_gift_Desc">HP +2 Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="LookAtMe_gift_Desc">HP +4</text>
  <text id="LittleWitch_gift_Desc">SP +4</text>
  <text id="BlackSwan_gift_Desc">HP -4 SP -4 Success Rate +10 Work Speed +10</text>
  <text id="FireBird_gift_Desc">SP +2 Movment Speed +4 Attack Speed +4</text>
  <text id="Piano_gift_Desc">HP +1 SP +1 Success Rate +1 Work Speed +1 Movment Speed +1 Attack Speed +1</text>
  <text id="Shark_gift_Desc">SP +6</text>
  <text id="ViscusSnake_gift_Desc">HP +5 SP +2</text>
  <text id="YoungPrince_gift_Desc">SP +5 Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="FengYun_gift_Desc">HP +10 SP -4</text>
  <text id="Wraith_gift_Desc">SP +6</text>
  <text id="BloodyTree_gift_Desc">HP +4 Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_gift_Desc">HP +2 SP +4</text>
  <text id="BigBird_gift_Desc">HP +3 Success Rate +3 Work Speed +3</text>
  <text id="Yggdrasil_gift_Desc">HP +3 SP +3</text>
  <text id="Censored_gift_Desc"> SP +10</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_gift_Desc">Movment Speed +10</text>
  <text id="SlimeGirl_gift_Desc">HP +5 SP +10 Success Rate -5 Work Speed -5</text>
  <text id="Fairy_gift_Desc">Success Rate +2 Work Speed +2</text>
  <text id="Wellcheers_gift_Desc">HP +2</text>
  <text id="Bald_gift_Desc">Movment Speed +2 Attack Speed +2</text>

  <text id="SlimeGirl_armor_specialDesc">When E.G.O GIFT is equipped, creates R type shield when more than 10 damage is taken while HP is under 20%&#13;&#10;Movement speed is reduced by 50% when the shield is activated.</text>

</localize>