<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304011">
    <Name>Woof ruff! Doodly-doo? Heehaw~!</Name>
    <Desc>On a successful Blunt attack, deal 1-2 bonus Stagger damage.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304012">
    <Name>Triarchy</Name>
    <Desc>The first three Speed dice use Combat Pages that belong to specific heads.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304013">
    <Name>Uncontrollable Performance</Name>
    <Desc>Cannot be Staggered. Starting with the second Scene, performs the following action every 3 Scenes: uses a Mass Attack page, then all resistances change to "Fatal" on the following Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304014">
    <Name>Shimmering</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Scene, exhaust all pages in hand and deck; add new pages to hand. Their Cost becomes 0.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304015">
    <Name>From the Top</Name>
    <Desc>Every Scene, one head becomes active. Each head uses different Combat Pages.
On certain Scenes, uses special Combat Pages that inflict the target with 'Tagged', a status effect that allows them to gain a copy of a Combat Page after winning a clash against it.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1304016">
    <Name>Busted Chops</Name>
    <Desc>When Staggered, the Speed die that belongs to the currently active head will break, and the character will recover from Stagger next Scene.
When all heads are destroyed, the battle progresses to the next phase.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <!--뒤틀림-->

  <PassiveDesc ID="1404011">
    <Name>Martial Song of the Battlefield</Name>
    <Desc>While this character is alive, give an ally a random positive status effect. (Strength, Endurance, or Haste) The amount given equals the amount of Light this character has.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <PassiveDesc ID="1404012">
    <Name>Beklemmt Resolve</Name>
    <Desc>Loses all Light when Staggered.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <PassiveDesc ID="1404013">
    <Name>Erlöschend Dirge of a War Grave</Name>
    <Desc>Upon death: all enemies gain 3 Strength, Endurance, and Haste next scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
</PassiveDescRoot>
