<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301011">
    <Name>Shimmering</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Scene, exhaust all pages in hand and deck; add new pages to hand. Their Cost becomes 0.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301012">
    <Name>Searing Sword</Name>
    <Desc>While Overheated: inflict 1 Burn to target on hit, and inflict 1 Burn to attacker when hit.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301013">
    <Name>Searing Sword</Name>
    <Desc>While Overheated: inflict 1 Burn to target on hit, and inflict 1 Burn to attacker when hit.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301014">
    <Name>A Blade Ablaze</Name>
    <Desc>Inflict 1 Burn to target on hit, and inflict 1 Burn to attacker when hit.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <!--공용-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301015">
    <Name>Cooled Heart</Name>
    <Desc>Takes no damage from Burn.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301016">
    <Name>Sword of Embers</Name>
    <Desc>When inflicting Burn using Combat Pages, apply +1 additional stack.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301017">
    <Name>Tempered Passion</Name>
    <Desc>Whenever the Emotion Level rises, inflict 3 Burn to all characters, including self.
Gain Power by half the current Emotion Level (Rounded down)</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1301018">
    <Name>Overheat</Name>
    <Desc>If the character has 15 or more Burn at the start of the Scene, become Overheated, dealing more damage with attacks but becoming more vulnerable to Stagger damage.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <!--1페이즈에 나옴-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301019">
    <Name>Crackling Heart</Name>
    <Desc>HP does not go below 60% of Max HP. When Staggered, proceeds to the next phase, change resistances, and purge all status ailments from self.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <!--2페이즈에 나옴-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301030">
    <Name>Vanished Mind</Name>
    <Desc>When an Unspeaking Child is defeated, lose Power by the number of Unspeaking Children that have been put down so far next Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301032">
    <Name>Sizzling Heart</Name>
    <Desc>HP does not go below 30% of Max HP. When Staggered, proceeds to the next phase, change resistances, and purge all status ailments from self.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301021">
    <Name>Torched Heart</Name>
    <Desc>Takes half as much damage from Burn. Starting with the Scene after it was spawned, gain 1 Strength and Endurance every Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301022">
    <Name>Overheat</Name>
    <Desc>If the character has 15 or more Burn at the start of the Scene, become Overheated, dealing more damage with attacks but becoming more vulnerable to Stagger damage.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1301023">
    <Name>Combustion</Name>
    <Desc>While Overheated: gain 3 Fragile each scene, and inflict 1 Burn to target on hit. Also, uses a different set of Combat Pages.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <!--뒤틀림-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1401011">
    <Name>Borrowed Embers</Name>
    <Desc>While alive, the first Offensive die allies play each engagement inflicts 1 Burn on hit.
After death, allies are inflicted with 1 Burn when hit.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1401012">
    <Name>Supraheat</Name> <!-- "Supra-" + "Heat" -->
    <Desc>If the character has 10 or more Burn at the start of the Scene, become Overheated, dealing more damage.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1401014">
    <Name>Scorching Desperation</Name>
    <Desc>Every 3 Scenes: 'Scorching Desperation' is added to hand, which will be used the same Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1401017">
    <Name>Restraints</Name>
    <Desc>On hit against a target with 3 or more stacks of 'Restraint', Immobilize them for the next Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>>
</PassiveDescRoot>
