<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">

  <!-- 아르갈리아 뒤틀림-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1410011">
    <Name>Shimmering</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Scene, exhaust all pages in hand and deck; add new pages to hand. Their Cost becomes 0.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1410012">
    <Name>Il Direttore dell’Ensemble Riverbero</Name>
    <Desc>While Pluto or Elena are alive, HP does not go below 100. Gain a Speed die for every other Ensemble member that died this reception.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1410013">
    <Name>Emozioni Intensificantesi</Name>
    <Desc>Every 4 Scenes, give all Reverberation Ensemble members 'For the duration of the Act, gain 1 Strength and Endurance every Scene'.
At the end of the Scene, all characters' Emotion Levels rise by 2.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1410014">
    <Name>The Grand Finale</Name>
    <Desc>If no other Reverberation Ensemble members are present, fully recover Stagger Resist, and use a different set of Combat Pages.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>

  <!-- 엘레나 뒤틀림-->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1408011">
    <Name>Shimmering</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Scene, exhaust all pages in hand and deck; add new pages to hand. Their Cost becomes 0.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1408012">
    <Name>Speed</Name>
    <Desc>Speed Dice Slot +1. Gain a Speed die on the fourth Scene. Gain an additional one if there's an enemy whose Emotion Level is 4 or higher.
Does not gain Speed dice from Emotion Level bonuses.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  
  <!-- 플루토 뒤틀림 -->
  <PassiveDesc ID="1409011">
    <Name>Shimmering</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Scene, exhaust all pages in hand and deck; add new pages to hand. Their Cost becomes 0.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1409012">
    <Name>Unconscionable</Name>
    <Desc>Every Scene, uses an 'Unjust Contract' Combat Page.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1409013">
    <Name>Stygian Shade</Name>
    <Desc>Spawns a Shade on the second Scene. The Shade gets a copy of the Patron Librarian's hand and deck (Excluding [On Play] pages). If the Patron Librarian is not present, a random other librarian's deck will be copied instead.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  
  
  <PassiveDesc ID="1409021">
    <Name>Without Light</Name>
    <Desc>If Pluto is not present at the end of the Scene, dies.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
  <PassiveDesc ID="1409022">
    <Name>Powerful Shadow</Name>
    <Desc>Dice Power +1. Uses the Shade's Combat Page every Scene.</Desc>
  </PassiveDesc>
 
</PassiveDescRoot>