<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id="300002">
    <narration action="move">
      #0 is on their way to $0’s Containment Unit to begin the work process.
    </narration>
  </info>
  <observe level="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel="0">T-09-78</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/ResearcherNote</portrait>
      <name openLevel="1">
        Notes from a Crazed Researcher
      </name>
      <riskLevel openLevel="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>
      <openText>The final chapter ends with the phrase: “Born again.”
      </openText>
    </collection>
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {The old notes are full of incomprehensible cursive letters and writings. }
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {They once belonged to a researcher who had gone mad during their work. It’s only been partially deciphered, but it seems most of it relates to the various experiments that were conducted in this place. }
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {It begins with guilt and confessions of unethical experimentation but gradually spirals into madness, overrun with insane and broken up sentences about research toward the end.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">

      [
      {The final chapter ends with the phrase: “Born again.”}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {One’s observational skill will improve just by holding this item. However, if it is returned without fulfilling the yearning for knowledge, the incompetent shall explode. }
      ]
    </desc>
    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">Those who equip $0 will benefit from a sharp increase in the stats related to Temperance.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">If ordered to return $0 within 30 seconds of equipping, the user’s skin will start to swell and their body will explode within seconds.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">If ordered to return $0 without performing any sort of managerial work, the user will explode.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="4">If the user receives a certain amount of damage, they will explode, and the explosion will cover the entire section. The explosion will deal massive RED damage to all nearby.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>