<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id="300006">
    <narration action="move">
      #0 is on their way to $0’s Containment Unit to begin the work process.
    </narration>
  </info>
  <observe level="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel="0">T-09-82</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Shelter</portrait>
      <name openLevel="1">
        Shelter from the 27th of March
      </name>
      <riskLevel openLevel="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>
      <openText>
        It literally makes itself into “the safest place on Earth.”
      </openText>
    </collection>
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {A bomb shelter that completely protects its interior from all hazardous influences of the outside world, including light.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {The shelter still retains the memory of that day.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Company P wished to construct the safest place on Earth. As such, the interior of this shelter houses a large number of non-perishable goods, which would allow anyone who stayed inside to survive for an extremely long period of time.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      <!-- Translation has been fixed here ;) -->
      [
      {Thanks to this shelter, the selected refugees were safely shielded from the ocean of endless screams and bloodshed.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {However, this shelter, while perfectly safe on the inside, alters the reality of the outside to be even more hopeless. It literally makes itself into “the safest place on Earth.”}
      ]
    </desc>
    <specialTipSize size="3">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">Any subject who enters $0 will be immune to all forms of damage. (However, this does not apply to damage caused by O-09-91). Furthermore, the subject’s HP and SP will slowly recover starting the moment they enter $0.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">If a subject enters $0 while being pursued by a hostile entity, the subject will become undetectable to the pursuer.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">If any subject remains inside $0 for more than 30 seconds, the Qliphoth Counter of a randomly chosen Abnormality currently contained in the facility will fall to 0. Such a phenomenon will repeatedly occur to all Containment Units until the subject exits $0.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>