<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id="100002">
    <narration action="move">
      #0 is on their way to $0’s Containment Unit to begin the work process.
    </narration>
    <narration action="start">
      [
      {$0 looks just like the teddy bears everyone had when they were young.},
      {$0 always wanted to hug children.},
      {$0 loves hugs. Its memories began with a warm hug.},
      {A teddy bear is born from happiness, so it needs to be happy at all times.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {$0 appears to be lost in thought, forlornly gazing at the stuffing that pokes and spills out of its seams.},
      {The dirty ribbon around $0’s neck ruffles gently even though there is no wind to move it. The name that was written on that ribbon is worn away and unrecognizable by now.},
      {$0 doesn’t move an inch, as if it is gazing towards nothing. In fact, it’s looking at a photo of a young girl.},
      {$0’s plastic eye silently dangles by a thread on the left side of its face.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {While #0 is busy working, $0 continues to gaze upon the picture frame.},
      {Even if there’s a commotion, $0 will fixedly stare at the picture.},
      {It seems the picture in front of it is the only thing that matters to $0.},
      {#0 was unable to draw $0’s attention away from the photo.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {While working, #0 approaches $0 and refastens its frayed ribbon.},
      {#0 takes a moment to dust off the picture frame $0 so dotingly gazes upon.},
      {When #0 begins to mend the tears and rips on its plush body, $0 does not react.},
      {#0 tidies up $0 a bit, however it does not react.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {$0 remembers the birthday party of that wonderful seven-year-old girl. It waited to surprise her inside a large and colorful box.},
      {$0 remembers going on a wonderfully fun vacation with the young girl. It was named “Bearly”.},
      {$0 recalls the numerous nights it protected that young girl from the dark as she snuggled up in its arms.},
      {$0 fondly remembers the child, now grown. Somewhere beneath her dresser, moth balls were collecting on its body.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="special_ability">
      [
      {$0 extends its arms, dragging #0 into its wide embrace. #0 starts choking and thrashing about, trying to free themself.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="dead">
      [
      {#0’s bones begin to crunch and crack in $0’s arms. Its old fur smells of longing.},
      {$0 does not release its arms, keeping #0 from leaving. #0’s movements slow and stop. $0 just won’t let go of its hug.}    
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="panic">
      [
      {#0 is now helplessly depressed. Life is meaningless for them. #0 is nothing but a speck of dust in the wind in the grand scheme of things.}   
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>
  <observe level="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel="0">T-04-06</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Teddy</portrait>
      <name openLevel="1">
        A Teddy Bear
      </name>
      <name openLevel="2">
        Happy Teddy Bear
      </name>
      <riskLevel openLevel="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>
      <openText>Its memories began with a warm hug.</openText>
    </collection>
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {An Abnormality that resembles a large, raggedy teddy bear. It's missing some fur and only has one eye.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {The old ribbon around its neck hints that it may have received much affection from its previous owner. There is a name on the ribbon, but it is too tattered to be discernible. It seems that it knows it has been abandoned, and looks dejected. }
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {&lt;Excerpt from Counseling Log&gt;&#13;&#10;
      "I was on the night patrol. I didn't feel the need to pay attention to Happy Teddy since it was harmless for the most part. I just looked inside the Containment Unit to check on it. Teddy was hugging someone tightly. I thought it was (Redacted), the employee who was in charge of Teddy for a while, working late. But something was odd. I entered the unit and called (Redacted)'s name, but they didn't answer. I immediately pressed the emergency button to call in reinforcement. Turns out, (Redacted) had been in a coma for 8 hours. They were in Teddy's arms the whole time."}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {&lt;An Old Letter, Stamped with "Rejected"&gt;&#13;&#10;
      Remember what was written in the employee manual?
      "Do NOT have personal feelings towards Abnormalities."
      At first, I didn't get what that was supposed to mean.
      Does it even make sense to develop any emotion toward those monsters in the first place?
      It's okay. They are monsters. Between the two of us, we can call them that.
      'Happy Teddy Bear' was the second Abnormality you took charge of.
      I guess you must’ve thought that not all Abnormalities are monstrous after seeing it.
      The figure of an old, abandoned teddy bear may have brought up old memories of yours.
      Teddy seemed to like your hugs.
      Yeah, it would actually produce more energy when you were around.
      And in no time, they put you in charge of Teddy.
      You probably felt some kind of responsibility for it, right?
      I started getting worried as you visited Teddy's unit more and more often.
      It felt as if you were visiting an orphanage for volunteer work.
      …
      &lt;i&gt;It seems Teddy saw you as its new owner.
      Maybe you'd have been happy to hear that.
      But, you see, Teddy never wanted to be separate from its owner ever again.&lt;/i&gt;
      You probably always promised that you'd return.
      But it couldn't understand.
      I heard that you miraculously survived.
      And that they spent an hour trying to separate you from Teddy's embrace.
      Though others may forget about you.
      I will always remember you.
      May there be a miracle.}
    ]
  </desc>
    <specialTipSize size="2">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="manyDead">#0 died of asphyxiation after working with $0 multiple times in a row.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="manyDead2">#0 was found dead in $0’s arms with a broken neck. It is believed that visiting $0’s Containment Unit several times in a row is what causes these unfortunate incidents.&#13;&#10;Please refer to the “Old Letter” document for more information.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>