<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id="300004">
    <narration action="move">
      #0 is on their way to $0’s Containment Unit to begin the work process.
    </narration>
  </info>
  <observe level="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel="0">T-09-79</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/MeatIdol</portrait>
      <name openLevel="1">
        Flesh Idol
      </name>
      <riskLevel openLevel="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>
      <openText>
        And the prayer shall inevitably end with the eternal despair of its worshipper.
      </openText>
    </collection>
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {A meshing of flesh and scrap metal.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {It is speculated to be a religious artifact, found in the flooded district. In the past, some people sought answers through religion. When an employee offers up a prayer, the flesh begins to move, as if receiving the oration.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {The supplicant will suffer various ordeals in a manner like being put through a trial. Meanwhile, all those around them will recover their ails and woes just as if they were being blessed with redemption.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="4" openLevel="2">
      <!-- 여기 번역 고치기 -->
      [
      {And the prayer shall inevitably end with the eternal despair of its worshipper.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">$0’s effect can manifest through prayer. The one who prays will receive damage of a random type at regular intervals.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">&lt;Experiment 1&gt; The subject prayed for a duration of 20 seconds or less. They died.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">&lt;Experiment 2&gt; The subject prayed for a duration between 21 to 45 seconds. During this timeframe, all employees other than the subject recovered HP.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="4">&lt;Experiment 3&gt; The subject prayed for a duration between 46 to 90 seconds. The results were similar to Experiment 2, but SP was also recovered.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="5" key="5">&lt;Experiment 4&gt; The subject prayed for a duration longer than 90 seconds. They died, AND the Qliphoth Counters of all Abnormalities dropped to zero.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>