<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day49_adam_1">Welcome.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_2">You won’t believe how long I have been painstakingly waiting for you.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_3">Ah…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_4">The wait was getting so, so boring.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_5">You know, the world made of dots is no longer interesting to those who’ve realized the existence of lines, so to speak.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_6">Think about the world in which you used to be.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_7">Singularities are manifested day after day. Everything changes in the blink of an eye. </text>
  <text id="day49_adam_8">The Wings and the Head control this world, and now humanity cannot live without their constraints.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_9">Every single person just stays silent, even though each and every one of them knows how many ethically morbid compromises the Wings are making.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_10">Those who are not under the spell of control die as loners and failures. That’s where we’ve ended up.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_11">“Who was I in the past, who am I during the present, who should I be in the future?”</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_12">Those are the questions that bring upon growth, but people stopped asking them a long time ago. All anyone has left these days is to die a slow death.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_12_1">Nothing is as boring as watching a predetermined fall.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_13">So…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_14">We managed to find it.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_15">We found the light that resides in everyone.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_16">Unfortunately, the majority of humanity wouldn’t find their light on their own throughout their entire life.</text>
  <!---text id="day49_adam_17">그러니 사람들은 매일 곤경의 눈물을 흘리고 닿지 않는 희망을 바라보며 살아가야 해.</text> -->
  <text id="day49_adam_18">We are bound to be unhappy as long as we are chasing an illusion without realizing the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_19">People began to hide their light in the deepest recesses of their hearts.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_20">Carmen believed that she should draw out such light, the archetypes that had been hibernating.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_21">Yes, we could see the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_21_1">The Abnormalities are no longer abnormal; they are no mere fantasies anymore.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_21_2">They are our truer forms.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_22">Restored to being by drawing a little speck of light from our hearts.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_23">Abnormalities are the true humans of this age. They are the pure form that bursts out from the chrysalis that is our empty skin.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_24">They feared and tried to contain the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_24_1">Do not place blame upon their ignorance.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_24_2">It is only natural for one to fear being naked in the face of the world.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_25">At least you and I know one thing.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_26">Carmen shall be our forbidden fruit for the new humanity.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_27">Now, speak my name.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_28">I am Adam, soon to become the root of this new humanity.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_29">I will wait for the fruit to ripen and come to life after I seed this vast forest.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_30">The forbidden fruit shall enlighten us all with the long forgotten knowledge branded in our hearts.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_31">Just a single bite will open their eyes and grant them wisdom.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_31_1">They will be free of the sin of forgetfulness for what we truly are…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_32">And they will understand that they should feel shame for covering it in their shell.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_33">If we draw from everyone’s well with the Bucket, then their ego will have no need to be locked anymore.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_34">Just imagine it. Everything that was suppressed, bursting out in every shape and figure possible.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_35">Does it not make you tremble in excitement?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_36">We’ve always asked this question…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_37">How should a human live?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_38">No one could answer that…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_39">But I found the answer. </text>
  <text id="day49_adam_40">I shall show you. So join me.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_1">Do you want to know how I could be so cruel?</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_2">People live with their own anxieties.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_3">It is a natural price one must pay for confronting the unknown.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_4">However, I did not accept that anxiety, that fear. I devoured them to survive in this world.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_5">That was the first and final sin I have committed.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_6">I have no regrets about it. It was for survival.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_7">You were the same, no?</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_8">I knew so, witnessing your face as you ripped through my brain back then.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_9">You may also say it was an inevitable process.</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_10">However, it is about time you faced the fear that you have now forgotten, and dare I suggest…</text>
  <text id="day49_binah_11">Face that fear if you want to stop the cycle.</text>
  <text id="day49_selection1">The Eye Facing the Fear; Breaking the Cycle</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_41">Do you truly believe you can see things clearly, when you couldn’t even face them all this time?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_42">You are only saying this because you are afraid, aren’t you?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_43">If you truly think it is a misdeed to deprive them of the act of facing their fear…</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_44">Then listen well.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_45">If we can conduct hundreds, no, thousands of good deeds, committing one single sin is acceptable.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_46">Helping to shed everyone from their empty skin, can you not see how that is the greatest good of all?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_47">People need someone like us.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_48">Think about the wave of redemption that will follow.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_1">It is within every person’s instinct to pursue freedom.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_2">Please remember the reason why I happily let you pass.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_3">I did so because I wanted to see you fly with your own strength, despite being left in this harsh world with a skin as fragile as yours.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_4">Perhaps if we had talked more sincerely in the past…</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_5">Perhaps… it may have resulted in better circumstances.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_6">However, we have already left our past far behind us. There is no turning back.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_7">We live in endless conflict and regret, starting from birth up and unto death.</text>
  <text id="day49_hokma_8">We grow by embracing that conflict—that regret—and we walk towards the future.</text>
  <text id="day49_selection2">The Eye Embracing the Past; Building the Future</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_49">So you refuse to join me, and instead choose to move toward the unpredictable future?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_50">Our days will be filled with marvel and wonder that you cannot possibly imagine if you join me.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_51">You are painfully crawling through each day, and you still aren’t even sure if you are on the right path.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_52">Our sacred secret cannot be wasted like this, no.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_53">I cannot spare any more time. If you are not ready, I shall go first.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_54">..Are you…?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_55">Heh, so you don’t want to stop here, but instead stop me from going forward.</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_1">…………….</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_2">So you do not want me to be at your side, even for the finale of this play.</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_3">Those who shall face the end, together with you…</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_4">It seems I am not among them…</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_5"></text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_1">The flesh that lies within is bound to rot when it’s covered with ill-fitting skin.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_2">Do not worry; I shall demonstrate, for I know everything.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_3">You are me, and I am you.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_4">I am the only one of us who realized the one truth, and stood atop the world itself.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_5">I am the you who shall leave the paths I walked once, and choose to join the world she truly wanted to create.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_6">And you and I, we shall be the us who can do whatever we imagine from now on.</text>
  <text id="day49_selection3">.......</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_6_1">M-Monsters! Help me, please!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_6_2">Something weird’s g-growing out of me. L-Look at this, ahahahahaha!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_7">Behold.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_8">Witness how this loss-ridden world is perfected by us.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_9">The foolish god named rationality ruled over this world until this moment.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_10">No, to call it a god is an overstatement. It is simply a tragic illusion.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_11">We shall drag it down from the heavens with our own hands and open everyone’s eyes to the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_12">Yes, the world Carmen yearned for will soon unravel before your eyes.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_13">Let us create this paradise, you and I.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_13_1">Even the Head and the Eye are merely human. They cannot stop those of us who have accepted the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_14">You know that everything we witnessed in this land is only a shadow, and that you never saw the truth until now.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_15">With this, the plump fruit of redemption will reach everyone’s hearts.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_16">Those abandoned, those who hold power, those with wealth, those who remain hopeful, all of them.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_17">The tree of humanity will reach the root of this world.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_18">Again, behold.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_19">Did I not declare that all shall be free in the end?</text>
</localize>