<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day50_ayin_1">So, you’ve met your reflections, the pieces of the mirror?</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_2">They must have tried to stop you because their own tomorrows are not on the horizon.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_3">But you gave up the path to stay in those yesterdays with them.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_4">And now, we finally meet here today.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_5">You must have realized that as well, seeing as you have made it to this point without hesitation.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_6">I had known…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_6_1">For a very long time…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_7">That we all lost our hearts.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_8">I knew, and I didn’t do anything about it. I’m sure many others were the same way.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_9">...That’s what makes Carmen different from us.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_10">Instead of turning away, she wanted to save them, and guide their souls back.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_11">She was the one who made the noble decision to dedicate herself to save humanity.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_12">Yet I, who held no such ambition, had to continue her legacy.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_13">Ironic, isn’t it?</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_14">Maybe I was not the right man for the job. </text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_15">As you can see, we’ve become just like the other Wings, committing atrocities just like them.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_16">The employees here have repeated hundreds upon thousands of deaths…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_17">My friends were robbed of their lives and trapped in this cycle of agony…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_18">All the while I just sat and watched, justifying it all as the means to realize her ideal.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_19">This sin shall never be forgiven.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_20">Nonetheless…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_21">We must finish this.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_22">If these wrongdoings can finally cut this vicious cycle once and for all…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_23">I will gladly take this burden upon myself.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_24">Our mission is to simply seed the people’s hearts.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_25">Every single person has their own light. </text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_26">In the light, they create their own stories, and lay down the roots of their existence in it.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_27">We are merely there to sow the seeds. It is up to the people to bloom it in their own ways.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_28">What about us, you ask?</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_29">Unfortunately, we won’t be able to see what kind of forest will grow.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30">Besides, we still have one last thing to do…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_1">It is something we have done countless times.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_2">….It is time to manage the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_3">You’ll make it. I know you will.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_4">Come now.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_5">This will be our final day at work as the manager.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_31">A sprout burst from the land and grew into a towering tree, scattering fruit unto the world from its branches.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_32">The tree cultivated from the process of infinite possibilities is closer to the sky; it is more fierce than anything else.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_33">The borders between the past and the future, reality and illusion, the body and the mind, space and time… They all were slowly fading away.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_34">It is said that the void awaits at the end of the line…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_35">But I know that it is not just nothingness.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_36">You shall be the infinite light.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_37">Your name is Ayin.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_38">Remember this name of ours.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_39">Now…</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_40">Fade away without a trace.</text>
</localize>