<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g1">…</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g2">….Huh?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g3">What? Who are you?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_selection1">I'm the manager.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_selection2">&lt;i&gt;I’ll stay silent.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_1_g1">Ah, you’re the new manager?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_1_g2">Sorry, you don’t look anything like one.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_2_g1">Ah, so you’re the manager Tiphereth was talking about?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_2_g2">Ever heard of the saying, “silence gives consent”? Consent enough for even hot lead to be embedded in your skull?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_2_g3">You’d better watch yourself.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g4">The other departments may kiss your ass while you walk around with an air of arrogance as the manager.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g5">But here, that pompous attitude will knot itself into your noose.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g6">Well, seeing that you’ve at least made it here, I guess you won’t be a complete deadweight.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g7">I’m Gebura, head of Disciplinary.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g8">We’re the best department when it comes to combat out of all the teams. We have no need for cowards.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g9">You wanna know what kind of person I hate the most?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g10">Those crybabies who constantly whine about Abnormalities or employees being pitiful things, how they don’t want to see anything die.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g11">It’s the exact same as a soldier refusing to kill in the heat of the battlefield.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g12">As long as you’re not one of those annoyances, then we should get along just fine.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_selection3">You really seem to hate cowards.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_selection4">Couldn’t some Abnormalities be pitiful?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_3_g1">Shouldn’t it be obvious? They’re a hindrance.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_3_g2">Let me ask you this…</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_4_g1">Do you really think that’s possible?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g13">What do you think Abnormalities are?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g14">Holy entities? Poor defenseless creatures caged underground? Precious beings that make energy for us?</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g15">Totally wrong. They’re none of that.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g16">Abnormalities can be damaged, but never destroyed.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g17">At the very least, they seem to feel pain.</text>
  <text id="gebura1_intro_g18">Let’s make their unending lives as painful as possible.</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g1">Well, that task I gave you was pretty easy, don’t you think?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g2">Though, a couple times you were too indecisive and passive.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g3">Next time you should…</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_c1">Gebura, about this suppression plan you sent me, don’t you think the scale is a tad bit too grand?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g4">Alright, now move along if you’ve spat out what you needed to.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_c2">C’mon, you know a similar incident happened before~ I’m the head of the Welfare Team after all, so I just felt I should point it out.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g5">Yeah yeah, got it. How about you head on back to your department now and lap up that coffee you love so much?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_c3">And another thing, some of the E.G.O in my department seems to be malfunctioning. I’m sure you had nothing to do with it, right? Although your recent suppression was… strangely quick.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g6">…I’ll be sure to make it up to you. But if you press any further on this, those E.G.O you value so much may be pointed at your head.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_c4">Aye, aye. I’ll be on my way then~ Man, why’d I have to draw the short stick? The companions I have are either a hotheaded warmonger or some weird kids with unreadable minds.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h1">It's been a while since I came down to the Middle Layer. Long time no see, Chesed.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_c5">Oho, are you here to see Gebura? Careful what you say, you may just end up with a hole in your head. Take care~!</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h2">I-Is that true, Gebura?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g7">Oh get lost, Chesed. Hod, what brings you here?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h3">So, um, it’s about the suggestions you made involving the Abnormality Breach Training. I feel it needs some adjusting.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g8">Go on.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h4">Well, if we were to engage in a head-on assault like you suggested, our employees would suffer heavy casualties around this section. I believe if we change the training plan like so to a more defensive stance here, the casualties would be lower.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g9">…</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h5">Does it seem alright?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g10">But, then…</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h6">Hm?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g11">Aren’t we being too nice to those Abnormalities with this kind of response?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h7">Um, I’m sorry, but I don’t understand.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g12">…Forget it. Since you’re the head of the Training Team, your opinion is final, right?</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h8">I am, well, as long as you’re willing to…</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g13">Do it.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h9">Oh, thank you! See you later!</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g14">Hod!</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h10">H-Huh?! Yes!</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g15">You forgot your report.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_h11">A-Ah, I could have lost it. Phew, I thought you were going to shoot me in the head like Chesed said. Thanks again!</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g16">...</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g17">Hod’s too soft.</text>
  <text id="gebura2_intro_g18">If I were the head of the Training Team, I’d never act like her.</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c1">Gebura will be back soon.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c2">…</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c3">Manager, if it’s alright with you, could you pass my words along?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c4">Gebura, she’s…</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c5">She’s strangely obsessed with suppression, wouldn’t you say?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c6">Any casualty to employees during the suppression process… she entirely disregards it.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c7">Lady Angela’s perfectly aware, but she conveniently turns a blind eye to it.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c8">Gebura’s great at handling the Abnormalities when they breach. It’s as if she was born for this job.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c9">So I suppose a few extra dead employees is considered a reasonable tradeoff.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c10">But you see, as a manager, you should know that massacring Abnormalities is not our only priority.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_c11">Well, I dunno if Gebura will listen to you, but I’d really appreciate it if you could give it a go~</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g1">I saw Chesed leaving, what nonsense did he ramble on about this time?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g2">Be honest with me, I can see everything.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g3">….</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g4">Let me warn you.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g5">Don’t act as if you know everything.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g6">I’ve been here for a long time. I’ve seen much more than you have.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상1-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g7">Experiment subject 09-34, we’ll be running a simple test before we administer the chemicals.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Christopher1">Ah Gebura, the machine with a soul. A wonderful creation of Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g8">What does it mean to have a soul?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Christopher2">It means one may truly have worth. It’s the center of the faith our Venerable Lord A believes in. I participated in this experiment because I trust him.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g9">I don’t know if I have a soul… If I’m disassembled, will there be a soul inside me?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Christopher3">Well, it can easily be determined just by talking with you. A soul cannot be seen, but it can be felt.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Christopher4">I will be reborn as I confront my own soul... Mankind and the world will be changed soon. Trust in A, for he is our savior who shall lead us all.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 2-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Isabel1">So you’re Miss Gebura, I heard a lot about you from Christopher. They say you have a real soul. Our Venerable A really is remarkable. Don’t pay attention to those who disrespect you, they do not know your true worth.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Isabel2">Oh, meet Gilly, our daughter. She is kind and sweet, just like you.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g10">Does this child also have a soul, then?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Isabel3">Of course. A soul is something every living creature has. It’s the essence of us all, yet not known to many.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_Isabel4">This world only believes in things that can be seen with the eye. It’s a sad belief that will eventually lead everyone to destruction.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 3-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g11">Miss Angela, is that a monster?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_a1">That is what we call an Abnormality, Gebura.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g12">How is it different from monsters?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_a2">Monsters are in themselves repulsive, terrible creatures at the core and start of their existence. However, Abnormalities originate from humans.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g13">Then why does that 'Abnormality' have Mr. Christopher's watch, and why does it make sounds as if it were mimicking Mr. Christopher's voice?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_a3">You see, Gebura, that's because Abnormalities originated from 'them'. It's not like they materialize all of a sudden or come into existence from nowhere.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g14">Do Abnormalities eat humans? Is it mimicking Mr. Christopher like that because it devoured him? I don't understand.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_a4">That is a complicated thing to explain, Gebura.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_a5">What's certain is that this did not happen because of someone's vice or malice, and that the shape you perceive as a monster certainly carries the will of the man you called Christopher.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 4-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g15">Excuse me, Tiphereth. Why does the experiment log include a step where Mrs. Isabel is sent to chamber DI-01? Why should we place her anywhere near that horrific monster?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_ta1">I don't know, Gebura. You know she isn't known for explaining the purpose of every experiment to us. I think I heard that it's to rigorously determine the “loss of humanity”, but I don't get what it really means.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g16">That's definitely going to end up hurting Mrs. Isabel. I should tell Miss Angela to stop it.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_ta2">Gebura, maybe you should just keep quiet about it. I've seen other machines question her orders, and Miss Angela would reset us if we disobeyed her.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g17">…</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_ta3">Please, if you are feeling anger, I suggest that you rather embrace that anger and move on.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_ta4">Wouldn't that be better than to lose your memory and exist as a lifeless puppet, being a shame to the soul you got to bear?</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 4 끝-->
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g18">What do you think the ending to that story is?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g19">Where did Christopher's wife and his daughter Gilly disappear to?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g20">I won't ever know, either. Hard to say if it's fortunate or unfortunate, but the experiment was not under my responsibility.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g21">All I know is that old blanket Gilly had was the only thing to come out of the monster’s chamber.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g22">Most people wouldn't even talk to us, since machines weren't worth putting their minds to.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g23">But Christopher and Isabel, they told me I was worthy of something… They looked past my exterior and saw what was inside of me, something I wasn’t even aware of.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g24">Those monsters we’re obligated to call Abnormalities have killed many people since then.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g25">And yet those things never die.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g26">It’s not fair.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g27">Why do we have to treat them nicely?</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g28">Don’t pay any heed to the employees in front of you. When an Abnormality shows up, their lives will be the least of your worries.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g29">Since it’s clear that those monsters feel pain…</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g30">I’ll dish out as much pain as possible.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g31">That’s the only reason why I’m standing here.</text>
  <text id="gebura3_intro_g32">...Don’t ever patronize me again.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <!-- text id의 gebura_4_intro_r~은 용병 대장 (토끼대장) 을 의미하며 gebura_4_intro_a~는 앤젤라, gebura_4_intro_g~는 게부라를 의미합니다.-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r1">Listen, I know Lobotomy Corporation is an important client and all, but don’t you guys renew the contract too often?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 용병대장 (토끼대장)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r2">This place is so grimy, it’s like a dungeon. I always get a bad vibe.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 용병대장 (토끼대장)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a1">Please hold for a moment, Rabbit Captain. We need to explain what we’re doing here to the manager.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r3">Oh, he still doesn’t know who I am? Go on and explain it quickly, then.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a2">…..This must be the first time you’ll participate in a meeting with an outside party, manager.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a3">As was mentioned a few times prior, our company has initiated contracts with some of the other Wings for sustainable development and business opportunities.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a4">It is also my job to renew those contracts with our associate Wings when the moment arises.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a5">All that is needed from you is to be our token manager and present yourself in that role. I shall handle the rest of the formalities and procedures.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r4">Pff, “associate Wing”? What’s with that boring introduction?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a6">You may feel free to provide more detailed information at a later time in private, Myo. For now, let us start the meeting.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a7">….Speaking of, would you be so kind as to remove your helmet? At least for the duration of the meeting.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r5">You’re kidding! The helmet is the whole identity of the Rabbits!</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r6">Well, fine, it’s whatever.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r7">I just gotta brief the content of the contract from my end, right?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r8">I mean…</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r9">Ugh, I’m sick of reading this out over and over… You can just look at the contract for the whole damn thing. Do I really have to say it one more time?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a8">As I informed you prior, it’s part of the formal procedure.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a9">I myself have to specify whether or not you agree to the terms again.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r10">Still as strict as ever, aren’t you.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r11">Allow me to explain our services first.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r12">Company R will provide military support and protection from all external threats to Company L.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r13">Every branch of Lobotomy Corporation will be included under the term “Company L”, however there will be certain exceptions where a branch may not be considered under the designation.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r14">Well, I say “exceptions”, but we’re willing to let it slide unless it involves the Head or the Eye.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r15">Company L will provide the energy Company R needs to maintain its operation.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r16">This renewal process also includes a prerequisite that invokes a mutual and continual agreement between Company W and Company L.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r17">And, let’s see… Company L will provide all specialized ammunition utilized for the killing of Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r18">All Rabbit Team members will have their memories erased after the completion of their missions.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r19">There will be no questions or concerns raised about the peculiarity of the facilities or purposes of this location.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r20">And finally, I, as the captain of the Rabbit Team, will deploy my team following Company R’s guidelines and assume the role of command for operations taking place in this facility.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r21">That should be everything. Look through the written contract for the finer details.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a10">There has been no change in the agreement with Company W.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a11">Along with that, the renewal period will be 1 year, just as before.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r22">Yeah, sure, it’s one year for you, but… okay, then.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r23">On a side note, can you please do something about the teleporter to make the process a bit smoother? It feels like my body’s being taken apart piece by piece and thrown out a window.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a12">I am afraid you will need to ask Company W about that. It’s out of our control.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a13">Hm, Gebura, why do you have such an expression?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g1">Why are little bunnies being let out of their cages and dispatched here of all places?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r24">You must really not know a thing if you’re looking down on the Rabbits!</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r25">It’s already been concluded that the Rabbits are the most fit for the honorable task of slaughtering in this place.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r26">The Rhinos would most certainly smash this entire place beyond recognition.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r27">And the Reindeer, with the exception of the machines that work here, would cause irreversible damage to mister manager over there.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r28">Miss Angela made it explicitly clear to not hurt or affect the manager.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r29">We always pay special attention to our client’s requests.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g2">I’m not talking about your damn Rhinos or Deer!</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g3">I’m saying that we can handle our own problems! We don’t need any outsiders to interfere.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r30">What’s that? What can YOU do with that flimsy tin body of yours, huh?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r31">You seem much weaker than us now, can’t you see that?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r32">If you were like how you once were back in the day, then maybe it’d be a different story.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r33">But look at you now! As soon as you set foot into the Backstreets you’ll be torn limb from limb by those Sweepers.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r34">The old days when you shredded everything before you into a red mist is now lost to the past.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r35">Things have changed. You should realize that.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g4">If I wanted to, I could tear up a tiny Rabbit like you in seconds...</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a14">Please, everyone, we need to focus on the topic at hand.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a15">Gebura, our agreement with the Rabbit Team is to help us be prepared for the worst-case scenario that will be beyond our own abilities.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a16">I’m certain that you have learned this from your experiences with previous suppressions.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a17">The combat skills of the mercenaries sent to us by Company R are on par with those of the other Wings.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g5">We can handle our problems on our own perfectly fine!</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g6">I can prove it right here, right now if you want…</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a18">I have compiled the statistics. The amount of data is too vast for any person to calculate, with my exception of course.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a19">The reason I continue to contract the Rabbits is that the risk of involving outsiders pales to the potential of our worst-case scenarios. They’re worth every penny.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a20">However, the Rabbits will not intervene with general suppression.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a21">Please calm down and analyze the situation reasonably, Gebura.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g7">…….</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a22">That should be all for renewing our contract.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a23">Gebura is the one in charge of the basic suppression process.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a24">So if you need any advice or help regarding combat, just ask her.</text>
  <!-- 앤젤라 퇴장-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r36">I’m afraid I don’t have a single, itty bitty question for you. We Rabbits have our own way of handling things.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g8">...Nor do I have anything left to say to you filthy animals.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g9">You’ve done your business, how about you just bunnyhop away now?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r37">Sheesh, you’re being so harsh to a fellow native of the Backstreets.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r38">You wouldn’t happen to be mad at me because I made fun of you earlier, are you?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g10">Don’t act like you know me. I’m not in the mood for your stupid games, so just shut up.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r39">Aha! I get it now.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r40">You’re mad because you feel we interrupt your fight, aren't you?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g11">Yeah, I don’t need any help from the likes of you.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r41">Well, it’s not like we’re here for a greater cause or some ulterior motive.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r42">We just drop by quickly when we’re called, and vanish without a trace just the same when it’s time.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r43">I thought you were just like me, finding joy in the slaughter.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r44">But as it turns out, you’re just crazy.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r45">A complete wacko.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g12">…….</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r46">We are the Rabbits who hop around following orders to find fresh patches of grass, but you’re different.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r47">You used to know who you were supposed to fight, who your enemy was.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r48">You wouldn’t believe how shocked I was to find you. I never expected to see the fabled hero like… well, this. And in a drab basement too.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r49">The hero I remember was someone who wasn’t afraid of shedding blood to protect others with all her might. Please don’t taint the fond memories I have of you.</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_e1">...All the Abnormalities have broken out, everyone here is done for…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g13">….Dead? All of them?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_e2">Probably, there won’t be any survivors left…</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_e3">Abnormalities aren’t something we can handle on our own...</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_e4">You’re in danger too, ma’am… You’d best escape now…</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상 2)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_Christopher1">Gebura, I’m going to take part in an experiment pretty soon.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 크리스토퍼-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_Christopher2">We’ll probably see each other again, but just in case, I want to say one thing…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 크리스토퍼-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_Christopher3">Please take good care of Isabel and my little Gilly while I’m gone.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 크리스토퍼-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상 3)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a25">Are Abnormalities able to feel human emotion when confronted with a person of close relation?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a26">What choice would they make when faced with such a situation?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a27">The experiments… seem to have yielded the expected results.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_e5">Excuse me, Lady Angela, what should I do with these? There’s a blanket and a few feeding bottles left.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a28">I have gotten all the results I need from this experiment.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_a29">The owners are no more, so you can simply discard them.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r50">Hey….</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 용병 대장 (토끼 대장)-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (현재)-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r51">Hey, hey! Did you just shut down or what?</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r52">I really should be going.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r53">Whelp, I don’t think next we meet will be on such calm waters.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_r54">The Rabbits will leave now.</text>
  <!-- 용병 대장 퇴장-->
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g14">…..</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g15">I’m definitely not the hero.</text>
  <text id="gebura4_intro_g16">Never have been, and never will be…</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g1">You all might have noticed, but we’ve never had this kind of situation before.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g2">Those monsters were supposed to be slumbering away, but now they woke up all of a sudden.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g3">There’s no need to focus on what caused this.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g4">All that matters is that we solve the problem at hand.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g5">Let me add a few words before we jump into battle today.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g6">I don’t need cowards in my department.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g7">You should not let complacency waver your mind when you confront the monsters.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g8">You must arm yourselves with anger and pure anger alone to crush those monstrous bastards.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g9">If you object to any of this, I suggest you transfer departments immediately.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g0">Don’t expect me to bat an eye even if you get torn apart right in front of my eyes; charging at the monsters standing in my way is my only concern.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g10">I won’t squeeze out a tear or mourn over you perishing without even your name being left behind.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g11">If you want your body and mind to stay comfortable, I’ll kindly drag your ass over to the pathetic Welfare Team so you can chicken scratch your dishonorable name on the waiting list for department transfers.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g12">There’s good reason why my department has far fewer employees than any other. However, I want you to keep in mind that this also means only the best have gathered here.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g13">Meeting over. We’ll talk more when the situation has been sorted out.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_tb1">(Ksssht)</text>
  <!-- 무전기 속 티페리트 b-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_tb2">Miss Gebura, I think your mainframe has sustained too much damage.</text>
  <!-- 무전기 속 티페리트 b-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_tb3">Maybe we should suspend the suppression operation for now?</text>
  <!-- 무전기 속 티페리트 b-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_tb4">Tiphereth is investigating the cause of this situation right now, so we should be able to figure it out pretty soon.</text>
  <!-- 무전기 속 티페리트 b-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g14">I don’t need a break… I can still fight.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_tb5">But in your condition…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g15">Shut up! I said I can still fight!</text>
  <!-- 비나 등장-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b1">31 E.G.O damaged, 17 employees dead and counting.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b2">And your body needs five or six parts replaced and repaired…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b3">It’s not thrilling to look after a machine who behaves like a child in a temper tantrum.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b4">However, the Sephirot of the Middle Layer apparently could not keep you on a leash, so here I am.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g16">…….. You..</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b5">Oh, poor little thing, look at yourself.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b6">There was a time when I had a pinch of admiration for that fire in your eyes…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b7">But now even that is smothered with ire and madness.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b8">It is such a shame that the both of us are locked up in this dungeon.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b9">However, I did not bend over or break my back at the very least.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b10">I imagine we will no longer have to face off with our lives at stake and be at each other’s throats like the past, but…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b11">I will say this for you, pitiful thing.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b12">Stare directly into the object of your anger.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b13">The edge of a blade that has lost its way will be unfathomably blunt, for there will be nothing but the void to slash, no matter how much the blade is sharpened.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b14">I hope you don’t think I get some kind of satisfaction out of this, seeing my once earnest rival now looking as pathetic as a dog. I have decency, you know.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g17">Cutting, slashing, throttling, trampling, destroying...</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g18">Sometimes I remember the faces of those who showed me true kindness.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g19">If I could just get the smallest taste of revenge upon those monsters who stole their smiles, their happiness, their future…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g20">My sword and spear would never stop their flurry.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g21">I see people dying in my blurred vision.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g22">They’re always torn apart by monsters.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g23">Those dying faces differ from time to time.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g24">Sometimes they’re strangers, sometimes ones I dearly miss, and sometimes… I see Christopher or Miss Isabel.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g25">Whoever they were, I’m filled with agony for them.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g26">Looking at my paralyzed leg and my severed arm, I scream and curse my weak body in a fit of rage.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g27">Then I black out.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g28">I’m so sick of this darkness…</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상2)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_a1">It is impossible to fight with such low manpower. I cannot approve your proposal.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g29">...Please reconsider…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_a2">Why should I approve an operation that will so clearly end in failure?</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g30">If manpower is the issue, I can make up for it. If they’re too weak, I’ll make up for that too.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_a3">……..</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g31">There’s nothing in the rules against a Sephirah utilizing E.G.O too.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_a4">If you so wish, then I won’t stop you.</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상3)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g32">A familiar grip, the right weight, and practiced form.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g33">This feeling is so distinct that it pulls me right back onto the right path, away from straying to wander, just like a road sign.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g34">I completely lose track of time when I wield my weapons.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g35">It was kinda funny to see Tiphereth and Chesed with bewildered faces when they witnessed me return from battle covered in blood.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g36">No matter how hard I stab and break those monsters, they will recover sooner or later.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g37">Some of them wail and others scream.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g38">In battle, I also fracture and break some of my components, but those are soon replaced and repaired.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g39">What a perfect little hell, just for me.</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상4)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b15">Missing your arm?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b16">Here it is.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b17">Think of it as a respectful gesture to a fellow warrior, to leave you with one of your arms intact.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b18">I doubt she expected this. The tragedy she would bring here, caused by the oh-so-great ideology of hers.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b19">I don’t know if it will ease your pain, but this happens quite often, more often than you may think.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b20">This is no less common than, say, a little seedling getting trampled to death.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b21">I must admit that you’re quite the tough sprout, however.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b22">You even managed to thwart my plans a little.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b23">I never expected you would kill two Claws, stop all the monsters…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b24">And finally come to face me and give me a fair fight.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b25">By the way, about those monsters.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b26">I cannot deny that they’re astonishing things.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b27">Even after plowing through a hallway of your friends, they never softened nor tired.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b28">……It seems you aren’t much different from them, now that I ponder on it.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b29">Alright then.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_b30">If you can still manage to hold a weapon and stand up with your own two feet, then come. Come at me.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (현재, 관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g40">I will not be broken.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g41">…...…...</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g42">If I can’t get rid of these damn monsters…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g43">I’ll destroy the whole company myself instead.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_g44">Then finally my aimless wrath can crumble with it and rest beneath the earth forever...</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (A 독백)-->
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A1">Among the many Fixers of the Backstreets, she was one of the few who could go toe to toe with the Head and the Claw.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A2">She was called the “Red Mist” among the Backstreet’s denizens.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A3">That was a name she earned protecting us from all kinds of threats and maneuvers of the outside.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A4">Michelle’s betrayal led the Eye to the den we hid in, then the Head mercilessly threw their Claws at us.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A5">Instead of dealing with the Red Mist directly, the ever cunning Head unleashed the unstable Abnormalities to slaughter us.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A6">The Abnormalities were out of control, tearing apart our comrades who screamed in agony.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A7">All the while, the Claws sniffed out their prey and snatched it…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A8">The whole situation was beyond what she could handle by herself, but she gave it everything she had to protect us.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A9">She lost an eye, one of her arms was severed, and she had numerous, deep scars all over her body she could no longer heal from.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A10">Yet she didn’t give up…</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A11">And eventually, her efforts saved B and I from death.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_selection1">Collect her corpse.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_selection2">Collect her corpse.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_selection3">Collect her corpse.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A12">The cadaver demonstrated the horrendous, unbearable situation she went through.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A13">After a long time had passed, her eyes opened again.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A14">However, her anger that had lost its focus dragged her down, deep to the bottom.</text>
  <text id="gebura5_intro_A15">We had to reboot her many, many times.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <!-- 장면 : 과거-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g1">Why are you looking at me like that? You look like a thief just turned up on your doorstep.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca1">I honestly didn’t expect to see you here.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca2">Or, well, to be exact, I knew you would come here eventually, but I didn’t expect it would be this soon.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca3">You had such a sour expression when we talked, but you actually liked me, didn’t you?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g2">What the hell…</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca4">You know, I don’t have any true contact with the lives of the people from the Backstreets, nor the pain they go through.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca5">Perhaps I have been living a more affluent, yet cowardly life compared to them.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca6">From that I’ve always felt so ashamed of everything, even to be graced by a small ray of sunshine.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g3">…….It wasn’t always all that rough.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca7"> ….I understand that it must have been a hard decision to come here, so thank you.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca8">Sooner or later, we will have to deal with unexpected hardships here.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca9">There are just too many problems to try and solve in peaceful ways.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca10">The real reason I chose to speak to you out of all the other Syndicates or Fixers that day was actually because of something rather trivial.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g4">……What was it?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca11">If we’re being honest…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g5">Honest…?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca12">I thought I could barter with you for cheaper prices...</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g6">……Looks like it was a mistake to come here. I’ll be going now.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca13">Please, hear me out.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca14">I saw you pay for the funeral expenses of an old lady whom you didn’t even know.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca15">I truly admired your kindness, and I even looked forward to seeing it myself.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g7">Corpses can cause an entire alleyway to be infested with vermin if they aren’t buried properly.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g8">Besides, I just wanted to repay her for treating me to meals a couple of times.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g9">Understand? I’ve never been close to being a kind person my entire life.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca16">…..…..</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g10">Why do you keep smiling, dammit?!</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca17">Just happy to be great at discerning the best of the best.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <!-- A 독백-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_A1">Carmen could back up what she said. She truly did have a sharp eye for people.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_A2">The tale of how she built her reputation could fill a chronicle of history books and then some.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_A3">The only problem was that Carmen was too wrapped up with taking care of others. She never had a moment to take good care of herself.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_A4">We were on such a delightful upturn back then, it’s almost cruel to bring those memories back up.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_A5">We were flying towards a limitless world that never seemed to end.</text>
  <!-- A 독백끝-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g11">By the way, who’s the guy glaring at me?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca18">Oh, that’s A. He just always has a serious look on his face.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca19">…….</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca20">I beg of you, please protect the people here.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_ca21">I know I can trust you with this.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (현재, 관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g12">From the past to the present, Abnormalities have wandered the facility, killing numerous people.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g13">Despite my reputation, there were too many things that I just couldn’t save.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g14">When I think about it, my entire life was far from one of justice.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g15">You probably wouldn’t know much about the Backstreets seeing as you stayed in the Nest your whole life.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g16">Those streets were a place where there was no need for justice, morality, or any other pedestals like those.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g17">If you have never been there before, you won’t understand.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g18">How agonizing and miserable the stories of people who live there are.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g19">How they are robbed of the chance to live a legitimate life. How unfair and unjust life is there.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g20">All I learned there was how to survive this miserable existence.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g21">But Carmen told me she wouldn’t give up on anyone, even people like us.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g22">She also told us that the weak who had willing spirits could someday possess enough power to cut off the Head.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g23">It was such an absurd and ridiculous thing to say. Why couldn’t I just keep on with how my life was before?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g24">........</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g25">I’m not smart enough for all those complicated calculations.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g26">I can’t even write a logical or coherent report.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g27">The only thing I was able to do was draw my sword against those who opposed us.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g28">All my life I only used my skills for my own survival.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g29">But that day… I had never felt more proud to be able to protect others.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g30">However, I wasn’t able to protect anybody in the end. That cut me deeply.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g31">I was filled with anger, and lost my mind for it.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_selection1">Ultimately, you did manage to protect someone.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="gebura6_selection2">You saved B and myself.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g32">True.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g33">You and that other person survived thanks to me…</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g34">I thought I had lost Carmen’s will forever.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g35">But after all’s said and done, I had to have carried that will all the way here somehow, right?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g36">I feel like I can catch a bit of breath now.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g37">When we first reawakened in metal, we could feel the exact moment our final breath stopped, lodged into us like glass shards.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g38">Stupidly, I woke up with only rage left in my heart for the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g39">You miss her, right?</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g40">I do too.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g41">I don’t think she’ll ever come back.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g42">We’ll never get to see her shameless smile ever again. The one that made even people like me follow her.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g43">Or the light that radiated from her, flowing so much that one couldn’t hold all of it with both hands.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g44">But her will and promise will always remain the same, even after an eternity has passed.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g45">It will be a place where she can live on, even after death.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g46">If you happen to remember it, please tell me.</text>
  <text id="gebura6_intro_g47">Tell me the gift she left behind for us.</text>
</localize>