<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Index_1</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Index">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">We are simply obeying our Prescript.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">As the Prescript orders…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Life and death all follow the plan of the Prescript. I have no fear.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">Close our eyes… We shall not see what we needn’t see…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_4">I can sense what is ahead of me, even without the aid of vision.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_5">I simply follow the predetermined path. The Prescript shall guide me.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_6">You are not ones to argue about the morals of our work.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_7">My own will is erroneous. Only the Prescript can lead me to the right path.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_8">May the Prescript lead my soul…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">The Prescript always guides us to the righteous path.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">I simply carried out what I was obligated to do. I hold no malice.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_2">The Prescript has been carried out, let us return now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_3">It has been done… We completed it in whole.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_4">Those books are nothing more than extra spoils we’ve earned in the process of carrying out the Prescript. I have no desire for more.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">I am… not sure why it has led me to this ending…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">This must be another dispensation of the Prescript… …I accept it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_2">Such is my fate. I have no objections…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_3">I should not be dissatisfied with my predetermined fate.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_4">The Prescript… was carried out; I can die in peace.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">…It could not be helped. Fate cannot be changed once sealed.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Rest in peace. We will help handle the rest.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Let your eyes rest, and go along the road determined by the Prescript…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">May the Prescript be with you in death…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">It is an honor to meet your death following the Prescript.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">It was by the will of the Prescript. Please understand.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">I do not engage in unneeded conflict.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">This has not ended yet.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_3">…I have no problems so far.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_4">A shame that you could not join us in the path led by the Prescript.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>