<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Zwei Association</GroupName>
  <Character ID="San">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">I don’t want to lose my loved ones again.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I steeled my resolve this time, I will secure the books of Mars and Lulu at all costs…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">I just have to do this the usual way…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">About Mars and Lulu… I don’t wanna blame you guys for their death.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">You carried out your responsibilities, and I fulfilled mine.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Lulu, Mars… And Julia, who trusted me and followed me here… I’m sorry.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Let’s be careful. I could get killed as well.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">…Please give me a minute to mourn them, at least.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">The situation seems grave, I’m not sure if there’s any hope for us.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">I just found the right timing to advance, that’s all.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">I suppose… this is no time to be saying sorry.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">I should put away personal sentiments in moments like this.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">Mars and Lulu… Are you the one who killed them?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">…Fair point. You simply do your job, and I carry out my own.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">Julia… What will I have left now…?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Julia">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">I’ll act with composure.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I hope that nothing bad happens to us… I hope that all of us can leave this place safely.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">This is a fight I can’t avoid, so I wanna win for the sake of everyone.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">I’m all ready for this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_4">We do what we can… with maximum effort.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">We did it… We’ve actually won, right? Now we can go back safe and sound.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Yeah, let’s tell Isadora all about this adventure we just had.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">San… I’m sorry. I couldn’t help you much.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">My legs are shaking… Are we at our limits?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">I gotta pull myself together… for the sake of my late colleague.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">…It won’t hurt to be sad just for a bit, maybe.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">It’s just something that always happens. I shouldn’t get too sad about it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">I can do it if I try!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">This is sad, but I guess there’s no choice…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">San!!! No… Please don’t die on me like this…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Walter">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">We’re nothing like the ones that came here before us. It won’t be as easy.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Ensure that you never put down your own shields. And ensure that you never let others put your shields down.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">We are not fighting as a joke.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">This is what happens when a measly Urban Legend dares to challenge the Zwei Association: an obvious defeat.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">This was the obvious outcome. I will make good use of the books you gave us.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Perhaps I underestimated my opponents…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">I was certain that I would succeed…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">This is a common occurence.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">How unfortunate. But someone’s got to live.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">What a waste of time. You shouldn’t have been a hindrance.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">This is how you do it; take out your opponents one by one.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">That wasn’t difficult at all to handle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">You’re a disorderly group of weaklings, aren’t you?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Isadora">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">…You must be one of the clique that took San and Julia.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">They don’t really look tough, but they did annihilate the previous group…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">I’m not willing to forgive you at all.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">We’ve won… San, Julia, I avenged you.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">…I’m partially responsible for your deaths, so let’s say that we evened up the score with this.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Dammit… I’m still not done with my revenge…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">Please, just give me just another chance…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">I should do my job, whether anyone else dies here or not.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">…I’m still not fully accustomed to this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">We have a man down! We need… assistance.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Director, I’ve dealt with a hostile on my end.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Think of this as the rightful retribution for all the killing you’ve done.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">You should’ve blocked the attacks better.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>