<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Librarian</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Librarian">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Alright~ This shouldn’t be a problem! Ready, everyone?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I’m a lot tougher than you expect. Think you can beat me?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">None of my colleagues are reliable… Sigh… I only have myself to trust.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">I won’t go easy on you just because you’re our guests. Please give me a good fight!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_4">I have nothing to be afraid of! They’re humans just like us, anyway.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_5">Think you can really dodge my attacks? Huhu…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_6">Cheer up, everyone! We can do this. Oh, yes we can!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_7">I bet you won’t stand a chance against me! Why don’t you come back when you get fit?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_8">Wahaha! If anyone’s scared, just tell me. I’ll block all the attacks coming your way!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_9">First, I swing like this… And the next was this, right? Alright, let’s do it the way I practiced!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_10">Let’s not waste any more time and deal with this quickly.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_11">I feel safe thanks to my friends fighting by my side.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_12">Hey! Yeah, you there! I’m about to assault you, so I wanted to make sure you’re ready for it~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_13">One, two… Three. I’m settled down now. I’m ready!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_14">You just muttered about how weak we look, didn’t you?!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_15">Stay still over there~ I’m on my way to give you a good smack!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_16">Hold your position, everyone! If our formation is broken, we’re done for, got it?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_17">I won’t let you through easily.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_18">I hope I don’t have a tumble while running… Gotta start with the right foot first so I don’t fall, right…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_19">They don’t really look that threatening? Those guys seem pretty similar to me…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_20">I’m so scared… I wanna hide behind a bookshelf or something.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_21">If they get the impression that I’m a coward, I might be their first target…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_22">Th-they…look awfully strong, c-can I really defeat them…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_23">Can’t make any mistakes. If I’m not careful, I might die here.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_24">Let’s warm up~ Stretch my wrists~ And ankles too~ Till they’re relaxed!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_25">…I’m gonna throw books at you if you scare me… So please don’t come at me…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_26">You know this fight is not a joke, do you?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_27">I’m pumped up! I feel like I could beat them all~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_28">It’s gonna hurt if I hit you, y’know? It’ll definitely hurt. I’m saying, don’t come any closer!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_29">Everyone is doing their best, so I’m sure we’ll win!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_30">How’s this? Do I look cool when I pose like this?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_31">How about a chant of support to pump ourselves up before we go in?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_32">Everyone alright? If you have any trouble, don’t hesitate to tell us!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_33">I won’t let any of you proceed further than this!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_34">I’ll go Pshhhu, Puh-pow~ And boom! …On you, so have fun?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_35">Whoever our foes may be, just leave ‘em to me! I’ll handle ‘em all.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_36">I-it’s fine… We shouldn’t have any trouble dealing with those enemies…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_37">An opponent with such stats… I believe we can defeat them fairly!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_38">Alrighty~ Is it time to show off my skills?!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_39">You got some nerve to pick a fight with me!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_40">It’s not too late, I’ll give you one chance to beg for mercy and run away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_41">My heart is pumping like crazy, yet it doesn’t feel too bad.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_42">Behold my utterly and completely flawless strategies!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_43">Think we’ll just let you take the books here as you want?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_44">C’mon, give me a bit more time to come up with a cool catchphrase~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_45">I wanna wrap this up quickly and get some rest… So let’s get on with it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_46">Let’s sweep ‘em all in a big swipe, like swoosh~!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_47">I suppose this battle is inevitable as per usual.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_48">It’s gonna be real embarrassing to be taken down by the likes of them.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_49">Let’s do this as we always have.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_50">I hate annoyances, so let’s get this business done.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_51">Don’t get ahead of yourselves. Careless actions will result in death.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_52">Just be careful not to trip over your own feet.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_53">Those guests can’t be any worse than the literal monsters we used to deal with, right?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_54">My body doesn’t feel quite as strong as before… Not a fan of this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_55">This is the one kind of work we can handle in the most masterful way, yup.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_56">I’m so upset. I would’ve swept them away like it was nothing back in the day… This is so frustrating~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_57">It’ll take some time to get used to this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_58">Our equipment was nicer back then, to be fair. They were some ridiculous stuff…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_59">I gotta be careful not to get cocky. I’m not as strong as I used to be.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_60">This seems pretty doable, doesn’t it? At least we can keep eye contact with them without getting appalled.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_61">I’m starting to feel tired… I’ve come too far without a break.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_62">This atmosphere is pretty decent, isn’t it? There are no intimidating warning noises.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_63">With the things I used to wield like they were part of my body being gone… I’m kinda stuck.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_64">I’ve mastered the art of spotting a target’s weakness by now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_65">I thought I barely managed to survive, but I ended up in another crisis…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_66">Maybe I’m too used to the equipment I wore in the past… My own body feels alien.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Huuu-cha! However the battle went… We won in the end.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Let’s retrieve the books and go back now! I wanna get done with sorting ‘em and take my fill of rest.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_2">What? Was that it? Those guests were a lot weaker than I thought!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_3">That was a trifling fight. Makin’ our job easier’s always welcome, though.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_4">If I gather more information, will I get stronger too? Guess I’ll have to keep trying…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_5">We still have work to do, remember? Giddy up now!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_6">Man… I have tons of stuff to clean up! This is too tiring… Gosh~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_7">Gotta take care of my responsibilities to the end, no?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_8">Let’s get cleanup over with and have a nice break!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_9">We should…sort the books first, but… Aren’t you guys curious about what these books say…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_10">I wonder what all’s written in a person’s book… Will it even have their favorite food in there…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_11">Huh, that’s all the challenge they had to offer?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_12">I’m not sure if there’s any important info in these books…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_13">It’s all thanks to our great efforts that we could get this good result.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_14">I’m not very happy about killing others, but… it’s what I have to do.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_15">I suppose it’ll be easier on my mind to think of this as a small but worthwhile step toward filling out the bookcases?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_16">It’s always delightful to savor the joy of victory.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_17">I’ll try harder next time so we can all win once more!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_18">Phew… That was too close… My heart almost stopped!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_19">Now now! Attention, everyone!! Are you all alright?! Anyone suffering from injuries?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_20">Hnngh… Hah… Today’s battle was pretty easy…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_21">Why don’t we sit around and read some books together when we get back, friends?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_22">It’s a hassle to clean up the mess. …Maybe no one’d notice if I sneak off…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_23">It was frankly embarrassing to have such inept people as you for our guests.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_24">A part of me is wishing for a stronger opponent to come and give us a challenge as equals next time.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_25">I get that this is part of our work, but… I can’t help but feel a teensy bit bad about it, you know?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_26">You should’ve retreated earlier or done something about it. Not that we would’ve let you get away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_27">You should have been smarter with your moves.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_28">Every action of theirs was a display of immaturity.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_29">I guess I just have to keep it up like now~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_30">Yeah, let’s keep pushing on like this in the future~!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_31">I’ll have to learn more about combat so that I can better prepare myself…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_32">Thank goodness, I lived through this…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_33">I don’t feel any guilt from this. All I did is receive the guests with all my heart.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_34">I’m glad that we managed to win this fight.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_35">I’m sorry… It was what I had to do. Please forgive me…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_36">The battle is over, so let’s check how many of us are still present.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_37">Aw, I thought they were strong; I’m a little let down.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_38">That was one heck of a battle!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_39">And a thank you to our enemies who fought us in this battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_40">Thanks, everyone. I’m not sure I helped at all, though…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_41">I’d be glad to know that I was even just a bit helpful.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_42">Don’t get too hung up about the results, what matters the most is that you tried, isn’t it?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_43">Welp, if any of us made any mistakes, we can fix them later! Good work, y’all~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_44">Sigh… I don’t want to make any more unnecessary movements for now. I squeezed out all my energy…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_45">See! You can just leave it to me. I can handle anyone for ya.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_46">Huhu, wouldn’t you say that I’m quite reliable?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_47">It’s over, right…? I’m heading back inside now…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_48">Gosh, my shoulders are aching! Can anyone give me a good massage?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_49">I feel totally drained now that the tension’s settled down…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">I don’t wanna die… I don’t wanna die in a place like this!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">Please, save my life…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_2">Right, gods were assholes that would always ignore desperate prayers…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_3">Yeah, I was never good at anything, after all…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_4">I tried my hardest, I really did! I was terrified of dying, so I tried…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_5">At least I didn’t impede others, so I’m glad.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_6">I hope everyone can get over my death and fight to the end.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_7">…Gah, this sucks. All kinds of nostalgic memories are flashing before my eyes.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_8">This is how I really die, huh… I don’t wanna move.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_9">I shouldn’t have stepped forward and bragged that I could deal with them… Why did I bother acting heroic when I’m so petty…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_10">I wish I was born as a more coolheaded person.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_11">Those people came here out of their own free will… What about us? I didn’t sign up to die like this!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_12">I’m blacking out… My body won’t move. Sorry, friends.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_13">No… No! This can’t be!!! Help me… It’s all my fault… Please spare me…!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_14">I couldn’t be of any help in the end… I’m a disgrace.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_15">Please don’t mind me. I want the rest to stay focused on the battle…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_16">So I wasn’t quite up for this as I expected…? How shameful…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_17">I dug my own grave like a fool.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_18">I couldn’t do much…because I was just too weak… I’m sorry.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_19">Not yet… I can still fight…! I won’t give up here!!! Please, give me a second chance…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_20">We might end up losing at this rate… I want us to win even if I die here.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_21">Don’t get too cocky just because you bested me… The others will avenge me for sure…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_22">I don’t…think I can help anymore. Sorry.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_23">Haha… This feels a bit too dangerous, doesn’t it?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_24">…What the heck. I can’t believe it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_25">I did my best because I didn’t wanna die… It was all for naught; I feel so empty.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_26">It’s.. It’s all your fault…! Damn you all… If only you actually oppressed the enemies… This wouldn’t have…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_27">I thought death would be a whole lot more scary, but… I actually feel relieved now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_28">I should’ve kept my guard up till the end…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_29">Maybe I could’ve went on a rampage or two before dying.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_30">I’m not too upset about it. I’ve always been preparing for this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_31">Maybe it’s better this way. I can finally rest now, free from any more of this suffering…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_32">…Well, I’m sure they’ll do fine without me. I’m counting on you.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_33">Don’t worry about me, take care of yourselves.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_34">Sigh… It had to go like this in the end.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Why… Why did it have to go this way. Why do we all have to die!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Sorry. This wouldn’t have happened to you had I been more courageous and fought them harder…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Don’t blame me. I was scared too… You get it, right…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">They jumped forward on their own. I—I never asked them to protect me.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">They had it coming. I told them countless times not to wield their weapon so carelessly.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_5">We don’t even leave a corpse and just turn into books when we die? No… Help us…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_6">I’m scared, I’m afraid… My legs are frozen… I don’t wanna die like they did…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_7">I’ll avenge you. I swear I’ll beat them all to snuff for you… So rest easy now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_8">Someone, please end this hell… The person next to me just turned into a book…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_9">……A moment of silence for the fallen.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_10">No. No. No way! Without you, we have a higher likelihood to lose!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_11">We’re not on the losing side, are we? Please tell me we aren’t…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_12">They wanted so much to survive, and now they’re gone. That leaves a bitter taste…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_13">My, one guy got cornered, and then~ off they went. What a pity.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_14">I’m the most important person here, so I just have to focus on keeping myself alive…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_15">Thank goodness it wasn’t me… I’m fine as long as I’m not the victim. I don’t wanna end up like that.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_16">You’ve done your job well. I’m sorry I wasn’t competent enough.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_17">Whoever dies here, don’t pay them any attention… Just focus on the battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_18">I’ve already become too numb to seeing people die.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_19">I won’t forgive them… I’ll kill everyone responsible for this!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_20">Told you not to be so foolhardy with your moves.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_21">They simply held up their responsibilities.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_22">It’s alright. It’s not because you were weak or anything. So please rest in peace.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_23">I don’t want to lose you all so suddenly! Wake up… Let’s start over again, please?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_24">That one was too much of a coward. I’d say death was a better fate for them than breaking down from even greater anxiety.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_25">You should’ve at least used your brain to make up for your lack of strength.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_26">I told you it was too reckless! Why, why did you have to charge in like that?!?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_27">It breaks my heart to see my beloved friends die out like that…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_28">Why can’t I do anything for them!!! I’m not being helpful, not like this…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_29">I’ve decided not to care anymore. We have to get used to this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_30">The fact that I’m back in yet another warzone finally starts to sink in…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_31">I’m being reminded of horrible memories.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_32">There’s no use mourning over the death of coworkers in a situation like this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_33">I should stay strong for the sake of the other colleagues.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_34">It’s just the same shit for every different day. We’ve gone through this plenty of times, no?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_35">Those of us who are still alive should stay sharp.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_36">Whatever happens, my well-being comes first.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_37">It’s unfortunate, but I couldn’t do anything to stop it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_38">You did well… Rest in peace.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_39">You were too reckless. …Still, it sucks to see my long-time colleague die.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">That was a smooth kill. I’m feeling fine today.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">We’d be the winners with the way things are going, no?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">You’re my enemy, so there’s no reason for me to let you off. Good night, sweet fellow.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_3">Haha! I knew I could make it. Any other pals brave enough to take me on?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_4">…I didn’t mean to hit you so hard… I didn’t want this fight, either…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_5">I took them out without hurting myself too bad… I can make it if I try, huh?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_6">I wonder what this guy’s book says… Aren’t you curious?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_7">No time to relish this dub. I’m moving onto the next target immediately!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_8">Just give me three seconds. Wow! I won! Woohoo~! …That’s enough. Back to battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_9">Huh, maybe this work suits me better than I thought…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_10">You were out of luck, dear guest. I appreciate your efforts, regardless.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_11">Personally, I would rather have accepted my fate and died a dignified death than throw an immature fit as a last resort.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_12">The dead can’t speak, but the living can and should~ I won, baby!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_13">That wasn’t all that difficult…? I think I could be more active about this!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_14">Nailed it, didn’t I? I can do it if I try.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_15">N-now I see, so this is how I do it! That was doable, even for me.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_16">Yahoo~ Did you just see how I did that? That’s a piece of cakewalk!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_17">That was quite the tricky foe, but… I managed to handle them. We mustn’t let our guards down yet, however.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_18">D-did I… get to be a big help to everyone with this…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_19">Heheh, well, that was nothing! I could kick their ass with the flick of my pinky~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_20">You shouldn’t have come here if you were going to be so amateurish.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_21">That one was all strength and no style. No complaints, though; these kinds of brutes are much easier for us to deal with.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_22">What? I think that guy rattled off something moments ago… Maybe I should’ve gave them some time to leave their dying words?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_23">You dummy! That’s what ya get for standing in my way.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_24">I’m not supposed to rejoice over killing somebody, although… This means I’m doing my job well.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_25">Did I do a good job? I’m looking pretty reliable now, don’t I~?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_26">Can’t meet the same fate as those clumsy chumps. Who’s next? Bring it on!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_27">I must conclude your story here. I shall take a moment to grieve for you, at least.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_28">Died all too quickly, like “Quack!” …I’m not impressed one bit!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_29">I’m heating up!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_30">The work… I mean, the battle seems to be progressing smoothly.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_31">No need to be sympathetic over killing someone.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_32">Things are not the same as before… But there’s still things I can do.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_33">You have a millennium of combat experience to catch up to, pal.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_34">With my old buddies, there’s nothing to be afraid of!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_35">It was your fault, don’t make excuses about it.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_36">Getting impatient? Your attacks got predictable.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_37">Guess I’m not as rusty as I thought!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_38">Your mind was even more fragile than your body. Where’s the determination to sink or swim?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_39">I’m feeling it? Seems like I’m getting back in shape~</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>