<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Stray Dogs</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Gyeong-mi">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Don’t send one at a time like cowards, and fight me all at once!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Looks like the goons we sent in advance weren’t any good. What a bother.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Yeah! Shudder with fear. I’mma full send on you!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">So the ‘books’ we could supposedly find here… It was this easy to win ‘em?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">That son of a bitch Walter was a soft stooge. How could he manage to lose against these wimps!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">This has got to be a dream… There’s no way I can lose!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">Those sons of bitches must’ve pulled some dirty trick on me…!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Why’d you have to run wild in the front and get wrecked.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Pathetic, getting pwned by a bunch of nerdy wimps.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Don’t care if one or two die.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Adjust my strength? Never tried that.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Die! Kill ‘em all and drop dead!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">I would’ve loved to smash this guy’s head to a pulp to blow off some steam.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Zulu">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Did the guys who got in first get wrecked already?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">It ain’t hard work to deal with chumps like you.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">You’d better wimp out while you can.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Go back and get some more nutrition, why don’tcha. You were just as crummy as I thought.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">We’re a bit pressed for time, but they should like the quality intel in these books.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">No… I didn’t come all the way here to die like a sack of shit…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">I gotta crush ‘em all… I don’t wanna end this!!!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Another one dies. …Doesn’t feel too good.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">I’m used to seeing lame pansies get themselves killed by now, but…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Shoulda just stayed behind if you were gonna be so mediocre.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Shouldn’t have stood in my way in the first place.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">At least make this fun for me… Petty bastards.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Got no other choice. I have to kill others if I don’t wanna die myself.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Dino">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">We’re supposed to fight a bunch of little brats now? That’s discouraging…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Sigh… Those poor sods. Looks like they got wiped out helplessly.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">This could dislocate your bones if it misses the mark, so just stay still.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Didn’t even break a sweat conquering this place…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Man, I’d be too embarrassed to tell anyone that we got these books by defeating ferocious foes.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">I misjudged. Shouldn’t have underestimated those bastards…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">This ain’t fair… Not fair at all!!!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">…Fine, not everyone can survive, I guess.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Dammit, who just died? …I was hoping we won’t have to face this kinda situation.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Poor bastard… To die in a place like this.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">The bookworm is flying high across the field.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Should have backed off once you noticed you’re weaker than me.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">This guy’s so soft, it feels like I’m kicking air.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>