<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Molar Office</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Olga">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Urgh… I’m still feeling nauseous.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">It’s me friend’s request, so I’ll chin up and get this done.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">They don’t look strong enough for me to intervene, eh?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Weh? Was that really it? That simple? This is a wee bit lackluster…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">And I was excited to tell Myo about my excellent adventure ‘ere, this won’t do…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">…Guess I went in too deep without a good backup plan. That was right dumb of me.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">If I die ‘ere, what’ll become of Rain and Mika…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH" />
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Oi, you just saw me slay that one with style, right?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">My bad, my bad~ Hit you a little too hard there~ You could’ve also just tried dodging that, ey?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Seems like we’re taking a huge lead, no?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">I don’t feel safe leaving that stern lass alone…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">It doesn’t feel right to leave him alone… Welp, whatever.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">Welp… With both of my partners dead, I wasn’t gonna make it too far by myself, anyway.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_3">I won’t push myself any longer. Mika, Rain, thanks for your service.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_4">…You always loved to act high and mighty and nag at me all the time, and now you leave me behind all so suddenly?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_5">What is my Office gonna do without you, what am I going to do without you!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Mika">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">It’s rather intimidating to be in unfamiliar places…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I am frankly concerned… But I believe everything will work out.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">What a mess we’ve gotten into…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">It seems we’ve accomplished the goal. Stellar work, everyone.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Let us retrieve the information relevant to us and get out of here posthaste.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Where… did I go wrong…? I don’t want to end it already…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">I can’t die already… I couldn’t even help them much yet.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH" />
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">…We’ve urgent matters to address.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">…Rest in peace.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">The operation seems to be on wheels. Let’s keep this up!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">Even if I could somehow leave this place in one piece… No one would be welcoming as those two were.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">You always cared for us so much, why couldn’t you take good care of your own life!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">…Boss? You aren’t supposed to sleep here. …Please get up.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Rain">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Sigh… Mika is quite dependable, but I just can’t trust you, Big Sis.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I guess it’s up to me and Mika to deal with all this, judging from your messy state, Big Sis…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">This is pretty big for a library. I’m seeing a lot of books here…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">It was rather challenging, but it was a good experience.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">…There’s just too many terrifying things here. Let’s leave this place quickly.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">No… This can’t be!! There’s no hope here…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">Everyone is going to die… And it looks like I’m done for as well…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH" />
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">This one is nothing more than a cakewalk.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Another one down. Try and catch up to my score, Big Sis~</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">If I was just one bit careless, I’d have been the one lying cold on the floor…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">…I only have my incompetence to blame. I’ll catch up to you two soon.…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">So I told you multiple times, Big Sis, that you’re too sloppy…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">.You acted so composed and level-headed… It’s not cool to die on us like that.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>