<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Dawn Office</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Salvador">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Don’t expect to get away scot free.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Those fellows seem to have rather frail bodies.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">An old man’s body holds as much experience as it has aged.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I pay much respect to your courage.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">It must have been a bad day for these fellows.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">Thank you for your service, Yuna. You can rest easy—our Office will be fine.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">I have no attachment to life, however… I’m simply worried about that young fellow.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">Oh dear… Philip, I believe you should save your strength and retreat.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_3">…To feel more sadness at such an old age.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_4">I suppose it was still too much…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">There’s no need for all of us to share the same fate.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">You must’ve gotten tired, seeing as your attacks became more predictable as time went by.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Victory is at hand.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">One can predict their opponent’s next play by observing their movements.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Yuna">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">They might seem like easy targets, but they’re still an Urban Plague… Let’s be careful.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">No need to overdo it, Philip. You can stay behind and support us.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Let’s strike first before the opponents start attacking.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">That ended smoothly. Philip did a pretty good job, although he got scared.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">I’ll take care of Philip and the Office for you… Rest in peace, gramps.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">I hope he can do fine by himself…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">…Watch for the right timing and run away. The situation isn’t looking good.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_3">I will fight till the end even if the tide is against us…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_4">I’ll be fine, don’t worry about us and just run.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">It’s the fault of my ineptitude.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">You weren’t too bad, but you couldn’t capitalize on your skills.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Forecasting what happens after can make or break the battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">That won’t stand a chance against me.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Philip">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">I’ll end up being a burden to others if I don’t try…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I can’t hide behind my seniors all the time.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">With my skills… I suppose I can impede them at least.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">We’ve suffered some damage as well… But I suppose it’s the results that matter the most.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_0">……What will be the point of winning now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_1">I’m sorry… I’m not strong enough. I can’t take any more of this…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="SPECIAL_EVENT_2">I’m too much of a coward to get anything done…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">No… It can’t be… This is unexpected.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">There’s no way I can hold out in a situation like this…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">I wouldn’t have come here if I had known that it would be this dangerous…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">I’m glad to be of help somehow.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Striking without hesitation is the answer in situations like this, right…?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Nothing will change if I don’t make a move.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>