<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Hook Office</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Naoki">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Let’s see, are you guys also not human? Maybe I’ll find out once I bust up every single one of you?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I’m gonna crush you all, so get ready!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Get ready. I am gonna win this for sure.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Haha, this is way too easy! We barely did anything.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">This is our chance to earn the favor of our boss. Time to earn some riches~</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">What the heck… I was too careless. Lame, lame, lame lame!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">These fucks… are strong… Dammit, I thought I could make it through this…!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">It’s not all too pleasing to see my colleague die.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">And you boasted so much about how you’re the strongest. …That’s what ya get.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">You know how lame it is to be a burden till the end, yeah?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">I wanna slash you some more, but… You’re already a mess, so I’ll hafta move on.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Whoever stands in my way is getting wrecked, that’s all.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">How does it feel to be on the receiving end of my thrilling blade?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT" />
  </Character>
  <Character ID="McCullin">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Sigh… My body’s still feeling sore. A shame I can’t fight in my best condition.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Careful there. This is gonna hurt bad if it hits you in the wrong spot.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">We’re fully prepared for this.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Well, money is one thing, but it’s just a bit too anticlimatic to turn into books right after death.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">I was expecting to have some small fun with your bodies, like tearing them apart and hanging ‘em on a hook. …That’s a bit unfortunate.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">It’s… not over yet… I can’t fall to the likes of you, I’m better than that…!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">They got me good… This can’t be happening…!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">A fitting end for a rash idiot like you.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">I’ll avenge your death.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Should have been a bit more careful.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Why’d you bother holding out if you were gonna get wrecked anyway.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">What? Come on, you can’t die so soon, I didn’t even get started with the real fun.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Weaklings, weaklings everywhere.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT" />
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Taein">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Let’s get this over with, aight? No point dragging on.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">I could easily dodge all your attacks with my hands in pockets man.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Why don’t you just hand over the goods before we mess you up real bad?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">Huh, so it was this easy to make a fortune and straighten out my life?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Don’t you ever tell anyone that you’re guardians of cool treasures or anything. I’m honestly embarrassed for you.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Can’t believe I’ve lost against these suckers… Dammit…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">They were predicting my moves…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">That’s what you get for standing around and taking all those hits to the face.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Idiot. You stood still and took it all.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Well, shoot… Guess you never really know how things will go, huh.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">I’d have crushed your head to bits if we weren’t in this weird place.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Tsk, and I got a brand new weapon, too… You’re too weak to test it on.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">C’mon, try to hold out for longer so I can actually enjoy this!!!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="SPECIAL_EVENT" />
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>