<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleDialogRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <GroupName>Liu</GroupName>
  <Character ID="Liu-Fixer">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">My eyes shall look straight ahead as we advance.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">We will not expose our back to the enemy.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">To become a dragon of the battlefield, honorable and courageous…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">No matter what you do, maintain a sound body and mind.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_4">It may not be the kind of task we usually handle, but surely it can be dealt with in the same way.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_5">Remember the protocol… Let’s not get nervous.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_6">I am not afraid. Moving out!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_7">The Liu is overpowered by none.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_8">We must be quick to go on the offensive.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_9">One’s actions should not be a detriment to all.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">It’s hardly believable that such amateurs made it to this grade…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Regardless, we’ve accomplished the given mission… Let us go back.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_2">It’s not a good idea to become overconfident in victory.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_3">I won’t take pity on the opponent.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_4">A smooth triumph. Let’s take the books we were requested to retrieve and return.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">I’d hate to drag others down…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_1">I don’t want to give in at this point…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_2">How rash… A single mistake resulted in this…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_3">Hesitation would only be a roadblock…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_4">It would seem… I’ve reached my limit.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">We can’t afford to dwell on personal feelings.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">…All we can do is move onward in silence.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">It’s still difficult to stay composed over someone’s demise.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">…The offensive must continue.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">We can’t back down now, despite the risk.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">I wish for the rest of our combat to resolve swimmingly like just now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Inviting people to a fight with such a lax mindset was your mistake.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">I won’t let a single second pass in vain or let a single foe escape my notice.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_3">In moments like this, your weapon is the one thing you can rely on.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_4">Such feeble attacks won’t get through.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Lowell">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Focus. They aren’t pushovers by any means.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">Cecil, Mei. Are you ready?</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">As long as our body and mind are sound, the results won’t betray us.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_3">Don’t be scared. Remember that the key to the enemy’s defeat is within yourselves.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I understand that you’re tired, but don’t forget to take the books.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">Victory was already in our hands when we entered, so it was inevitable that the enemy lost.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">…At least, I could do something for my own sake till the end.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">I’m sorry… Thank you for your efforts.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">Your will shall carry on… I swear to win this battle.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">…Should we pull back? No, the situation isn’t right yet…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">In difficult situations, be on the defensive.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_4">Even if everyone else dies, as long as one person stands… There’s still a chance to win.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">The battle isn’t over yet. Stay focused!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">We’re pressing on further. This isn’t over just yet…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">Even the most rigorously trained soldier has weaknesses in body and mind.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Cecil">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">Yessir! Going forth right away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">We shall not let them attack us from our back. We’ll push forward with a steadfast spirit.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">We will advance before the enemy can assume a formation!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I think the intel we got here will prove to be handy.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">I wonder if Section 1 has finished their work by now. Shall we head back?</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Perhaps I wasn’t fit… to best a Star of the City.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">Now is the time for action! Don’t be discouraged!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">We can endure this. We won’t lose…</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">With the right mindset… We can overcome situations like this.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">We will retaliate with even greater strength!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">A clean finish.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">They’re almost finished… We’ll charge further into their ranks!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">I’m not exhausted in the slightest; I feel like I’m on fire!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
  <Character ID="Mei">
    <Type ID="START_BATTLE">
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_0">I’m prepared! Moving out now.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_1">There aren’t too many foes!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="START_BATTLE_2">Know your enemy and know yourself! Then you won’t falter after a hundred fights.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="BATTLE_VICTORY">
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_0">I was just starting to get warmed up… That’s a bit of a shame!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="BATTLE_VICTORY_1">That was an easy formation to break!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="DEATH_0">Sorry, director… I could’ve toughed it out…</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH">
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_0">I won’t stop here! Giving up would be a rude thing to do to all my colleagues that have passed away.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_1">The battle is ongoing… It’s not finished yet!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_2">Can’t let them have it their way… HERE I COME!!!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="COLLEAGUE_DEATH_3">I’m not foolish enough to let such a casualty surprise me.</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
    <Type ID="KILLS_OPPONENT">
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_0">Things seem to be on a smooth track!</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_1">Is everyone alright? We should know when to advance and when to hold our position.</BattleDialog>
      <BattleDialog ID="KILLS_OPPONENT_2">It’s too late to hope for victory when the battle has already begun!</BattleDialog>
    </Type>
  </Character>
</BattleDialogRoot>