<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<root>
  <!--
  
  직원 상황별 대사
  
  AgentNewgrade_XXX_Y_Z : XXX - 상황, Y - 직원 유형, Z - 텍스트 넘버
  
  Y : 0 ~ 4 (A,R,W,B,P 순. A는 모든 유형에 적용)
  
  -->
  <!-- (/｀ω´)ﾉ 먼저 게임을 해보는 것이다 by prog. -->
  <category type="normal">
    <grade level="1">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>I can’t believe it. I’m working for one of the Wings now!</lyric>
        <lyric>I’ve finished management training, but I still don’t have the hang of it…</lyric>
        <lyric>Why is everyone telling me to be careful around the Abnormalities? They can’t be that dangerous, can they?</lyric>
        <lyric>I just hope the work here isn’t too difficult.</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t even imagine how experienced and skilled the manager must be to have his position.</lyric>
        <lyric>Now I can proudly tell people that I’ve joined a Wing.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>The easier the work is, the faster we’ll finish.</lyric>
        <lyric>Another tough day at work.</lyric>
        <lyric>I can do this!</lyric>
        <lyric>So, we need to satisfy the Abnormalities’ desires, such as hunger, with Instinct.</lyric>
        <lyric>We’ve made it this far. Let’s keep it that way.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>I heard people from the Outskirts get in here too… Do they just hire anyone?</lyric>
        <lyric>I wonder what this chip in our armbands is for?</lyric>
        <lyric>The guy I met yesterday was replaced by someone else before I even got to know him.</lyric>
        <lyric>We need to analyze the Abnormalities via Insight, and shape the environment they favor.</lyric>
        <lyric>The directive that forces us to do whatever is ordered feels too harsh for me.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>If I keep working hard here, I’ll be able to bring my family into the Nest.</lyric>
        <lyric>I know there are sinister rumors about the Wings, but I have no choice but to work here. The pay is just too good, and everyone around looks up to me.</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t believe we’re actually able to talk with the Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>Perhaps we could befriend the Abnormalities?</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>I like this facility, but the air is too heavy.</lyric>
        <lyric>Feels like I’m being watched…</lyric>
        <lyric>Repression, a work that pushes down everything that could erupt…</lyric>
        <lyric>It feels as if all the hallways and rooms in this facility are branded with fear and despair.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="2">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>The Abnormalities are more dangerous than I thought.</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t believe people can die so easily.</lyric>
        <lyric>So this is the true face of Lobotomy Corporation…</lyric>
        <lyric>I thought I’d never win against an Abnormality back then, but now, I feel like I just might be able to.</lyric>
        <lyric>Working here is better than whatever goes on in the Backstreets at night, I guess.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>All you need to do is go with the flow of the body and the mind when using a weapon.</lyric>
        <lyric>The definition of “food” is rather ambiguous for Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>Satiating Abnormalities is more than just feeding them, it turns out.</lyric>
        <lyric>We can’t always be doom and gloom. Let’s keep our heads up!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>Does this stuff happen in the other Wings as well?</lyric>
        <lyric>I thought Lobotomy Corporation was just an eco-friendly energy producer…</lyric>
        <lyric>There’s something off about this place.</lyric>
        <lyric>This is way too inefficient. Why do these dangerous things need to be managed by humans? </lyric>
        <lyric>It takes more than just knowledge to analyze the Abnormalities.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>I wish I could get the hang of it already.</lyric>
        <lyric>Not all Abnormalities are bad…</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m starting to see how to handle the Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>I know they say to never get personally attached to the Abnormalities, but…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>The equipment here is fascinating… I feel a rush of nostalgia about them.</lyric>
        <lyric>I wonder how everyone else feels about working in this place.</lyric>
        <lyric>Something in my heart wavers every time I do Repression work.</lyric>
        <lyric>It feels as if there’s a direction to everything that happens here, like an end purpose.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="3">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Those newbies have no idea what they’ll face here.</lyric>
        <lyric>I just have to endure this. Employees get paid vacation after working two months.</lyric>
        <lyric>I heard rumors about monsters that roam the Backstreets at night. They sound awfully like Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>If I die, I’ll just be replaced by someone else…</lyric>
        <lyric>As bitter as it is, I’m getting accustomed to life here.</lyric>
        <lyric>At the very least, working here is better than dying out in the Backstreets.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>I’m now able to eat after seeing a corpse the same day.</lyric>
        <lyric>I hate myself for being so used to witnessing death. </lyric>
        <lyric>The type of “food” differs between Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>The stench of blood still lingers in my nostrils. I can’t seem to wash it away with water.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>Is this all really worth it? Doing work like this, in a place like this?</lyric>
        <lyric>I saw what happens when people go insane for real.</lyric>
        <lyric>What if Abnormalities are some kind of gods?</lyric>
        <lyric>The more I know about the Abnormalities from Insight work, the less I realize I understand.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>I’m starting to hate those things. They ruthlessly murder us, but we have to take care of them. How unfair is that?</lyric>
        <lyric>Do not become personally attached to an Abnormality, even if you’re doing Attachment work.</lyric>
        <lyric>The Abnormalities are always so picky about their games.</lyric>
        <lyric>Friends are meaningless here, but at the same time, you can’t get through the day without your comrades beside you.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>Sometimes I feel like I’ve awakened from a long slumber.</lyric>
        <lyric>It feels like I’m stuck in a dream whenever I face an Abnormality.</lyric>
        <lyric>We need to know what they truly are, and repress them.</lyric>
        <lyric>It feels as though the souls of the dead still linger in this place.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="4">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>I wonder how many of our rookies are gonna die today?</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m sworn to do whatever the manager tells me to.</lyric>
        <lyric>Don’t get too hard on yourself with work here.</lyric>
        <lyric>Suppose I’ll buy W Corp’s travel package when my vacation time finally rolls up.</lyric>
        <lyric>If I work just a bit harder, my family can come to the Nest.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>They’re not so different, suppressing Abnormalities and culling panicked coworkers.</lyric>
        <lyric>I hope work finishes soon.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m starting to miss the smell of blood.</lyric>
        <lyric>Eating is the only joy we can find here.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>The human mind is simply too fragile.</lyric>
        <lyric>One should not try to understand things that simply cannot be understood.</lyric>
        <lyric>We will lose all our humanity someday if we continue to work here.</lyric>
        <lyric>Some people just have to do what they’re told not to do.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>Everyone has their own way of living.</lyric>
        <lyric>Just take it easy. Don’t overthink things.</lyric>
        <lyric>Just chill out and work. Everything will resolve itself.</lyric>
        <lyric>Don’t get too nervous. We’ll handle this one step at a time.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>The essence of Repression work is connected to the subject’s meaning of existence.</lyric>
        <lyric>We are all equal in the face of death.</lyric>
        <lyric>Our souls will flow through the world even if we lose our bodies.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="5">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Everyone dies someday.</lyric>
        <lyric>Same shit, different day. We just follow orders.</lyric>
        <lyric>There’s not much meaning to be had. We work and get paid. That’s all.</lyric>
        <lyric>Don’t worry so much, even if you’re new here. You’ll get used to it all in no time.</lyric>
        <lyric>Don’t give too much thought to those who’ve died. Just accept it and move on.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>We’re nothing but flesh and blood after all.</lyric>
        <lyric>Blood gracefully flows through every mortal life.</lyric>
        <lyric>The purpose of Instinct work is merely to keep them in physical form.</lyric>
        <lyric>Life’s beautiful like a candlelight, for it is weak, yet intense.</lyric>
        <lyric>We must do what we can now, not wrap our heads around the future.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>What does it truly mean to be humane? Is it humane to seek truth and verity?</lyric>
        <lyric>We must gaze upon things beyond what our eyes can see.</lyric>
        <lyric>Everyone has their own mission, to prove their own existence.</lyric>
        <lyric>We recreate the world by witnessing the truth with the eye of wisdom.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>Humans, Abnormalities, it’s not important. What’s truly important is the resonation of existence.</lyric>
        <lyric>Protecting others is the least I can do.</lyric>
        <lyric>A relationship is a chorus that blooms from the connection, the contact between beings.</lyric>
        <lyric>Shells are just shells, we must not forget what they cover.</lyric>
        <lyric>If we could become one and share our existence, it’d be fascinating.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>Death is not the end of it all.</lyric>
        <lyric>Life is beautiful because it shines through the darkness of the night like a star.</lyric>
        <lyric>The setting of stars is truly a magnificent sight.</lyric>
        <lyric>The true nature of Repression Work is the denial of the meaning of existence.</lyric>
        <lyric>We will come again after death, following the guidance of the soul…</lyric>
        <lyric>Abnormalities have souls, just like humans do…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
  </category>
  <category type="panic">
    <grade level="1">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Please give me an order! Please give me an order! Please give me an order! Please give me an order! Please give me an order!</lyric>
        <lyric>Just let me go home, manager… I WANNA GO HOME!</lyric>
        <lyric>Manager, please do something about my situation if you’re seeing this. Please SAVE ME.</lyric>
        <lyric>AAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHH!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="2">
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>I don’t want to die all alone…</lyric>
        <lyric>Yeah, it’s all your fault! YOU’RE THE ONE WHO MESSED UP EVERYTHING!</lyric>
        <lyric>You’re the one to blame! Not me! NOT ME!!!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>It’s all my fault. It’s my responsibility…</lyric>
        <lyric>I don’t see any hope in this situation…</lyric>
        <lyric>Even if I survive, I’ll just continue to suffer because of this moment for the rest of my life…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>Help me! Please! I want to get out of here! Just open the emergency door!</lyric>
        <lyric>Manager?! Manager! Open the emergency door! PLEASE LET ME OUT!</lyric>
        <lyric>I-I’m scared. Everyone’s dead… What do I do? What do I do…?</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>Watch me, manager! I didn’t fail! I swear I didn’t fail!</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m not like all these idiots around me! LOOK AT ME! LOOK AT WHAT I DO!</lyric>
        <lyric>Why the long face? Don’t worry, just you wait! I’ll make you happy again!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="3">
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>Just end it all. This company, us, you… JUST END IT!</lyric>
        <lyric>I can do this. I- I can kill humans just like they did.</lyric>
        <lyric>YOU LEFT ME BEHIND!!!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>The hallway is all coated with blood and brain fluid… You can see it too, right? We need a mop and bucket… We have to clean it up…</lyric>
        <lyric>I saw my dead colleague yesterday. We had a nice dinner and coffee together. He seemed to be doing just fine. I might visit him soon…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>We’re all going to die. They’ll ravage our bodies and minds here in this miserable place…</lyric>
        <lyric>I DON’T WANT TO DIE. DON’T LET ME GET KILLED LIKE THEM! Don’t let me die…</lyric>
        <lyric>AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</lyric>
        <lyric>D- DON’T SEND ME IN THERE!!! DON’T KILL ME!!!!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>ManagerIJustWantToApologizeToMyDeadFriendsI’mSorryIDon’tWannaDieLikeThisIMissMomAndDadSoMuchPleaseHelp.</lyric>
        <lyric>Let me introduce you to my imaginary friends! They asked me to! They’re screaming to be let out!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="4">
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>DIE! KILL IT ALL AND DIE!</lyric>
        <lyric>The smell of blood is calling me. I yearn for blood and flesh.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’ll kill everyone. I’ll destroy everything. Nothing matters anyways.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>I can hear someone. It’s the sound of back home. I just can’t stop hearing it…</lyric>
        <lyric>There’s no hope left. My mind’s collapsing. Everything’s collapsing…</lyric>
        <lyric>We will all sink and perish, devoured by madness…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>I just can’t. I swear I tried to get used to it, BUT I JUST CAN’T.</lyric>
        <lyric>Please let me out of here. I tried, I really tried. I tried my best. But I just can’t take it anymore!</lyric>
        <lyric>Nobody wants to die like this. We don’t want to die like this. We’re not here to just die like this!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>Let us find peace from them.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m so sorry dear friends, I’ll let you out now.</lyric>
        <lyric>Come on out everyone! Step out and free us from this accursed place!</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="5">
      <lyrics rwbp="r">
        <lyric>It’ll be fun! The tearing of flesh will create a beautiful melody!</lyric>
        <lyric>Why do humans die so easily? Humans like you.</lyric>
        <lyric>It will end quickly, so relax. I’ll free you from this prison we call flesh.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="w">
        <lyric>The whispering of the moon and the sound of the stars. And the truth beyond…</lyric>
        <lyric>To the horizon of knowledge, beyond understanding…</lyric>
        <lyric>Their roar. The resonance between you and I. The incandescent wisdom…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="b">
        <lyric>I will never get out of here…</lyric>
        <lyric>We will all eventually become one in the origin.</lyric>
        <lyric>Collectively losing our sanity is the only redemption we can find here.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
      <lyrics rwbp="p">
        <lyric>We will find our redemption through the Abnormalities.</lyric>
        <lyric>Abnormalities are the true essence of humans. Let us reach them and find redemption.</lyric>
        <lyric>Let us reach the paradise beyond death, together with the Abnormalities.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
  </category>
  <category type="horror">
    <grade level="0">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Pff. It’s nothing.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’ve got this.</lyric>
        <lyric>Piece of cake.</lyric>
        <lyric>Just tickles is all.</lyric>
        <lyric>How boring.</lyric>
        <lyric>Doesn’t even phase me.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="1">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Just calm down, do what we always do.</lyric>
        <lyric>Just don’t lose your head and stick to the manual.</lyric>
        <lyric>We just have to keep on what we’ve always done before.</lyric>
        <lyric>No need to get careless now.</lyric>
        <lyric>Focus…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="2">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Hah, I’m getting nervous.</lyric>
        <lyric>Slowly, slowly…</lyric>
        <lyric>Breathe in, breathe out…</lyric>
        <lyric>Just need to stick to the manual.</lyric>
        <lyric>It’ll be fine if we focus, I think…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="3">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>There’s no room for error here.</lyric>
        <lyric>My legs are trembling…</lyric>
        <lyric>Damn, it’s scary.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m getting chills down my spine.</lyric>
        <lyric>Please, as long as nothing bad happens…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="4">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>GODDAMN IT!!!!</lyric>
        <lyric>What do we do here?</lyric>
        <lyric>Is there anything we can do in this situation?</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t move my legs…</lyric>
        <lyric>H-Help…</lyric>
        <lyric>I don’t want to die!</lyric>
        <lyric>I need to run. I have to run away…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="5">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Ah…</lyric>
        <lyric>What…</lyric>
        <lyric>What am I seeing…?</lyric>
        <lyric>I- I can’t take it…</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t understand…</lyric>
        <lyric>...................</lyric>
        <lyric>It’s all over…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="6">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>So this is God…</lyric>
        <lyric>My existence is meaningless…</lyric>
        <lyric>We are petty beings…</lyric>
        <lyric>So there is an all-mighty existence beyond the realm of us beings…</lyric>
        <lyric>Please, mercy…</lyric>
        <lyric>Grant us salvation…</lyric>
        <lyric>So I truly am nothing after all…</lyric>
        <lyric>Let us witness in awe…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
  </category>
  <category type="otherdead">
    <grade level="0">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>And another one bites the dust.</lyric>
        <lyric>Poor bastard.</lyric>
        <lyric>There’s no time to grieve for them.</lyric>
        <lyric>Happens all the time.</lyric>
        <lyric>Those who’ll die, will die.</lyric>
        <lyric>Poor weakling.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’ll pay them some respect at least.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="1">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Let us pay respect…</lyric>
        <lyric>Another employee passes away.</lyric>
        <lyric>I need to get used to all this death…</lyric>
        <lyric>We can’t let grief grip us.</lyric>
        <lyric>I wonder if there’s anyone who will cry for them.</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="2">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Damn it all, someone died.</lyric>
        <lyric>Comrade down! Comrade down!</lyric>
        <lyric>And they’re gone forever…</lyric>
        <lyric>We’ve lost one. Be careful!</lyric>
        <lyric>Let’s keep focus. I can’t die here…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="3">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>{0}...? Are you really dead?</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t believe you died like this {0}...</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t let them kill me too.</lyric>
        <lyric>Please. Please. Please…</lyric>
        <lyric>Is {0} really dead? Is it my turn next?</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="4">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>My God…</lyric>
        <lyric>I relied on them so often…</lyric>
        <lyric>What do we do…?</lyric>
        <lyric>If even {0}’s dead, then…</lyric>
        <lyric>I won’t last… Even {0}’s died now… </lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="5">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>It’s over for me…</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t believe {0} died… How...</lyric>
        <lyric>WE’RE ALL GOING TO DIE!!!!</lyric>
        <lyric>{0}’s died. The same is going to happen to me soon…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
  </category>
  <category type="otherpanic">
    <grade level="0">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Yet another turns to insanity.</lyric>
        <lyric>The heart is easily breakable.</lyric>
        <lyric>Weak minded folk have no place here.</lyric>
        <lyric>The sound of despair, I’m used to it.</lyric>
        <lyric>Even screams bring me delight now.</lyric>
        <lyric>I thought I would go crazy back then, each time I saw someone like that. But now, well… </lyric>
        <lyric>It’ll be quiet again soon enough…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="1">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>One more who’s lost heart.</lyric>
        <lyric>I won’t end up like him. I can’t.</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m starting to get used to seeing the faces of insanity.</lyric>
        <lyric>The screams of the mad will always disturb me.</lyric>
        <lyric>Will I lose my mind like them someday?</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="2">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>We’ve got someone panicking!</lyric>
        <lyric>Someone’s just hit the maximum mental corruption level!</lyric>
        <lyric>I can’t lose my mind here.</lyric>
        <lyric>I gotta stay focused here… I can’t lose my mind.</lyric>
        <lyric>It’s so painful to watch. It’ll drive me insane…</lyric>
        <lyric>I don’t want to hear those screams of pain anymore…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="3">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Even the seniors can go insane just the same...</lyric>
        <lyric>I don’t know if I can endure all the madness in this place.</lyric>
        <lyric>Please don’t give up on your mind.</lyric>
        <lyric>Please come back to us!</lyric>
        <lyric>Just what did you see?</lyric>
        <lyric>Oh {0}... Please come back to your senses…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="4">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>The high rankers go crazy, too…</lyric>
        <lyric>Just how long will I endure this madness?</lyric>
        <lyric>No one is safe here…</lyric>
        <lyric>What drove them insane…?</lyric>
        <lyric>{0}... They hit the maximum mental corruption level… Oh God…</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
    <grade level="5">
      <lyrics rwbp="a">
        <lyric>Madness rules this place…</lyric>
        <lyric>{0}... {0}... Not you… You were supposed to protect us…</lyric>
        <lyric>THAT PERSON WILL KILL US ALL! THIS PLACE WILL TURN TO HELL FOR US!</lyric>
        <lyric>WE WILL ALL BE DRIVEN MAD AND DIE JUST LIKE THEM!!!</lyric>
        <lyric>There’s no hope left in this place… Everyone eventually goes crazy…</lyric>
        <lyric>It will only be a matter of time before I turn mad just like {0}...</lyric>
      </lyrics>
    </grade>
  </category>
  <!--Tumblbug Agent Lyrics -->
  <credit>
    <category type="normal">
      <unit id="0">
        <!--미스터블랙 -->
        <lyric>Laughter is the best medicine. Clearly it’s good for you, so laugh!</lyric>
        <lyric>HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</lyric>
        <lyric>Grin from ear to ear! Look, like this~!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="1">
        <!-- 양치기 -->
        <lyric>A shepherd tends to the sheep for their wool and meat. It’s just like what we do here.</lyric>
        <lyric>Things like this happen too often in the world. Even among people.</lyric>
        <lyric>At the end of the day, however, those Abnormalities are not sheep. That’s for certain.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="2">
        <!--김대리 -->
        <lyric>Where… Where are my stomach pills…?</lyric>
        <lyric>Sigh, I wish I could go home in time today…</lyric>
        <lyric>No, sir! I didn’t say anything bad, manager sir!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="3">
        <!--아란 -->
        <lyric>Pff, whatever.</lyric>
        <lyric>Hey, I’m always trying my best here.</lyric>
        <lyric>Annoying.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="4">
        <!--유메카 -->
        <lyric>Oh I’m craving strawberry cake…</lyric>
        <lyric>What day is it today? I forgot again.</lyric>
        <lyric>What am I supposed to do here again? Oh that, yeah.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="5">
        <!--이희창 -->
        <lyric>I’m just doing this for the money, not because I enjoy it.</lyric>
        <lyric>Annoying… Irritating… A pain in the neck…</lyric>
        <lyric>God I really need to quit this job.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="6">
        <!--전상민 -->
        <lyric>Jeez, I don’t wanna do anything.</lyric>
        <lyric>I wonder how many will die today?</lyric>
        <lyric>Perhaps my death is already approaching, will it be soon?</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="7">
        <!--에피비네아 -->
        <lyric>Oh, I wonder if I should make lucky charms for everyone…? I’ll secretly sneak them onto people, even if they refuse!</lyric>
        <lyric>Let’s see, Abnormality observation report. And here’s another Abnormality report… Oh! Here it is! The employee observation report!</lyric>
        <lyric>They say we should spend breaktime doing things that are good for us. I guess that makes it fine to spy on people to make sure they’re okay, right…? It comforts me.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="8">
        <!--PESCA -->
        <lyric>Sigh… There’s not a single handsome guy here…</lyric>
        <lyric>I just want to work a little and earn a lot…</lyric>
        <lyric>I hope I’ll get to work with a cute Abnormality! If that’s possible…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="9">
        <!--SpeciaLee -->
        <lyric>Overtime yet again… Great…</lyric>
        <lyric>I wanna go home.</lyric>
        <lyric>Ah… I don’t wanna.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="10">
        <!--예띠 -->
        <lyric>I want to see more Abnormalities when I get promoted! I’ll get to do that, right?</lyric>
        <lyric>I feel like I’m capable enough to ask for better treatment than this, no?</lyric>
        <lyric>My friends and family will be so super-surprised when they hear that I’m working here! Hehe!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="11">
        <!--알렉스 -->
        <lyric>Oh, sorry. Can I help you?</lyric>
        <lyric>I’m planning to have spaghetti for dinner.</lyric>
        <lyric>Always maintain focus. You never know what could happen.</lyric>
      </unit>
    </category>
    <category type="panic">
      <unit id="0">
        <lyric>SMILE! SMILE! SMILE!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="1">
        <lyric>The old days… They were so much better!! Guards!!! GUAAARDS!!!!!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="2">
        <lyric>YAY! OVERWORK AGAIN!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="3">
        <lyric>Going to graduate school was my biggest mistake!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="4">
        <lyric>It’s not a bunny! No way! I won’t do it!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="5">
        <lyric>I SHOULD HAVE QUIT A LONG TIME AGO!!!!! AAAAAAAAAAH!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="6">
        <lyric>I don’t want to die to the likes of them!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="7">
        <lyric>N-No… Everyone will die! Just like he did…!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="8">
        <lyric>Oh heavens! Somebody help me!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="9">
        <lyric>...</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="10">
        <lyric>I should never have come here in the first place. What a fool I am… I want to go home. I want to go home… Please…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="11">
        <lyric>AHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!! I’ve never felt better in my life!!!</lyric>
      </unit>
    </category>
    <category type="horror">
      <unit id="0">
        <lyric>Hey buddy, are you smiling like a good boy?</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="1">
        <lyric>These… These damned things…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="2">
        <lyric>I haven’t gone home yet!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="3">
        <lyric>The work never ends huh…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="4">
        <lyric>That’s a bunny… That’s a fluffy, cute bunny…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="5">
        <lyric>It’s all over now…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="6">
        <lyric>We’re all done for.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="7">
        <lyric>Have you lost something dear to you too…?</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="8">
        <lyric>Wow, how marvelous! I want to touch it!♡♡♡</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="9">
        <lyric>?!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="10">
        <lyric>Wow! Maybe we can be friends?</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="11">
        <lyric> ...Okay, here goes nothing.</lyric>
      </unit>
    </category>
    <category type="otherdead">
      <unit id="0">
        <lyric>…… I won’t get to see your smile anymore.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="1">
        <lyric>I told you that they were not sheep nor hounds…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="2">
        <lyric>I- I need to get out of here!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="3">
        <lyric>I didn’t get my degree for this!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="4">
        <lyric>Are, are you dead? Seriously? I don’t know anything!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="5">
        <lyric>We’re all going to die…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="6">
        <lyric>I could’ve ended up like that if I were a bit late…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="7">
        <lyric>…… I thought I could protect them this time.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="8">
        <lyric>I’m not going to die until I meet a handsome guy…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="9">
        <lyric>!!!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="10">
        <lyric>I- I…. I know I’ll end up just like that someday… but…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="11">
        <lyric>That is why I do not make promises.</lyric>
      </unit>
    </category>
    <category type="otherpanic">
      <unit id="0">
        <lyric>Just smile my friend! It will calm you down.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="1">
        <lyric>Get out of my face, you piece of trash.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="2">
        <lyric>O-Overtime again?!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="3">
        <lyric>Someone stop them!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="4">
        <lyric>Again? Looks like I’m the only sane one here.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="5">
        <lyric>Huh? What’s going on? I feel like I should be running.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="6">
        <lyric>Let’s take care of that idiot before things get out of control.</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="7">
        <lyric>I wish I could calm you down, but…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="8">
        <lyric>Get it together! What happened to you?</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="9">
        <lyric>!</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="10">
        <lyric>I can’t believe people’s minds can turn on a dime like that… I’m not sure I’ll be fine…</lyric>
      </unit>
      <unit id="11">
        <lyric>This is much sadder than I expected.</lyric>
      </unit>
    </category>
  </credit>
</root>