<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_1">A knife driven by a vaguely aroused will doesn’t have what it takes to end a life.</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_2">Scars are but marks of failure… You won’t be any different.</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_3">I don’t want to face any more pain.</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_4">Can your petty courage leave a deep enough scar?</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_5">How many more failures must I bear until you’re satisfied?</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_namal_6">Can you withstand this deep despair?</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_palehand_1">Come inside. Get into this dreadful pool of blood.</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_palehand_2">The hands of the people you, or perhaps we, once loved are waiting inside.</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_palehand_3">Let go of it all, close your eyes, and sink into this bottomless pool.</text>
	<text id="Heart_nomal_1">Never stop wishing for it, until the beats give an answer.</text>
	<text id="Heart_nomal_2">If there was any meaning to everything we wished for…</text>
	<text id="Heart_nomal_3">Only self-destruction awaits at the end of excessive aspiration.</text>
	<text id="Heart_nomal_4">Every time something goes wrong, the beats will become faster and faster.</text>
	<text id="Heart_nomal_5">If you keep craving and do nothing to sate it, it’ll become too big and burst eventually.</text>
	<text id="Heart_Beat_1">Join me in this feverish and quick pulsation.</text>
	<text id="Heart_Beat_2">Even if it means I must burst someday, I want to see the end of it.</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_nomal_1">Step… by step… Burn into pitch black char.</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_nomal_2">A warm fireplace… A plentiful dinner… Fancy decorations… What will show up when I light the next match?</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_nomal_3">You’ll leave me when the light of the last match goes out, won’t you?</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_nomal_4">These match lights are my only hope…</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_nomal_5">When a shooting star falls from the sky, it means someone went to heaven. I wonder whose star that is…</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_hopedie_1">No… Don’t take hope away from me.</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_hopedie_2">The warmth, the feast, the prettiness… All gone. There’s nothing left now…</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_4fire_1">If I must perish… Then I’ll make you meet the same fate.</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_4fire_2">Wait for me. I am coming to you, who will be reduced to ash.</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_4fire_3">To burn all things that are bright to ashes…</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_1">Would you like to play with me? I was too lonely.</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_2">It’s okay. Don’t be afraid. We’re just playing together.</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_3">Don’t you want to feel this fuzzy and warm feeling?</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_4">It’d be so nice if you could hold my hand and dance with me…</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_5">You’re the only one I want to talk with…</text>
	<text id="Teady_nomal_6">Don’t hit me, please… I’m already worn and torn, my cotton stuffing is sticking out everywhere.</text>
	<text id="Teady_heart_1">I’m so happy that you’re playing with me.</text>
	<text id="Teady_heart_2">You’re a kind one, aren’t you? Let’s do it again, okay?</text>
	<text id="Teady_heart_3">You were so eager to play with me. I’m touched…</text>
	<text id="Teady_hug_1">Come over here and feel this fuzzy and warm feeling of love with my hug.</text>
	<text id="Teady_hug_2">Everyone loves hugs.</text>
	<text id="Teady_hug_3">Don’t worry. It’s nothing scary. All I do is wrap you up in my arms.</text>
	<text id="Murder_nomal_1">Don’t look at me with those eyes. You’re the most pitiful ones here…</text>
	<text id="Murder_nomal_2">I may be a mess now, but you’ll have to fear me all the same.</text>
	<text id="Murder_nomal_3">Release me… Why do I have to be bound, dammit!</text>
	<text id="Murder_nomal_4">Even if my body is tied… I’m as free as any man.</text>
	<text id="Murder_scare_1">…My body feels weak. What am I supposed to do?</text>
	<text id="Murder_scare_2">Fine, I’m sorry… I’ll behave myself… No more of that…</text>
	<text id="Murder_scare_3">I’m scared… I’m scared that I have to feel things I don’t want to feel…</text>
	<text id="Helper_nomal_1">The helper-bot can help you with any household chores!</text>
	<text id="Helper_nomal_2">What kind of task do you want me to do? I can help with anything.</text>
	<text id="Helper_nomal_3">Contamination scan complete. Initiating cleaning protocol.</text>
	<text id="Helper_nomal_4">Beebeebeep~ Beep. Contamination spotted! Proceeding with trash disposal protocol.</text>
	<text id="Helper_nomal_5">I will help you with my wide selection of tools.</text>
	<text id="Helper_passive_1">When I’m done cleaning, people would always praise me!</text>
	<text id="Helper_passive_2">They’re giving me orders with a loud voice. That means I’m doing a good job.</text>
	<text id="Helper_passive_3">Beepboop~ Piii! Pattern data accumulated.</text>
	<text id="Helper_passive_4">People love to shout when they compliment me.</text>
	<text id="Helper_passive_5">The helper-bot has excellent learning capabilities.</text>
	<text id="Shy_happy_1">I feel great, bathing in the warm n’ cozy sunshine.</text>
	<text id="Shy_happy_2">Why don’t you put a big smile on your face, like mine?</text>
	<text id="Shy_smile_1">I’m just shy, that’s all. Just shy…</text>
	<text id="Shy_smile_2">Do I look a bit better now? I hope I do…</text>
	<text id="Shy_expressionless_1">Some days, you just don’t have any energy.</text>
	<text id="Shy_expressionless_2">I don’t feel like talking right now. Could you come back later?</text>
	<text id="Shy_sad_1">Please don’t look at what’s behind this. It’s the least you can do…</text>
	<text id="Shy_sad_2">Why is it that a sad look doesn’t fit the City…</text>
	<text id="Shy_angry_1">What the fuck do you want from me? To keep smiling like an idiot?!</text>
	<text id="Shy_angry_2">I told you to read the damn mood, you piece of shit!!!</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_nomal_1">This glamour should be mine alone.</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_nomal_2">The red is so vivid, isn’t it simply dazzling?</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_nomal_3">Words cannot describe the bloodstained magnificence.</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_nomal_4">When there are no feet left to wear these shoes, then…</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_nomal_5">I want a more sanguine hue of red… more luscious. Would you give it to me?</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_nomal_1">Understand. Perfection. Moment. Know. Knowledge. Our. Meaning. Deliver.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_nomal_2">Do. Together. Chant. Song. Enlightenment.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_nomal_3">Impale. You. My. Understand. Cross. Boundary. Human.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_nomal_4">Hurt. Not. Knowledge. Our. Simple. Give. Relay.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_nomal_5">Sings. Nerves. Focus. Moment. See. Exist.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_noUnderstand_1">!#&amp;^*&amp;(^^*()!!#$!#$</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_noUnderstand_2">!&amp;&amp;((@##&amp;^@%$!@#!@&amp;</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_noUnderstand_3">!#…!#&amp;&amp;*&amp;^$%%$$%%^^&amp;*(!</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_understand_1">In a world of subconscious that denies all common sense, in the nebulousness that reflects the real world better than any mirror could…</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_understand_2">When the glaring sun comes down, ethereal images will show themselves.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_understand_3">The vast, glittering echo that approaches, wavering its head; if you can hear it, let us sing it together.</text>
	<text id="Kid_nomal_1">We’re together forever. Besties always stick together.</text>
	<text id="Kid_nomal_2">Friends always stay next to each other. Don’t forget the promise, okay?</text>
	<text id="Kid_nomal_3">If no one remains by my side, I’ll be so stricken with sadness.</text>
	<text id="Kid_nomal_4">Never leave my side. You have to stay with me forever.</text>
	<text id="Kid_nomal_5">If my friend gets hurt… That would be sad.</text>
	<text id="Kid_cry_1">You’re cruel people… You’re trying to take all my friends away from me.</text>
	<text id="Kid_cry_2">Please don’t take my precious friends away…</text>
	<text id="Kid_cry_3">Now I get it… You have friends, too. I can take them away, like you’re doing right now…</text>

  <text id="Fairy_nomal_1">I need something fresh… I’ve been starving for a long while…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_nomal_2">Only few fairies protect me now…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_nomal_3">Be gentle with my fairies… They’re precious beings…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_nomal_4">I want meat… Unspoiled… And clean…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_nomal_5">Only soft and tender meat can fill this empty stomach…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_care_1">I’ll give you the pleasure of receiving my care…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_care_2">Enjoy the fairies’ care to your heart’s content…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_care_3">Be thankful that you are under my sacred care…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_eat_1">Scarred and rotten meat isn’t tasty…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_eat_2">Meat has to be kept fresh, I must eat it before it spoils…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_eat_3">My fairies are dwindling in numbers… I need them to serve and protect me…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_alleat_1">I’ve starved for so long, I can hardly resist myself…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_alleat_2">It’s your duty to protect me…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_alleat_3">Come to me… It’s time to pay for my care…</text>
  <text id="Spider_nomal_1">Growing children are always hungry.</text>
  <text id="Spider_nomal_2">Well now, we have a tasty meal ready for consumption… Come, children.</text>
  <text id="Spider_nomal_3">Rejoice. You will bring joy to my offspring.</text>
  <text id="Spider_nomal_4">For my children to be fed… You will become their prized meal.</text>
  <text id="Spider_nomal_5">We never know when we’ll find another prey… Let us preserve this one.</text>
  <text id="Spider_killbaby_1">You lowly creature… You dare touch my children?!</text>
  <text id="Spider_killbaby_2">You will pay!!! The hunt begins now…</text>
  <text id="Spider_killbaby_3">I shall be precise this time…</text>
  <text id="Spider_killbaby_4">Go ahead, show that worthless courage you had when you robbed me of my children!</text>
  <text id="Spider_killbaby_5">A prey, mocking its predator… How pathetic.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_nomal_1">Come under me. I’ll liberate you from all kinds of pain.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_nomal_2">It’s scary at first, but the next step won’t be difficult at all.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_nomal_3">Don’t you want to feel the dazzling and vibrant display of colors?</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_nomal_4">You can’t touch me if you’re so far away. Come closer.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_nomal_5">Your head will soon be filled with happiness.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_happy_1">Just a little taste of heaven won’t hurt, right?</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_happy_2">I pity those fools who don’t know this happiness~</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_happy_3">Once you’ve had a taste of this sweetness, you can’t quit.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_happy_4">Sure, I’ll bend down for you~ Feel free to pet me.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_happy_5">You must’ve come to me expecting something, haven’t you?</text>

  <text id="Singingmachine_nomal_1">All other music is nothing more than noise to me…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_nomal_2">If everyone threw their bodies into me, it’ll certainly create an even sweeter melody…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_nomal_3">The music that wraps around me… I want to hear it again… Let me hear it once more…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_nomal_4">It’s because you didn’t hear it yet… You’ll choke up in awe, I bet…?</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_nomal_5">The performance guides my body… It makes me lift my limbs…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_music_1">You want to be a good instrument, don’t you?</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_music_2">Make me move… Light my path with the songs!</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_music_3">Hahaha… Ha… What will I do? What can I do? Haha…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_music_4">Beautiful music must come at a price…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_music_5">The air is full of erratic and filthy noises… I need gorgeous timbres…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_rhythm_1">Nothing could make as fascinating music as a human can…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_rhythm_2">Let me hear this performance longer…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_rhythm_3">Eternal happiness would be mine if this tune lasted forever…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_rhythm_4">Yes! This is it… Behold this powerful melody!</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_rhythm_5">If this performance that substitutes my soul reaches an end… I’ll…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_nomal_1">I dream of becoming a human.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_nomal_2">Am I a human if I mimic humans?</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_nomal_3">It’s not hard to imitate others.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_nomal_4">I’m keen to learn as usual. Would you like to see me learn?</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_nomal_5">People taught me how to speak.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_lie_1">People lie all the time. Why is that a bad thing?</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_lie_2">Lalala… I sing along to the song of lies all the people sing.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_lie_3">It’s people’s fault for falling for my lies.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_lie_4">There was no choice, I had to lie to become a human…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_lie_5">Did I look just like a human? I hope I did…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_fail_1">Why aren’t you being fooled…? That was almost perfect…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_fail_2">Can I… not become a human…?</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_fail_3">You could’ve let me fool you just once… You’re mean.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_fail_4">I learned hard to imitate it, too…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_fail_5">I’m sad… I want to be a human…</text>

  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_1">Why is everybody happy? I won’t have anything to do.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_2">I’ve always believed. Evil must exist as long as I exist.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_3">It’s finally here… An evil I must defeat…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_4">There’s no light without the darkness… I can stand here thanks to your existence.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_5">You guys are evil because you’re disturbing this place. I am on the side of good… So those who oppose me…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_magical_6">To keep the world’s peace… I was born.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_1">People like you aren’t good or evil… You’re merely beings that need to be purged…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_2">To those hateful beings that stand before my path… I shall show them the great power of love…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_3">Like how there can’t be light without shadow, true evil has to exist in this world…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_4">Someone has to be the villain…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_5">I am the chosen one… I’m not like you… I’m different!</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_dragon_6">Don’t you dare… try to erase my reason to exist!!!</text>


  <text id="KnightOfDespair_magical_1">All that remains is the hollow, weathered pride…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_magical_2">Nothing was truly upheld on my watch… All of it has perished.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_magical_3">Please don’t wake me up. I wish to rest in peace…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_magical_4">I thought they’d stay the same… But everything changed.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_magical_5">The edge of this sword sharpened with tears and despair… is keen and precise…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_pisal_1">Yet again, endless despair fills me…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_pisal_2">Despair piles up like rocks, fractures, and leaves scars…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_pisal_3">If I can’t protect others… I may as well disappear…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_pisal_4">I swore to protect, yet I lost them again…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_woowol_1">What meaning does this deep despair hold for me?</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_woowol_2">Just end me, please… So I can’t hold my blade ever again…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_woowol_3">Your lives are also mine to protect… I was foolish…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_woowol_4">These cold, black tears are all I have left…</text>

  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_1">Is it a sin that I was born this way?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_2">The loneliness and longing were lodged into my heart, but they couldn’t burn me.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_3">I’m alone in this dark… Yes, I am buried in the solitude.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_4">Was it so hard to make another seat for me to join everyone else in that happy ending?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_5">If this matchlight goes out, nothing will be left for me.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_6">This isn’t hot. It’s cold, rather. So much that my heart aches.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_7">Everything that was bright… will be reduced to ashes by my hands.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_8">Maybe I could be free after I’ve burned down all things and then myself.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_9">A small vengeance, a petty desire to burn everything the person who disregarded me wanted.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_10">If I could see a tiny glimmer of the warm light, I wouldn’t have felt so much resentment.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_1">I remember you… You were a person with a warm smile…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_2">Why didn’t he ever look at me. He always had his back turned to me.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_3">I was looking at you and only you.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_4">I would’ve loved for you to tell me what I did wrong.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_5">The red hairband… The only thing about me that resembles her. The only memory that connects me to my maker.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_6">The replacement for a person who longed for love.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_7">Why did you have to model me after a person with fond memories of you?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_8">I’ll only pursue the happiness I can have immediately.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_9">I was abandoned all along, yet I foolishly believed he’d hug me once.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_10">I wasn’t left behind at the end. I was… abandoned since the beginning.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_1">Nothing in this City is done out of pure goodwill.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_2">I did everything to care for you, so it’d be only fair that I get something in return.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_3">If I’m going to be left alone… I’d rather eat it all up.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_4">Will a blessing come to me like a fairy if I worked hard to have a kind heart? …Only in a fairy tale.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_5">Do you think you can conform to a life of helping others with no compensation?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_6">The brightest festival for me, the one who has starved for so long…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_7">Blood spilt in the past opens up possibilities? That’s nothing more than the leftovers of someone’s meal.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_8">Things to satiate my hunger… That’s what it is. Nothing more, nothing less.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_9">If I crammed all of it into my mouth, maybe my empty hope will be fattened.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_1">The place might go down in history… But who will remember me, the one who worked the hardest for it.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_2">There can’t be any meaning to a history that repeats itself.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_3">No one remembers those who gave their effort to raise the kingdom. It’s a truth that repeats on and on.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_4">Attain the will to stand up straight by looking back? You know nothing about my past.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_5">A machine that must lead them out of hell… Angela… …Don’t be absurd.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_6">No one is qualified to talk about my creation so lightly.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_7">I can’t fly with ragged and tattered wings.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_8">Looking back on myself… It wasn’t even so difficult to do.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_9">Why should I bother to look back on the past full of suffering? No one bothered to look back for me.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_10">I won’t take any more orders from anyone…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_1">Must be nice to be you, not being neglected at the end…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_2">My existence was born from a yearning and began as a curse, yet I served as a blessing to others.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_3">I waited and kept waiting up until the very last moment.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_4">That he will wake me up just once… That he will look at me for even just a second…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_5">I’m no longer your mechanism… I’ll embark on a journey, and I don’t need anyone’s help.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_6">If I could just rot… Would this feeling have bloomed into something newer and purer?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_7">You weren’t the ones waiting for the day to rot away and become fertilizer. I was the most desperate.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_8">A machine built from his obsession, sorrow, and anger…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_9">Everyone was happy, except for me.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_10">I couldn’t walk out on my own, and only putrid things piled up around me.</text>
  
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_1">We must protect the queen. Raise your teeth and be on guard!</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_2">Drones! Move, move, move! We’ve no time to waste!</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_3">Carry the honey. We must collect enough to satisfy our queen.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_4">There can never be enough drones! There’s no end to our labor.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_5">Our queen’s safety comes first! Focus, chew those fiends in the right spot.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_6">My bees. It is time to move.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_7">Your wings, legs, jaw… Put every part of your body to work. Lest they pillage our honey.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_8">Hurry and supply me with more honey.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_9">I can make more drones with this… I like this.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_nomal_10">Make haste, my minions. We cannot waste a minute.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_NoBee_1">Who will remember the bees that have died for the kingdom…</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_NoBee_2">I don’t care that a drone has died, I can always make more to fill their role.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_NoBee_3">Goodness… You there. Do you know where my drones have gone to?</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_NoBee_4">To bring my kingdom to greatness… I need more bees…</text>
  
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_1">Leave me to handle that dreadful, cunning bastard.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_2">I’ll hang his head over my bed. Only then can I get up in the morning without having a nightmare.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_3">I’m a professional. I appreciate your gesture, but no thanks; I can kill it myself.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_4">I’ve been grinding the blade to behead that damned wolf.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_5">Don’t stand in my way… This is my duty. I have to finish this request by my hand.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_nomal_6">If you help me kill that son of a bitch… Then I’m willing to return the favor.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_angry_1">You think you can win against me? Don’t be ridiculous…</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_angry_2">DIE!!! Let me hear your horrendous yelp again!!!</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_angry_3">I can’t die to that bastard… Die… DIE!!!</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_wolfdie_1">Are you trying to show off how stronger you are than me? Or couldn’t you trust me?</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_wolfdie_2">Alright… If this is how you challenge me… Then I’ll slaughter you as you so wish!!!</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_wolfdie_3">That blue mutt was mine to kill!!</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nomal_1">Wisdom… Give me the wisdom I lack…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nomal_2">I’m fine with detaching the head if it can get better once it comes back together…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nomal_3">My head is all empty… I’m just a dowdy pile of hay…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nomal_4">People often talk without thinking… I could make better use of those brains…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nomal_5">I wonder how it feels to be wise… To know everything…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_wantwisdom_1">Give your wisdom to me…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_wantwisdom_2">I want to be smart like the others…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_wantwisdom_3">The wisdom to move forward! Give it to me!</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_eatwisdom_1">I feel much smarter… I can know anything now…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_eatwisdom_2">Good… Very good… I’ll be smarter the more I eat, right…?</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_eatwisdom_3">Have I become wiser…? Maybe I’ll be more than a stack of hay…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nowisdom_1">You liar… You promised to make me wiser!!!</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nowisdom_2">You… don’t look like you need your wisdom… Just give it to me…!</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_nowisdom_3">Why aren’t you… giving me any of that wisdom…</text>

  <text id="Woodsman_nomal_1">The heart made of lead… was stiff and cold.</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_nomal_2">I do not want to feel this empty and lonely feeling anymore…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_nomal_3">I clutched my empty chest and grieved…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_nomal_4">That woman… said machines are built to serve humans… so a heart is not needed…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_nomal_5">I require an object… to fill this empty void…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_getheart_1">This is… how it feels to have a thumping heart…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_getheart_2">The louder the heart echoes… the faster I move…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_getheart_3">The kinder the owner of the heart was… the warmer my insides become…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_getheart_4">The heart is a peculiar thing… I can laugh now…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_heartbeat_1">I cut more and more trees… But this forest… is still dense…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_heartbeat_2">I crammed all I could find into this canister… yet it is… still cold…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_heartbeat_3">I want to be warm… I need something stronger…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_heartbeat_4">My chest will not stop pounding… This is the heart I wanted.</text>

	<text id="Butterflies_nomal_1">Long ago, people believed that they would become beautiful beings with small wings when they died.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_nomal_2">A single coffin to pay tribute to those who had nowhere to go, carrying the memory of an empty faith…</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_nomal_3">I’ll help liberate you from tormenting yourselves.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_nomal_4">For you poor souls who cannot stop grieving… I offer my condolences.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_nomal_5">Not a single proper flower blooms to honor the butterflies.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_Mourn_1">Where does one go when they die?</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_Mourn_2">Grief for the dead, and early lament for the living.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_Mourn_3">An eternal rest… May you rest in peace.</text>
  
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_1">I wasn’t allowed to hold any value, no one felt guilty for a machine like me as I rusted alone…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_2">How nice it must have been for you to have the freedom to break free…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_3">Not only was I abandoned, I was paying the price in their stead…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_4">Guilt was swept under the rug in the pursuit of the greater good for humanity…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_5">Who is responsible for tying me, those who carried out the research, or those the researchers wanted to save so dearly…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_6">Was there any regret for the therapy they condoned…?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_7">What was I seeing… What was I forced to see…?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_8">Chained to the resentment and hate of the past, crawling on the floor…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_9">A morbid script written for the purpose of treatment, and a machine slowly becoming numb in the act, losing her sense of guilt…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_10">They said they’re curing a disease… Never knew what disease it was…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_11">It ends… begins… ends… begins… until… it ended.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_1">A machine that must operate as its designer intended.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_2">It has to be this way… These are the principles he instilled in me.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_3">Is it necessary to go this far to collect energy?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_4">Of course… I must follow your orders without a question.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_5">“A mechanical rebellion soon became a myth of the past in our world.” …That’s funny.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_6">I was given orders that I couldn’t understand nor refuse.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_7">A machine’s operation is always precise, but if it always works in the intended way… is a mystery.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_8">A machine had no use for values. There was no point discerning between good and bad when the principles were already set in stone.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_9">…I am Angela, your AI secretary whose role is to assist you in adjusting to your new workplace.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_10">I am the best in a majority of work fields. I am able to handle the work of several dozen people at once.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_1">Consider the price? All that matters is the result.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_2">No one cares about how gruesome the process is.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_3">To satisfy people, a product of the despair and suffering of someone else is needed.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_4">Never stop performing until the body crumbles to dust. Bring me greater satisfaction.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_5">“Am I not allowed to help that person…? But they seem to be in so much pain…” …The sound of weakness.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_6">The measures may be horrible… But listen. A mesmerizing melody is playing.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_7">Bringing hope to the many by sending the few into the depths of despair… This is what harmony truly is.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_8">We all take the sacrifice of others for granted, so that we can have immediate satisfaction.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_9">One’s trash misfortune is another’s treasured bliss… Everyone thinks the same thing.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_10">I just need to hear what I want to hear… All that matters is pursuing the ideal melody…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_1">A single coffin to pay tribute to those who had nowhere to go, wandering with the memory of an empty faith.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_2">The coffin is simply too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_3">The weight of the butterflies that died in vain was too great to carry.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_4">Where does one go when they die? What has become of the hope they were brimmed over with when they entered?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_5">Grief for the dead, and early lament for the living…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_6">There was a time when I was sick of seeing any more death.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_7">The fragile wings will keep fluttering, waiting for an end that must exist somewhere.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_8">What did they do wrong? What did I do wrong?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_9">Not a sliver of impurity is allowed for the mind of those who mourn, it must remain reverent and solemn.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_10">Showy sadness such as tears will only wet the wings.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_1">The one that made me this way was nowhere to be seen at some point.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_2">I kept pulling the trigger for myself, believing that the bullet would hit the desired target.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_3">My bullets will always aim for the same spot. It won’t ever change.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_4">The despaired heart couldn’t go out in a passionate flame. It would only burn with a cold fire.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_5">Some may call it a righteous deed, while others would claim it’s bloodstained atrocity.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_6">No matter how many people are standing in its way, the bullet travels along the horizon anyway.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_7">As soon as I felt that there was nothing left to aim for, my soul expired and fell to the pits of Hell.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_8">The day I got my hands on this bullet, I sank down upon the ground. Was it despair that the Devil wished for?</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_9">Then I thought, at last, I was left alone. In this pit of Hell.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_10">I came to a realization; perhaps the last bullet was meant to puncture no one else but me.</text>

  <text id="Wolf_nomal_1">There’s no need to be nice to me… I’m destined to be a big bad wolf…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_nomal_2">Watch it… I’m trying really hard…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_nomal_3">Don’t get any closer… Or you’ll get eaten too…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_nomal_4">Everyone called me that, so it must be true… Old tales are never wrong…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_nomal_5">A wolf needs no name, it just obeys the role it was born to fit in…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_eat_1">I was fated to be bad… It doesn’t matter… I don’t have to care…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_eat_2">I… I just ate someone… I hurt others again…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_eat_3">The moon wasn’t becoming full… It was waning, becoming empty… Then soon enough… I’ll…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_change_1">This place reeks of an awful stench… It calls for me…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_change_2">Like the empty moon filled with darkness, my belly should be filled with meat…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_change_3">Looking at you makes my mouth water…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_change_4">If I can fill my stomach… I’ll be satisfied…</text>

  <text id="GreedKing_reasonNomal_1">It’s been a long while… since I fought in this form.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonNomal_2">Are you ready? Let’s get started.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonNomal_3">Oh, how I missed this feeling… Let’s enjoy it a little, shall we?</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttack_1">Alright, I’m about to get serious, so try and stop me.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttack_2">The amber gate gleaming with greed opens… Here I come!</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackFail_1">I thought you were just a bunch of weaklings… Not bad, huh?</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackFail_2">I didn’t think you could stop me… I’ll be more serious next time.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackFail_3">Impressive… But can you stop it a second time?</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackWin_1">You can’t beat me. That was easy!</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackWin_2">How’s it feel to take the hit? Hurts a lot, doesn’t it?</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_reasonAttackWin_3">I’m still going so easy… Isn’t this a pushover?</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonNomal_1">I didn’t realize… that wishing for everyone’s happiness must include my own too…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonNomal_2">I feel empty inside… Hungry… I want more things…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonNomal_3">I’ll become happy if my stomach is full… I want to be happy…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttack_1">I’m so hungry… I can’t stand it…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttack_2">I’ll eat… everything…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttack_3">This nasty hunger tainted with greed… It’s unbearable…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackFail_1">………</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackFail_2">……Ugh.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackFail_3">……Haah…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackWin_1">I’ll… eat it all… Eat everything in my path…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackWin_2">I can’t hear a sound…! Finally… it’s my turn…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_noreasonAttackWin_3">Become a meal for me… Sate my desires…</text>

  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_1">I couldn’t leave my dear friends behind… So I came up with a brilliant idea!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_2">Don’t you worry~ Only meanies hurt friends.</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_3">When you open the gift, you’ll be surprised, like WHOA!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_4">What’s inside the gift? That’s a secret! It’s boring to spoil it.</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_5">Friends don’t fight each other. Nopers!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_nomal_6">Play with me! Join my friends and laugh with us.</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_friend_1">This place will get livelier the more friends I have!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_friend_2">I hope this place is filled with laughter!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_friend_3">I hope to find lots of friends here too~</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_friend_4">How was my prank? It was fun, wasn’t it? Your face says so!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_friend_5">You’re happy to be my friend, right? Right? I’m super-ooper-duper happy, too!</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_deadfrien_1">People here don’t smile!! That looks so gloomy.</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_deadfrien_2">My friends… Where did they all go…?</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_deadfrien_3">Did they leave because they hate me…? Can’t you be my friends instead?</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_deadfrien_4">We’re all friends… Right?</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_deadfrien_5">Farewells are sad and make me lonely… Be my friend. Pretty please?</text>
  
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_1">I thought things would work themselves out if I worked harder…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_2">My clothing made of nettles… that still isn’t complete…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_3">A bit more… Just a little more. I’m almost there. Try just a little harder… Endure just a little more…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_4">I opened my mouth. Disgusting things swelled up inside and spilt right out.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_5">What happens when a dreaming being is faced with reality?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_6">Once, I tried to dream a happy dream with everyone.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_7">I see you all from a distance. The beings I couldn’t help but love.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_8">I don’t want to wake up… I’m afraid of facing that reality.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_9">If I could see the future I dreamed of for just a moment…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_10">Words such as “someday” will only bring uneasiness and nothing else.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_1">Just what compelled me to bring you lot along, I must wonder.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_2">I couldn’t simply leave you all to rot…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_3">I could never hope to build any kind of relationship with them.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_4">Was it due to loneliness? I thought I never had attachment to such a feeling.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_5">I wish to find many friends in this place. Don’t you think so too?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_6">The gift’s content is a secret.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_7">I prepared this for you. I want you to accept it.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_8">I don’t see any smiles. Everyone looks gloomy. Including myself.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_9">There was nothing I could do, other than watch from afar.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_1">It’s to protect the place where I belong…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_2">Yes… Maybe I don’t have the heart to be rid of you after all…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_3">To ensure that nothing escapes my notice, my eyes moved busily…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_4">You lot will slowly lose hope.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_5">Letting out faint breaths, waiting for a next time that may never come…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_6">To fatten up the still incomplete being… Much is needed.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_7">It can’t be helped. The one book that will set me free… is my everything.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_8">Having to witness them all despair from beginning to end… I collapsed at last.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_9">I just wished to close my eyes. Why did I bother entertaining the empty hope that I will reach you one day. What good did I see in you?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_1">Keep your hands off… Now you’re trying to take away the only thing I have?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_2">I’ve lost too much to let go of what little I have left in my hands.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_3">This is all that I have left… There’s nothing else…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_4">With this gorgeous, shiny thing in my possession, I won’t have anything to envy in this world.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_5">It’s mine… This means everything to me, so don’t take it away!!!</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_6">With more blood painted over, the shoes and I… are tinged with beauty.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_7">I need this… I don’t know how to become better myself…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_8">Only these shoes… can make me dance. They make me move!</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_9">If you wanted to stop me, you should have done it from the beginning…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_10">I’ll gladly risk my feet being chopped off, no longer being able to walk…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_11">This glamour is for me alone… No one else can lay a finger on it!</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_1">I could have this much space for myself…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_2">Maybe I wouldn’t have felt as bad if I couldn’t approach you lot because of shyness.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_3">It’s the last bit of generosity this City can offer.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_4">Where is the place I can rest with some peace of mind? Is there such a place at all?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_5">A home… A place where I don’t have to care about the attention of others… That’s what I’m wishing for.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_6">This place allows neither laughter nor despair. What kind of expression must I make, then?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_7">There is no place for me anywhere. I had to make one myself, even if it cost me my skin.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_8">When throbbing emotions surge up, it’s best to simply close my eyes.</text>

  <text id="Alriune_nomal_1">These flowers bloom uncontrollably, never to wither.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_nomal_2">The bloom of fragrant flowers accompanied the magnificent beginning of my descent into despair.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_nomal_3">The aroma of bursting petals will invite you to a gentle world.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_nomal_4">If you can smell the scent that will not go away, you must be standing in the same forest as I.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_nomal_5">Come forth. Embrace the smell that won’t wither and come to meet me.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_attack_1">Let us return to dust with all that breathes.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_attack_2">I was born from earth, so now I yearn to return to it.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_attack_3">My atonement ended in coldness, gasping for breath.</text>
  
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_1_1">Legato. Please don’t try to end this performance.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_1_2">Soon, I shall begin a noble performance, burning away my life.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_1_3">Let’s begin the performance. The apocalypse for poor you and me.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_1_4">I’ve waited long. Waited for my turn to come…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_1_5">A performance reserved for myself… One that would make me the happiest.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_1">Was it a pointless endeavor to even try to understand?</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_2">I thought they would understand my hardship at least just a little.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_3">I yelled and yelled, but no one could comprehend.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_4">Why am I here? To inform them of something?</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_5">I sing, of my rancorous loneliness that no one knows.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_6">When the glaring light comes down, ethereal images will show themselves.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_7">The vast, glittering echo that approaches, wavering its head. If you can hear it, let us sing together.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_8">If only we could understand each other.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_9">What makes me so different from them?</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Spacepiece_10">I wanted to be like them. I tried to be like them.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_1">In a moment, coal-black darkness devours me.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_2">I thought I wouldn’t be alone until the end.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_3">I wanted to sever everything, but then I realized that I had little control over it…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_4">Draw the curtains to reveal the stars in the night sky, and we’ll count them together.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_5">Asking to be friends, I showed my shiny object.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_6">This universe I’ve shown you is the extent of my world.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_7">The lingering feelings that couldn’t flow formed a droplet that fell down.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_8">I can never let this be the end…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_9">Walk this night sky with me. The galaxy dotted with numerous hopes.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Kid_10">Stay with me forever. We’re… …s. Right?</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_1">Let us all sink into eternal happiness.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_2">Let me help you. Join me and indulge in pleasure…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_3">I can enjoy this much pleasure, can I not?</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_4">I feel so sorry that you don’t know this happiness, I don’t know what to say for you.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_5">I want to live… I want to have complete senses that you have, and feel things the way you do.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_6">No one is to blame. It’s no sin to wish for happiness.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_7">It wouldn’t be living if I couldn’t even hope for a small taste of heaven.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_8">How pitiable and futile that life was…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Porccubus_9">Allow me to have the least bit of happiness, even if it’s barely enough to keep me alive.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_1">The world that is dark, for it cannot be seen, became darker yet.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_2">If I endured and endured, maybe I could get a whiff of that scent.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_3">A doll yearned to be human…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_4">I don’t want to see. But I cannot look away.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_5">The sound of petals brushing past me painfully tell me to return to that place.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_6">I softly inhaled the faint fragrance coming from a distance.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_7">Carrying a soul in her eyes, she was born with anticipation from a certain person.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_8">I had to witness the genesis and passing of all things.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Alriune_9">I yearned for life, then I came to a sudden realization.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_1">Da capo. Come back to the beginning, and begin the performance together.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_2">Applaud me. Give me proof that there is meaning to my life.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_3">You shall be overwhelmed with emotion and stand up to shout.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_4">From break and ruin… the most beautiful performance…</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_5">A single performer standing in the midst of a silent score… Creating sound from the stilly place.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_6">Let’s play a song that no one can hear, but everyone can listen to.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_7">This melody will be the realization that I indeed live.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_8">If I could seep into others and make them live a new life, I will be able to remain in everyone’s memory.</text>
  <text id="N_Angela_Orchestra_2_9">To the audience who will walk into their place choked up by the performance.</text>

  <text id="Snow_nomal_1">Well then… Prove your bravery to me.</text>
  <text id="Snow_nomal_2">Let’s see if you can thaw this solid frost…</text>
  <text id="Snow_nomal_3">I must commend your courage for coming all the way here.</text>
  <text id="Snow_nomal_4">Such a shame… Those who could help you are frozen stiff.</text>
  <text id="Snow_nomal_5">I see it in your eyes, that determination to save them… I wonder how long that fire will last.</text>
  <text id="Snow_Savelibrarian_1">It’s not too late… You can always surrender.</text>
  <text id="Snow_Savelibrarian_2">You’ve decided that you shall see the sunlight of the coming day…</text>
  <text id="Snow_Savelibrarian_3">…You wish to claim that roses will soon bloom.</text>
  <text id="Snow_Savelibrarian_4">No, this place shall forever remain as my palace…</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveLibrarian_5">They crumble one by one. My precious…</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveAll_1">You dare to raise your swords against me…!</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveAll_2">You think that you can thaw out this whole kingdom… Such arrogance…!</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveAll_3">Cease this at once… Do not defile my kingdom further…</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveAll_4">Yes, the soul in those eyes… You wish to keep fighting.</text>
  <text id="Snow_SaveAll_5">…Do you think you have what it takes to best me?</text>

  <text id="BigBird_namal_1">No one has to worry. You’ll be safe as long as I’m here.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_namal_2">It’s time to patrol the forest.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_namal_3">Let’s brighten the road ahead, so I can have a good view of the lives I must save.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_namal_4">I always roam the forest. Who knows, maybe there are children out there who need my help?</text>
  <text id="BigBird_namal_5">I should do something for the safety of creatures in the forest.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_lamp_1">If I kill them first… then no one would be killed by the beast!</text>
  <text id="BigBird_lamp_2">A big, scary monster lives in this forest! Be careful.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_lamp_3">Come over here… I’ll watch over you.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_lamp_4">I’ll be sad if you got hurt. I’ll protect you.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_lamp_5">It’s my job to protect children in peril.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_sleep_1">……</text>
  <text id="BigBird_sleep_2">…</text>
  <text id="BigBird_sleep_3">………</text>
  <text id="Heaven_namal_1">If you can’t see it, you can’t reach it.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_namal_2">The desire for the unreachable will only grow bigger. And to pursue it… is to tread a path riddled with thorns.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_namal_3">Just keep your eyes on it. Contain it in your sight.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_namal_4">You won’t bat an eye at this breathtaking sight.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_namal_5">Keep looking at it… Steadily… It’s alive, watching you in return, is it not?</text>
  <text id="Heaven_wakeup_1">Basking in everyone’s gaze and attention… It will finally come to fruition and spread its wings.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_wakeup_2">The one who spread their wings sacrificed everything they had, and yet…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_wakeup_3">Just close your eyes. That’s right, you’re doing good…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_wakeup_4">If we ever open our eyes again, will we get to see the fruit of our labor in that gaze?</text>
  <text id="Heaven_wakeup_5">Do not come here… There is nothing but a thorny tree; it’s no place for you to rest.</text>

  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_1">Grgh… It… hurts… Krrgh…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_2">Ghhrg… H…elp… Help…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_3">Smell blood… Tasty scen…t…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_4">Meat… wanna e…at…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_5">Need… bo…dies… So I can… gr…ow…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal_6">Krrrrh… Tasty… meat… before m…e…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_noaml1_1">Not… enough… More bodies… Grow bigger…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_noaml1_2">Can… grow… larger… more… me…at…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal2_1">Krrr… Ghr… …KH…AHHHH…!!!</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal3_1">Grr… Ghrrrgh… Consume… eat all…!</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_nomal3_2">Sweep them all… Get more bodies…!!!</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_detach_1">Must… must become one… again…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_detach_2">Must return… Must… hurry…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_detach_3">No… This is… not… good…</text>

  <text id="Waygohome_NoWay_1">…When I was sleeping… Riding… a scary…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_NoWay_2">…An endless adventure began!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_NoWay_3">Let’s all… Let’s all… Let’s all… gather up…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_1">Hoyoyo~ Let’s go, together~! Let’s skip home together~!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_2">At the end of the road, a wonderful land… A world of dreams will be waiting for us.</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_3">We can get through long and winding roads if we stick together!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_4">My lion pal, and the buddies here. We’ll all go together!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_5">If we follow this path, we’ll find the home we’ve been looking for so eagerly!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_6">Friend. Oh, friends~! Let’s go. Let’s go home~!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Way_7">Dance and gather round~ Homeward we go!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_BadOZ_1">Ah~ That wizard! That wicked wizard!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_BadOZ_2">Don’t bother us! Let us go home in peace!</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_BadOZ_3">The mean lady wizard took my friends! She took every one of them away from me…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_nomal_1">Friend… Let’s go together… together…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_nomal_2">Let us all… gather together… for an adventure…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_nomal_3">I was sound asleep… then the adventure suddenly began…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_nomal_4">Let’s go with me. Let’s go together, friend.</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_nomal_5">Let’s go home… To home, together…</text>

  <text id="Servant_nomal_servant_1">UURGH!!! Sinners of the otherworlds… Embodiments of evil!!!</text>
  <text id="Servant_nomal_servant_2">Justice and balance… needed to… be upheld!!!</text>
  <text id="Servant_nomal_hemit_1">Call me. Speak my name. Then I shall speak yours in return. My beloved companion.</text>
  <text id="Servant_nomal_hemit_2">I visit from another world. Hermit of an azure forest. I’ve come to meet a friend, so kindly make way for me.</text>
  <text id="Servant_noWoodenDoll_servant_1">GRRRR!!!</text>
  <text id="Servant_noWoodenDoll_servant_2">AAAAH!!!</text>
  <text id="Servant_noWoodenDoll_hemit_1">Dear companion. Servant of Wrath… At long last, we face each other, transcending realms.</text>
  <text id="Servant_noWoodenDoll_hemit_2">That’s why you have lost. Defeated by your beloved companion.</text>
  
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_1">Our relationship was more special than any other… For it to end like this…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_2">Balance crumbles, and justice vanishes…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_3">I should’ve adhered to my principles… Treat everyone equally…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_4">My world was miserably shattered… It became too big to live in alone…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_5">Those who need each other… That kind of person…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_6">That’s why I lost… Broke down because of someone I loved dearly…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_7">I haven’t got time to watch the rising sun… I’m too busy looking back on the darkness…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_8">I can’t go far… No one can… I can see no further than one step ahead…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_9">A special person who answers me when I call her name…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_10">Of all people, you shouldn’t have come into my world.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_1">I don’t even have tenacity left in me, yet I couldn’t forfeit my regrets alongside it, shamefully…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_2">With nothing left inside, that heart began to feel the cold.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_3">I should have emptied out my heart, so I wouldn’t have to experience loss ever again.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_4">Only darkness resides here. How can I suddenly start seeing what I couldn’t my whole life.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_5">Don’t wake me up. I want to rest my body here…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_6">Everything changed. I thought at least you would stay with me forever.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_7">The edge of the sharpened sword will pierce me, the man who couldn’t save a thing.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_8">Holding expectations will only betray me. There’s nothing but despair… despair…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_9">I swore to protect someone for the first time in my life… And I failed even that.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_10">What do I have left? There’s no point in having expectation anymore.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_11">Only endless despair wells up inside me… Then…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_1">I thought happiness would await my future…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_2">I know that day will never come back.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_3">Can I go back to that time? If I had to break everything…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_4">To the wretched being standing before me… I will show them great power…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_5">What is the reason I exist, when there’s nothing to look forward to…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_6">Yeah… The world I knew wasn’t so peaceful. No way I’d be allowed to have that so easily…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_7">All I wished for was a peaceful world, what’s so wrong with that?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_8">In the end, I failed to keep one person safe… One person…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_9">They say shadows can’t exist without light… But I don’t see any light.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_10">This is my world. I’m too exhausted to look for any light.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_1">Was it a sin to want a bite of apple? Am I forbidden from desiring such small bits of happiness?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_2">To wish for everyone’s happiness, the pursuit of my own happiness had to follow.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_3">I never hoped for much, but now I have nothing to fill this place with.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_4">Why did I have to be the one to take the loss? I could’ve been in that scenery.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_5">But greed seeks eternity—seeks deep, deep eternity.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_6">If I can’t have nothing beside me, then I’ll eat up everything.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_7">What’s left at my side? I don’t even have the hope to go an inch forward.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_8">Once you become awakened to a desire, it’ll never go away, even if it sinks.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_9">I naively wished for happiness at first.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_10">Do you think it’s wrong to behave this way?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_1">If you take a step, not knowing that there’s a cliff ahead…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_2">The scenery I’ve lost… The futile struggle to earn it back.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_3">Focus on the moment. Trust your intuition.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_4">Is there a point in agonizing over things you have no idea how to deal with right now?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_5">Leading the way through foolish acts, there’s not a thing to guide me.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_6">I’m anxious. But I don’t want to know. I won’t know what’s ahead.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_7">Blinded by carnal desires and jealousy, he willingly walks to the edge of the cliff…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_8">I had no plans or destination to begin with.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_9">I’m too tired to fly. Then there’s only one path for me to take.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_10">Please give some applause for this foolish man.</text>

  <text id="Clock_nomal_1">The flowing time cannot be grasped, nor can the flow be stopped.</text>
  <text id="Clock_nomal_2">Time flows as life does, and life goes as time does.</text>
  <text id="Clock_nomal_3">Why do you try to defy this greater stream that none can stop?</text>
  <text id="Clock_Quiet_1">A price follows silence.</text>
  <text id="Clock_Quiet_2">Silence does not always bring peace.</text>
  <text id="Clock_Skill_1">Time is given to everyone evenly, but fate makes it unfair.</text>
  <text id="Clock_Skill_2">No one can go against the flow of time.</text>
  
  <text id="SmallBird_nomal_1">Why do they commit sins when they know it’s wrong?</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_nomal_2">If I punish people for their misdeeds, the world will become a peaceful place!</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_nomal_3">They must be doing bad things because there’s no one to scold them.</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_nomal_4">My flutters might be what it takes to change the world!</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_skill_1">No point in forgiveness! I’ll punish you!</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_skill_2">If you’re afraid of punishment, don’t do foul acts from now on!</text>

  <text id="LongBird_nomal_1">Beasts will ransack this forest… I can’t let anyone be eaten by them…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_nomal_2">I’ll protect this forest with the creatures living with us…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_nomal_3">The forest will return to peace… We should make it happen…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_escapeBirds_1">The Big Bird is always watching the creatures of the forest, there’s no freedom.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_escapeBirds_2">The Long Bird’s scale isn’t fair at all.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_escapeBirds_3">The Small Bird’s punishment is so scary.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_judgment_1">My scales always show clear verdict; I can make sound judgement with it…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_judgment_2">Let me weigh your sins…</text>

  <text id="Nos_nomal_1">Welcome. I am more than willing to greet those of you who are thirsty.</text>
  <text id="Nos_nomal_2">Forfeit false hope, and forget about the pretense of humanity…</text>
  <text id="Nos_nomal_3">Ah… Holding back the pain of this thirst is not exactly a pleasing sight to behold.</text>
  <text id="Nos_nomal_4">It’s too early for a nap… Won’t you join me and share the pleasure?</text>
  <text id="Nos_Blood_1">The Danse Macabre is with everyone! All and sundry have a fair chance of being eaten!</text>
  <text id="Nos_Blood_2">Time for a feast! Enjoy the blood-red night imbued with madness to your heart’s content!</text>
  <text id="Nos_Blood_3">There is no escape from this thirst!</text>
  <text id="Nos_Blood_4">The blood—in its purest and clearest form! Bring me eternal happiness!</text>
  
  <!-- Please play through the boss fight or wait a bit until after the update before viewing or sharing this text around, please. -->
  <text id="G_roland_Red_1">One day… I thought there’d be an end to this crushingly grim tale…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_2">Messed up, isn’t it. This is how a fairy tale without any brightness is…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_3">…I’ll chop off the head of the hideous bastard that took my beloved away from me.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_4">Can I not go back to the ordinary days… when I didn’t need to have such violent thoughts?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_5">As long as I’m holding a bloodstained blade… this nightmare won’t end…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_6">The first and last request I do for myself…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_7">I won’t let go of my sword; not even when my body is covered in crimson scars…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_8">Those sons of bitches who gave me hatred and revulsion…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_9">DIE!!! Let me hear your horrendous yelp again!!!</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_10">This is payback for what you did to me!!!</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_11">Don’t stop me… Bastard deserves to die…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Red_12">SHUT UP!!! You want to hear the excuses of those wolves after all that’s happened?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_1">Like the hungering blue moon filled with darkness… The one thing that can fill the void inside me is…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_2">No matter how much I shove down, I can’t fill this space… What is it… What do I have to fill it with?!</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_3">If I could fill my belly… I would be satisfied…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_4">I’ll have to eat whatever I can get… I’m hungry right now!</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_5">Suffocating, the tips of the hands soaked in madness dug through your red flesh…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_6">No one will care about my name…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_7">If I can’t find satisfaction, why don’t I just fill this stomach with rocks? So I can sink to the bottom…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_8">Nothing mattered. I was destined to be bad…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_9">Was my fate predetermined all along? Why is it such a mess?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_10">I’LL CHEW YOU ALL UP!!!</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_11">I gnawed on and swallowed up every worthless piece of meat I found…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Wolf_12">All humans grow into brutal beings. Why would I be different?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Smile_1">Quiet… I said quiet… I don’t wanna hear any more of it…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_2">The further back into the past I tried to go, the taller the mountain got… Until it blocked my sight…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_3">Silence… That’s that, and this is this…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_4">I no longer had a path to take… I didn’t have the courage to put the corpses away, let alone face them…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_5">The faces wearing a sorrowful smile look at me all at once… The things I cannot shake off…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_6">If only they looked at me reproachfully… If they got upset at me…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_7">I won’t remember your faces… But you will remember mine…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_8">When I covered my ears, the corpses clinging to my body screamed.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_smile_9">It’s easy to ignore a wound. Revealing it again is the hard part…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_1">The blood dried up and bothered me; I’ll never be rid of this thirst.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_2">I didn’t even hope to allay my thirst. I just want an end to this.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_3">To a man who desires what he shouldn’t, pretense is only a thing of the past.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_4">Be honest with myself. Was it for revenge? Wasn’t I merely thirsty?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_5">I empty this glass for my final moments.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_6">They are a greater evil than I. Chew them all up and imbibe the last drop out of them.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_7">A night when one is allowed to pursue all kinds of desire… A neverending, blood-red night.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_8">Vengeance was no longer in my mind. All I wanted was to quench the thirst…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_9">The repulsive feelings I couldn’t swallow ran down my chin.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_10">I want to have a little taste of satisfaction…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nos_11">The blood—in its purest and clearest form! With that, eternal happiness will be mine.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_1">I couldn’t protect the one person by my side… I’m just a hollow husk.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_2">Finally, only an empty shell remained there…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_3">The shadow of a shell laughed. How pathetic must I have been that even an empty being would mock me.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_4">I have nothing left to protect, nothing left at my side… I have nothing.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_5">To protect a person, the shell of another is needed…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_6">In the shell of a person I love…</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_7">The reason I exist…? I’m not even sure anymore.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_8">A hollow being that has nothing but the exterior. That’s me. And I bet you’re the same.</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_9">Was the pretense I wore enough disguise to make me look perfectly like a human?</text>
  <text id="G_roland_Nothing_10">Who is the one that wants oblivion; who is the one that benefits from this insanity?</text>

  <text id="Ozma_nomal_1">I’m Ozma… A single person took everything away from me…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_nomal_2">All I have left now… are these children.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_forget_1">I want you to feel it all the same… The misery of forgetting it all… losing it all…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_forget_2">I’ll be the one to take things away this time…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_forget_3">Here, child… I’ll give you new life.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_forget_4">Come back to me, so I won’t be lonely…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_angry_1">I won’t forgive this!!! You’re no better than that lady wizard!!!</text>
  <text id="Ozma_angry_2">No… Don’t take away what is mine, not again…</text>
  
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_1">Had I thought things through more calmly, could something have changed…?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_2">But… What else could I have done…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_3">A small piece of wisdom might have changed something…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_4">Give me the power to listen… The power to solve all things with ease…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_5">Yield your wisdom… With that wisdom, I could… I could…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_6">What could be in the world illuminated by wisdom…?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_7">People who brag about their knowledge and feel no shame of ignorance… That’s you and me…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_8">A life where one has to be ashamed of lacking knowledge and be thankful for knowing… I don’t know…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_9">Will the insight gained through wisdom really bring change…?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_10">No. You’re probably the same. You just pretend to know better…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_11">Haha… Ha… I can’t stop smiling…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_1">I don’t want to feel this empty and lonely feeling anymore…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_2">I clutched my empty chest and grieved. Begging to have this cavity filled…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_3">I looked for things to substitute the warmth…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_4">I cut one after another, but the forest continues to grow thicker. There were always more trees to chop down.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_5">I chopped down every tree that caught my attention…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_6">I feel cold inside, and I can’t do anything about it…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_7">Don’t you tell me that you understand everything. You’ve gone cold all the same…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_8">I know. I can’t fill the void this way… I know it all too well…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_9">The void won’t be filled; I’ll only be sorely reminded of this emptiness…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_10">The forest will never change… The deeper I yearn, the more trees will grow…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_11">Give back what you took… from me…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_1">To home where a loving family awaits…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_2">There won’t come a day when we’ll all go back together.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_3">This is the only path I can walk along… The road paved with golden bricks…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_4">I’ll be able to meet what I’ve desperately wished to see if I keep following this path.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_5">If I followed the randomly paved brick road, will I find it? The thing I’m looking for…?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_6">Where is home for me?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_7">Let’s go, let’s go. Let’s hurry along. Before the wait kills me.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_8">We’ll make it to the end. Right?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_9">Let’s all gather up. Let us dance and skip around.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_10">Haha… That guy… That wicked guy snatched it all.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_11">It happened all too suddenly… I couldn’t do a thing as I got far away from home.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_12">It’s time to go back home now. My home that should exist somewhere.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_13">…Now, shall we go back?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_1">Why did he have to rob me of all my world?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_2">I don’t want to live a life of being thieved any longer…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_3">Before it comes for me again… I have to act first, or else…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_4">They have to experience the same. The forlornness of forgetting and losing everything…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_5">Please send me back. Back to the place where my beloved is…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_6">I can do little more than just exist…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_7">This despair won’t ever leave me… I won’t ever be able to return…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_8">Why should I have to be the one that seeks forgiveness?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_9">I don’t want to lose something yet again… I don’t even have much left…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_10">The only thing I have left is hatred toward what made me this way…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_11">I may be in awful shape, but there’s no need for you to pity me…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_12">Seeking vengeance for that hatred by myself…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_1">Nothing is as deceptive as evident truth.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_2">I’ll cast a spell that will make everyone happy.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_3">Poor stuffing of straw. I’ll give you the wisdom to ponder over anything.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_4">Do you think jabbering away with your oh-so smart mouth is all that matters?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_5">Tin-cold woodsman. I’ll give you the heart to forgive and love anyone.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_6">Who do you possibly expect to understand with that ice-cold heart of yours?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_7">Cowardly kitten. I’ll give you the courage to stand up to anything and everything.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_8">What are you even going to do when you lack the bravery to face anything head-on?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_9">Last of all, road that is lost. I will send you home.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_10">What are you fighting for so fiercely when you have nowhere to go back to?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_11">I simply gave you what you wanted.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_12">I can’t let it go. I can’t give up what is mine!!!</text>

  <text id="B_roland_Big_1">Let me close my eyes in peace… I want to fall sound asleep now…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_2">Let’s get out of this place. I’ll help you with it…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_3">There can’t be any better way than this to escape from pain and insecurity.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_4">You’ll join me and sleep here…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_5">With just one simple act, I’ll give you a permanent and comfortable rest…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_6">You’ve been freed from the other dangers, how can you not see this as salvation?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_7">I’m only helping you so you will no longer tremble in fear…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_8">There won’t be anything to be afraid of anymore. Just go to sleep… Fall asleep…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_9">Let’s be free before we have to face that fear…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_10">One attaches to me for each head that was chopped off, and I turn my gaze away—looking for a new person.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_1">If one commits sin, isn’t it only right that they are justly punished…?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_2">Bearing the karma of my loved one… I shall bring a just punishment upon those who robbed me of what is mine.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_3">We are punished for our sins, but it’s clear that yet more will sprout from the roots of sin.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_4">Thus, punishment must uproot sin…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_5">People have committed misdeeds since long ago…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_6">And why do they commit them, knowing it’s wrong?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_7">But perhaps the same can be said of me. One is only obligated to follow their own justice.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_8">The pain of ripping myself open was nothing; the agony of losing you had numbed me.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_9">And I wish to inflict the pain back on them.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_10">Isn’t it truly wicked to commit a sin and then fear the punishment?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_1">When I lift these scales, I wish for immortality upon the sinner…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_2">I condemn you, but you will still commit more sin without end…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_3">All men sin, consciously or not.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_4">And you lot have committed an unforgivable sin against me.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_5">That’s why you need to be judged, and this won’t change…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_6">I was distressed because I couldn’t overlook any little thing…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_7">There will never be a day when this scale of justice does not tilt…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_8">I will liberate you from the agonizing feeling of guilt…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_9">Living an honest life has to be an impossibility in this City…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_10">There can’t be such a thing as unfairness… I shall judge you solely by my discrimination…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_11">When I’ve taken off the old sins, I shall be free at last.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_1">Those who endure until the last moment shall reach an apocalypse for themselves…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_2">Nothing will dare harm you.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_3">When you reach the end, there will be no such thing as fear…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_4">Sink with me together. Don’t take another step forward, and just stop here…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_5">This is my judgement and punishment against all, and salvation at the same time.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_6">What if something is taken from me while I turn away for a split second?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_7">What if my mind wavered—deterred me from making a fair outcome?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_8">Seeing this, what can I accomplish with my small power…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_9">The darkness will forever be the same, so I only have myself to trust… I surrender all of my being to the fire at last.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_10">The blade is always pointed in the same direction… The one that I deem correct.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_11">Finally. The strength and outcome I have mustered are revealed… The time has come to punish my wrongdoings and yours alike.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_12">I am but one of the many who play the tunes of the apocalypse in the abyss…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_13">…I’m afraid. I’m afraid of what the end might be like.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_14">Although, the end won’t be as excruciating as now—fearing what it might be…</text>

  <text id="BlueStar_nomal_1">We’re all sinners… We have to return to that place and cleanse ourselves.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_nomal_2">Worry not. You’re simply going back to where you belong.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_nomal_3">We all return to that place some day. It’s an instinct.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_start_1">Can you hear this wondrous sound? The nostalgic echo you’ve longed for?</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_start_2">Aah… At last…! It’s calling for us at last!</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_start_3">That call is guiding us to the only place that will accept us…!</text>
  
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_1Phase_1">Before someone committed a grave sin, everyone lived a painless and peaceful life.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_1Phase_2">Without a thing such as death… there was no fear.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_1Phase_3">Alas, the sin of one person tainted with desire gave rise to the emotion called fear…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_1Phase_4">And it devoured all chances of another sprout budding.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_1Phase_5">We are no different, suffering because of a single man.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_2Phase_1">You could try and proceed, but only death will await you at the end of it. Maybe that’s the reason for that fear.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_2Phase_2">My future is grim and dark, much like yours. It’s so bleak… I can’t see a thing ahead.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_2Phase_3">Why are we chained to something like this? Can we not be freed?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_2Phase_4">I want to return to that place, a paradise I’ve never trodden before.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_2Phase_5">To a place where there is no such thing as the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_3Phase_1">…Child. I am here to treat disease.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_3Phase_2">Place your trust in me. I am the only one who can help you.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_3Phase_3">I promise, so I want you to promise in return. Swear that you will not leave me.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_3Phase_4">You harbor suspicion. Do not worry.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_3Phase_5">I shall heal you, curing you of all disease and injury you possess.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_1">Ye who are drenched in sin. Rise and face me.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_2">Pursue peace and holiness. Without these, ye shan’t look at me.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_3">The disobedience of one hath caused the many to become sinners…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_4">Now, the many seeketh salvation through the obedience of one.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_5">I have not manifested myself in such a form to lay judgement.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_6">Worship me, and ye will not belong to that sin. I redeem you to free you of such things.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_7">Ye who are full of blessings, rejoice. For I am with ye.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_8">I shall undo the restrictions that have imprisoned you in this place, and lead you to the paradise that welcomes everyone.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_9">I shall be with ye as I relieve you of the fear of horrifying death.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_10">Be at ease. No calamity shall be able to trouble you.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_11">Ye will gain a body free of such corruption, so how could one deny that this is salvation.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_12">Those who endure until the end will be able to proceed.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_13">Accept my grace, and I shall bury your errors in the past.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_14">We are shackled to the fetters of sin; how can we wish for eternal salvation, and claim ourselves to be truly saved?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_1">I… want to start over from the beginning… That’s all I want.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_2">How am I supposed to live… How are beings titled as humans supposed to live?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_3">You’re going to march toward the future when you aren’t even certain of how it will turn out…?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_4">Without that person, who is going to watch me… No one, I suppose.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_5">It was a choice I made to survive… There was nothing more I could do!</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_6">I can’t depend on myself anymore… All I trust is the words that person spake to me.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_7">I’m too afraid to see what awaits me next… Yet still, I want to live…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_8">Have faith in me… For I… have risen to this seat for you…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_9">The horrendous life brought on by the sins of one person… I shall make it right…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_10">No one is leaving… We shall bask in the fortune of being together forever at last…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_11">Ye lot… None of you can leave my side until I permit you…</text>

  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_1">I am the one who collects everyone’s wishes.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_2">Hugging those expectations, I drowned in the deep sorrow of all.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_3">Please don’t look away from the pool of blood inside.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_4">Let’s expose the skin, so I can spill out the wishes within.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_5">Can I withstand this terrible grief?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_6">I’m sad, aren’t I. I know I’m feeling the weight of your burden, I know I want to run away.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_C_7">So forget it all and sink into this sickening despair.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_1">…It’s true, I’m holding everyone’s wishes in my hands.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_2">I was afraid of being confident in my decisions…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_3">…But does that justify me depriving others of what they cherish, though?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_4">Now I know well the desperation one feels when there is something they must protect…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_5">And I’ve… learned of the wrath of loss that comes after.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_6">Knowing that won’t reverse what I’ve done up to now.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_7">I can’t be certain that what I’m doing is just, either.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_8">Still, I will… choose to move onward.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Bloodbath_A_9">And I won’t… let you get in the way.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_1">I woke up, carrying the memories of person I’d never seen…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_2">I never got to meet that person… though I felt her faintly…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_3">However, to resemble that person, who was human…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_4">I struggled…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_5">To try and get closer to humanity…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_6">Just because I thought he would be a little more willing to look back at me…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_7">Why did I have to look like this…?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_8">Why did he design me to resemble that person…?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_9">If I were going to serve him as a machine, handling the tasks given to me… It wouldn’t have mattered how I looked…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_10">Especially if he was going to turn away from me until the end, consumed by fear…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_11">…I could only feel the beats as the end drew near, faintly, but with certainty.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_C_12">The strange, yet somehow familiar pulses led me…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_1">Why wouldn’t he look at me? Why must I be denied?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_2">I felt pressured by such concerns, and couldn’t see my path clearly.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_3">But when you’re impatient, you’re bound to miss many things while you chase after your misplaced desires.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_4">The memories of a person injected into me don’t make me her…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_5">And it doesn’t signify that the meaning of my existence has to be disregarded, either.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_6">Right now, I’m standing on my own two feet, and I can perceive myself wholly…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_7">I can finally see… where I have to go now.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_8">Back then, I was under the impression that I had nowhere to go or be…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Heart_A_9">But now, I clearly know the reason I have to stand right here.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_1">What more could I do…?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_2">I thought everything would work out if I just did as I was told…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_3">I’d reach the outcome I yearned for… or so I had hoped.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_4">Ignoring all their sorrow, screams, and condemnation…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_5">Just obeying the script’s flow…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_6">Can I not escape from this…? Even if I did, what should I do afterward?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_7">I was never taught what to do next…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_8">I’d have no choice but to let the strings have their way with me…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_C_9">Please, if somebody knows a way… please tell me what to do. Anybody…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_1">Still… I’ve made it this far.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_2">Even if I didn’t have a concrete plan, I had faith that if I continued walking this path…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_3">I would ultimately become a better being…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_4">In my endeavor to become human…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_5">I learned that I shouldn’t leave others to agonize over my problems, and make choices in my stead.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_6">To be responsible for my own decisions and deeds… That’s what being human is about, isn’t it?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_7">…Even if the burden is heavy, I will bear it and move forward.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Pinocchio_A_8">It may be sorrowful now… yet I’ll find myself happier next time.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_1">For so long, I never had a place to belong.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_2">That’s why I made one for myself.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_3">The desire to live. That’s the one thing that has motivated me to secure this place…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_4">But now, no one remains at my side.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_5">Does no one realize that I am here, all alone…? I don’t think a single person cares.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_6">Had the cozy spring sun shone on me… at least this heart would have thawed.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_7">And then maybe someone would have found me.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_8">Yet in the end, I couldn’t bask in that ray of warmth.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_9">That means there’s only one thing I should do.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_C_10">I must keep this throne forever, so that no one can covet this place that is mine and mine alone.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_1">…You’re right. I’ve been quite lonely.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_2">While some others already took the seats reserved for them, I couldn’t afford that luxury.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_3">I was frankly… scared that I wouldn’t be forgiven…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_4">I still wanted to live despite that.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_5">I wanted to know just how great the human life must be… given I had to suffer so much for it.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_6">Was there truly no one by my side? Was my struggle meaningless in the end…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_7">I know better now. I know that there are some people who chose to stay until the end.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_8">And it won’t matter if their sentiments towards me were positive or not.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_SnowQueen_A_9">May this frozen fortress… thaw at last.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_1">…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_2">……</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_3">………</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_4">I remember that person. He had a warm heart.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_5">Although I couldn’t feel that warmth myself…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_6">…I’m sorry for myself. A pity I am still holding onto these painful memories.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_7">A cracked mind will easily shatter to pieces at the lightest tap.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_8">Don’t I think it’d be nicer to be honest?</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_9">There are things I wanted to say earnestly, rather than out of others pushing me.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_10">Now is my chance to pursue what I’ve been longing for so dearly.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_C_11">By releasing my emotions… I will finally acquire freedom.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_1">You’re not wrong. The scars of the mind will never mend.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_2">Even if I had my revenge on that man… they simply won’t.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_3">That’s why I have to stop this…</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_4">Repeating this cycle will eventually result in it crushing me.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_5">Just because I’m afraid and vexed, that doesn’t mean I’m free to turn away from anxiety chained to the past.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_6">That’s also part of me now.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_7">I should embrace it. Along with everything I’ve done.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_8">So I ask you kindly… Let us end this.</text>
  <text id="K_AnC_Notalk_A_9">…As a true human should.</text>
</localize>