<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Malkuth_1">Then there’s only one way to do this! Let’s get ready, everyone!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Malkuth_2">That’s right! It’s too early to think that we’ll lose the battle.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Malkuth_3">It’s good to see that you guys aren’t demotivated. Okay, then… Time to do this.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Malkuth_Die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_1_1">They probably are. Some things about them might have changed a lot, too.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_1_2">We’ve managed to come this far, so what’s a little more challenge?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_1_3">Miss Malkuth! I think we’re ready.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_2_1">I wonder if they’re… stronger than the last time.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_2_2">We stopped them once, and we sure can do it again.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_2_3">You can stand back for a moment if you’re not feeling well.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_3_1">Are those their distorted forms… That’s kinda bizarre…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_3_2">Come on, keep your chin up.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_3_3">I think I’m okay…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_4_1">What the… What is up with those monstrosities?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_4_2">I can’t help but get tense in this situation…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_M_Librarian_4_3">That’s a spooky sight to behold… Is everyone good?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Yesod_1">A solution will most likely exist, even if it is not within our sight at the moment.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Yesod_2">And I presume those two are of the same nature.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Yesod_3">…That is true. The inner conflict would make this task all the more difficult to execute.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Yesod_Die">…I urge you not to panic and concentrate on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_1_1">We have to acquire information through trial and error, just like the old days.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_1_2">There really is a fine line between this, and that power.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_1_3">I don’t agree with their goal, but I can’t fully refute its validity either, ironically.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_2_1">They’re still an enigma…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_2_2">They can wield the power of the Distortion like that…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_2_3">How are they going to give this “freedom”, exactly…?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_3_1">And I thought I’d seen enough Distortions…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_3_2">But they don’t really seem to have lost control, either.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_3_3">We oughta watch out. If we get careless for just a second…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_4_1">Huh, they turned into complete freaks, ey…?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_4_2">They all have a few screws loose…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Y_Librarian_4_3">…Something about this atmosphere doesn’t sit right.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hod_1">…Yeah. We should deal with the Ensemble first.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hod_2">Don’t be too nervous. We need to believe in ourselves.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hod_3">I wonder about that as well… But we have our Light to protect right now.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hod_Die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_1_1">Well… There are pressing matters to handle first, so let’s keep our focus on them.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_1_2">They are not the ones that we received, either…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_1_3">I’ve got no clue. I can’t even imagine what they’ll end up becoming after this.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_2_1">This feels strange. What’ll happen to Lady Angela…?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_2_2">If only we could find a good way to deal with them.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_2_3">If they take the Library’s Light in their hands… Could they become even stronger?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_3_1">Yeah, but then this stuff happened before I could think about that…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_3_2">It’s concerning for sure… It might be inadvisable to just charge in.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_3_3">I can barely recognize their original forms anymore.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_4_1">The Light has been shot up again, hasn’t it…?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_4_2">They look stronger than before… Can we beat them this time?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_H_Librarian_4_3">…Is that the Blue Reverberation?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Netzach_1">You never know how it’ll turn out before you try…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Netzach_2">If you’re ready… we’ll get started.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Netzach_3">Each person has different pursuits and methods, after all…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Netzach_Die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_1_1">I guess starting with the one we know first is a good way to go about it, yeah?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_1_2">…Alright then, Netzach. Should we get to it right away?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_1_3">I think there are better ways to make that come true, though.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_2_1">There’s more of them, too…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_2_2">It’ll be fine as long as we stay calm…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_2_3">A life where I can be myself… I… am sorta curious to see that.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_3_1">We should keep an eye out… and respond to their moves appropriately.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_3_2">Facing unknown threats is always an unsettling experience…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_3_3">I dunno. And I… don’t wanna think about it, really.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_4_1">Netzach. This might be different from the last time…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_4_2">That clown is extremely lively, and… noisy.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_N_Librarian_4_3">What kind of ideal world is this ensemble trying to reach…?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Tiphereth_1">Focus! Let’s ease up a little and get going.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Tiphereth_2">Are you worrying about me? Take care of yourselves first!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Tiphereth_3">Anyway… I hope you all can stay strong until it’s over.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Tiphereth_Die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_1_1">That’s enough complaints. We have a job to do.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_1_2">You ready, Miss Tiphereth?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_1_3">If we agreed with them, fights like this wouldn’t have happened…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_2_1">I hope this is actually the last battle against them…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_2_2">We shouldn’t be too hasty, or we might mess it up.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_2_3">That’s what we’re trying to stop here.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_3_1">Duly noted… Our own carelessness should be the last thing to get us.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_3_2">There’s a familiar face…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_3_3">It’s gonna be a mess out there. The whole place might be razed to the ground.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_4_1">Please be careful, everyone.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_4_2">…They look grotesque indeed.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_T_Librarian_4_3">If they were to snatch the Light…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Gebura_1">There may be similarities between our aim and theirs, but the destination is ultimately different.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Gebura_2">Alright… Ready yourselves. It’s about to begin.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Gebura_3">Let’s tie up all these loose ends.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Gebura_Die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_1_1">That might not be “freedom” as we know it.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_1_2">…Miss Gebura. Shall we get started?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_1_3">Of course. It’s time to finish this…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_2_1">What are they trying to gain by changing like that… Freedom?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_2_2">We’ve got to tense up and prepare for fierce resistance.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_2_3">…You all up for this?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_3_1">They certainly don’t seem human…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_3_2">Both sides are fighting to achieve their own goals.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_3_3">Seems so. It’s almost over… Just a bit more, and we’re there…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_4_1">They’re huge, and somewhat… gross, maybe?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_4_2">I don’t think we can dispose of them easily…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_G_Librarian_4_3">Could they be… the last?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Chessed_1">I think it might be a good idea to handle what’s in front of us first~</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Chessed_2">Maybe there’s no need to try and force yourself to understand it?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Chessed_3">Mmhmm~ No problems so far. Well then, shall we… begin the reception~?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Chessed_Die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_1_1">Well… That’s not our biggest concern right now.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_1_2">It might be confusing… I can’t say for sure yet.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_1_3">Are you alright, Chesed, sir?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_2_1">Not everyone can accept a single idea.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_2_2">We wish for strings of some kind to lead us, consciously or not.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_2_3">…The atmosphere is way too intimidating.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_3_1">It can’t be helped, can it? Their ideals only scare me.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_3_2">…Well, doesn’t sound like it’ll feel all that good.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_3_3">This is the final stretch… We just need to stay focused a bit longer.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_4_1">I don’t think I can vibe with the kind of freedom they want…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_4_2">Cutting off the strings… How would that feel?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_C_Librarian_4_3">…I think we can make it.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Binah_1">Indeed. …It would seem that we are fully prepared.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Binah_2">I advise you to reflect on yourself before you gaze into the worlds of others.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Binah_3">Such intrigue is why one cannot stop thinking.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Binah_Die">…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_1_1">We should believe in that we can, at least.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_1_2">I guess it’s because their definition of freedom is not the same as ours?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_1_3">It’s not like I can’t see where they’re coming from… This feels weird.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_2_1">One or many… We’ll be able to manage.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_2_2">I gotta say, I don’t get the point of their way for bringing freedom.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_2_3">After all, fear is a natural response to something that’s not oneself.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_3_1">Seriously. Now they’ve ganged up…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_3_2">Maybe? I guess it counts in a broad sense.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_3_3">Understanding difference is the hard part.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_4_1">Just one of them was irksome enough…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_4_2">Can their goal truly be called freedom?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_B_Librarian_4_3">They lived a life under repression, I heard…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hokma_1">Moreover, it is up to the individual whether they sympathize or not.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hokma_2">I am of the thought that no methodology can be wholeheartedly affirmed. Even ours would have oppositions…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hokma_3">…Well then, ready yourselves.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Hokma_Die">…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_1_1">I suppose it’s not easy to sympathize with someone else’s opinions…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_1_2">All the more reason for us to stop them.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_1_3">I’d hate to repeat it another time…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_2_1">There wouldn’t be any joy to be found in a monotonous stream, though.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_2_2">I’m somewhat curious… Not that I want to see it for myself.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_2_3">That appears to be the case. We should give this a proper ending.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_3_1">Will people really be happy if they simply follow the flow without resistance?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_3_2">The things that felt unjust would be justified…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_3_3">Yeah… This is truly it, huh.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_4_1">A life of floating down wherever the current takes you…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_4_2">If the world changed as they want… It would be nothing short of a disaster.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_Ho_Librarian_4_3">Hokma, sir. It looks like the closure is nigh.</text>
</localize>