<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_1">I could put up with it all just for this moment…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_2">I’ve come this far so I can make her suffer the same… No, to bring her even more pain than what I’ve suffered.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_3">I don’t exactly believe there’s happiness waiting for me at the end of this…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_4">There’d only be empty regret. I’d get nothing out of it.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_5">But that’s still better than suffocating under these emotions that couldn’t be let out, isn’t it?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_6">I just want to be able to breathe for a second.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_7">You’ve got your causes to fight for. Don’t hold back.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_8">Few things could be more agonizing and detestable than finding a common ground between each other’s goals.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_9">Angela. Your pain and loss will be much greater than mine…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_1_10">…Alright. Let’s get started.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_1">The past isn’t all that different from now… Nothing ever changes… The same kinds of tragedies happen time and time again…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_2">Everyone knows that it’s wrong… But they can’t stop it from repeating…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_3">How many people do you think are sacrificed for the convenience and happiness of others…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_4">The City’s prosperity is fueled by the lives of others… And its people stick their heads below the parapet and carry on…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_5">There’s no other way to survive in this damned place…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_6">We all know that it’s pointless to reflect on ourselves and think things over…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_7">You wouldn’t want to care… You’d want to turn a blind eye!</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_8">Because that’s none of your business… Right. That’s none of your business.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_9">Because your life would be a bit more comfortable if you just closed your eyes and turned away…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_10">They give no ear to the pain of other people… Taking care of themselves is already hard enough…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_11">I hate this City for forcing us to be like this…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_12">And I’m horrified and disgusted at myself for partaking in its filthy business…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_13">But—that’s that, and this is this…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_14">I can’t just sit and watch as my happiness goes down the drain…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_2_15">My life is far from a clean one, but still… I hadn’t done anything to earn anyone’s grudge…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_1">What I cannot do is own her heart.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_2">Instead, my graceful love stole my heart and left me with lone hardship.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_3">I can’t help but love the pain which fills the void of solitude.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_4">Because I could look ahead thanks to you.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_5">But now, the wonderful scenery we used to watch together lay behind me…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_6">In this instant, I look back again. My eyes fixated on the most painful yet beautiful moments.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_7">Those moments I can only view from afar, as I can’t dare approach them.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_8">As I cleared the filth obstructing my view, it piled up on the path to the way forward…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_9">I don’t think I can face the growing mountain in front of me squarely.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_10">If I tried to confront it…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_11">I might be buried under mounds of resentment and suffering from others.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_12">I’m not sad about it, though. I don’t think it’s a shame that I can’t move on.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_13">To leave you behind in the past and move forward alone would be my greatest pain.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_14">I had only one option, then. To be able to gaze at paradise forever…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_3_15">I should move all which blocks that sight out of the way.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_1">If I beheaded my nightmare, I might feel good for a moment.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_2">I had been bearing with this shit until now to experience this small victory…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_3">If I were to gouge out this pain, would I be able to accept that it’s over?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_4">If I neglected this choice I’ve been given, wouldn’t it… find a way to me in some other form eventually?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_5">I thought it’d all be over once I could accomplish this dream of vengeance.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_6">I had a reason I couldn’t give up… I told myself that this was for me…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_7">That it’s only fair for me to destroy this place for taking the one I cherished away.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_8">Even if no one understood me… At least I would be able to understand myself.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_9">Deeper into the darkest depths. Fate made my heart cruel.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_10">The paradise I only got to step in once… What did I do for it to be stolen from me so ruthlessly?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_11">Time stood still for me ever since that day. All I can see now is the life of the past, shrouded in darkness.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_12">But if I forgave everything…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_13">If I decided to live down my past now, I felt I might have nowhere to stand.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_14">And I felt I might have to let go of all these precious memories of it.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_4_15">That’s what really scares me, Angelica.</text>
</localize>