<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="Bloodbath_roland_start">Angela’s right, this place really is bizarre. There are creepy-looking blood clots all over the place, too…</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_roland_die">I didn’t expect to die to some weird monster…</text>
	<text id="Bloodbath_roland_kill">Guess I should be thankful that the monster was weaker than it used to be… That was close.</text>
	<text id="Heart_roland_start">That thing can give power? Huh… Does it feel like having two hearts or something?</text>
	<text id="Heart_roland_die">I didn’t expect to die to some weird monster…</text>
	<text id="Heart_roland_kill">That ended pretty quickly for a fight against weird creatures, huh?</text>
	<text id="Heart_librarian_start">My body would be filled with energy whenever I got this thing’s help.</text>
	<text id="Heart_librarian_kill">That was alright. Except for the nauseating feeling I’m getting from all this blood around here…</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_malkuth_start">It’s grasping onto that charred matchstick, like that’s its only hope…</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_malkuth_die">Maybe I was too overwhelmed with enthusiasm…?</text>
	<text id="ScorchedGirl_malkuth_kill">It turned to ash in the end… Poor thing.</text>
	<text id="Teady_malkuth_start">Right, hugging was its favorite thing, wasn’t it? It feels refreshing to see you again!</text>
	<text id="Teady_malkuth_die">Maybe I was too overwhelmed with enthusiasm…?</text>
	<text id="Teady_malkuth_kill">It’s what I must do… But I feel a little sorry to see how tattered the teddy bear got.</text>
	<text id="Teady_librarian_start">That thing loved to play with people.</text>
	<text id="Teady_librarian_kill">Thinking about the people who got killed by that thing… I can’t say I feel sorry for it.</text>
	<text id="Murder_yesod_start">…I did not want to face it again.</text>
	<text id="Murder_yesod_die">It’s entirely the fault of my carelessness that I’ve met such a fate.</text>
	<text id="Murder_yesod_kill">It was fettered by empty anger and regret until the very last moment.</text>
	<text id="Helper_yesod_start">This should not be difficult as long as we have clear information on that machine.</text>
	<text id="Helper_yesod_die">It’s entirely the fault of my carelessness that I’ve met such a fate.</text>
	<text id="Helper_yesod_kill">I am still unsure if it was the result of a mechanical malfunction or someone’s malice.</text>
	<text id="Helper_librarian_start">Oh, I know that little guy. It would spin around like crazy before flopping on the floor.</text>
	<text id="Helper_librarian_kill">It does look round and cute, to be honest. It was actually pretty popular among us.</text>
  <text id="Shy_hod_start">The kid still hides behind masks… I gotta be considerate of its mood.</text>
  <text id="Shy_hod_die">My body feels numb, what do I do…</text>
  <text id="Shy_hod_kill">I managed to handle it alone, thankfully.</text>
  <text id="Redshoes_hod_start">Those who saw the shoes would chop off each other’s ankles to wear them, blinded with desire…</text>
  <text id="Redshoes_hod_die">My body feels numb, what do I do…</text>
  <text id="Redshoes_hod_kill">It was risky, but I can handle this much.</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_librarian_start">The damned shoes got redder with people’s blood.</text>
	<text id="Redshoes_librarian_kill">I almost got charmed for a moment there. I was so close to losing my mind.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_netzach_start">The echoes coming from somewhere… I still can’t forget the ringing.</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_netzach_die">Results aside, guess I can sleep tight now…</text>
	<text id="Spacepiece_netzach_kill">…Don’t really feel like trying to understand them, though.</text>
	<text id="Kid_netzach_start">It seems to be using a more vicious method now, but… Guess it still values its friends.</text>
	<text id="Kid_netzach_die">Results aside, guess I can sleep tight now…</text>
	<text id="Kid_netzach_kill">Not sure if that’s cherishing its friends, or just being desperate since there’s no one left to keep company…</text>
	<text id="Kid_librarian_start">That kid always ignored me since I wasn’t in charge of it…</text>
	<text id="Kid_librarian_kill">No one will be friends with that thing…</text>
  
  <text id="Fairy_malkuth_start">That one used to keep its food fresh by “caring” for them!</text>
  <text id="Fairy_malkuth_die">Maybe I was too overwhelmed with enthusiasm…?</text>
  <text id="Fairy_malkuth_kill">It’s eating its own minions to satiate its hunger…</text>
  <text id="Fairy_librarian1_start">You still thought it was doing that for our benefit?</text>
  <text id="Fairy_librarian1_kill">Yep, it still eats its prey while it’s fresh.</text>
  <text id="Fairy_librarian2_start">It’s gotten skinny now… It used to follow me around and care for me.</text>
  <text id="Fairy_librarian2_kill">I would’ve been eaten like that if I let my guard down…</text>
  <text id="Spider_hod_start">It was merciless, but it still loved its children.</text>
  <text id="Spider_hod_die">My body feels numb, what do I do…</text>
  <text id="Spider_hod_kill">I don’t feel so happy about this, it feels like I just ruined a family…</text>
  <text id="Spider_librarian1_start">Yeah, nasty. It never even comes down unless someone hurts its babies.</text>
  <text id="Spider_librarian1_kill">Don’t bother. It could’ve been us hanging up there.</text>
  <text id="Spider_librarian2_start">I never really noticed it since I had to be careful not to step on its offspring, but man, it looks gross.</text>
  <text id="Spider_librarian2_kill">…Thinking about those cocoons still gives me goosebumps.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_netzach_start">It’s not as violent as others, and I heard it can give unimaginable happiness, too.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_netzach_die">Hah… Hahah. This wasn’t the kind of happiness I was hoping to feel.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_netzach_kill">I guess being frenzied with happiness doesn’t always give rise to positive feelings.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian1_start">There was nothing ecstatic about seeing a line of headless corpses, though.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian1_die">My head is just too small to contain all this joy… Set me free!</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian1_kill">This is bringing back horrible memories… It wasn’t pleasant for me at all.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian2_start">Some employees would wait for their turn to visit that thing’s containment all day.</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian2_die">Give me more… I want more satisfaction…</text>
  <text id="Porccubus_librarian2_kill">I don’t ever wanna deal with something like that again…</text>

  <text id="Singingmachine_yesod_start">Stay sharp, everyone. Do not let its music allure you.</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_yesod_die">It’s entirely the fault of my carelessness that I’ve met such a fate.</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_yesod_kill">I don’t get how anyone can be so desperate to hear that performance…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_librarian1_start">Just thinking about the employees who were charmed by that song… Gives me the heebie-jeebies.</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_librarian1_kill">What’s so good about it, anyway? It only makes me feel sick…</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_librarian2_start">Yeah. They’d even throw people into it just to hear the music.</text>
  <text id="Singingmachine_librarian2_kill">They’re just nuts…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_roland_start">I think I read about it somewhere… A wooden puppet with a long nose…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_roland_die">I didn’t expect to die to some weird monster…</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_roland_kill">It must tell lies in order to become a human… Leaves a bitter taste.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_librarian1_start">Pinocchio. It was a children’s tale about a kid whose nose grew long after telling a lie, I think?</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_librarian1_kill">A shame it never got to be human.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_librarian2_start">That creaking wooden noise it makes… That’s icky.</text>
  <text id="Pinocchio_librarian2_kill">Is that thing mimicking us? …That’s kind of creepy.</text>

  <text id="Queenofhatred_Tiphereth_start">We were fooled by that cute appearance and left ourselves wide open for a hard blow.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_Tiphereth_die">She already… read my moves…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_Tiphereth_kill">She’s still the same. Well, at least her love for justice is.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_librarian1_start">Wasn’t it supposed to be a magical girl? She’s a total mess…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_librarian1_kill">Never trying out her version of peace again…</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_librarian2_start">She’d often come out to aid us, but she was more trouble than help.</text>
  <text id="Queenofhatred_librarian2_kill">She has her own standards for what makes a world “peaceful”, huh…</text>

  <text id="KnightOfDespair_Tiphereth_start">A knight whose pride turned into despair…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_Tiphereth_die">She already… read my moves…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_Tiphereth_kill">Stabbing swords into herself… …It’s a bit pitiful, I’ll say that.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian1_start">Mhm. She fell to despair after realizing that she couldn’t uphold what she vowed to protect.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian1_kill">I’m sure it wasn’t her fault, but she met a sad ending.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian2_start">Her blessing was pretty sweet to have.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian2_kill">Endless despair caused by the failure to protect… Huh.</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian3_start">W-what the. Is that person alright…? She looks terrifying…</text>
  <text id="KnightOfDespair_librarian3_kill">…Sent chills down my spine…</text>

  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_malkuth_start">Watch out! Let’s just focus on saving Angela.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_malkuth_die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_librarian1_start">Whoa, what happened to her to get in a mess like this?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_librarian2_start">She’s like a different being altogether… Is it really possible to save her?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_librarian3_start">What else can we do? We’ve got to trust Malkuth and do it her way.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_ScorchedGirl_librarian4_start">Alright… Let’s give it a shot. Y’all ready?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_malkuth_start">Remember the basics, everyone? Let’s do this with no hesitation!</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_malkuth_die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_librarian1_start">This time… Looks like that teddy bear.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_librarian2_start">It was craving for affection.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_librarian3_start">I can’t believe that Lady Angela is taking… a form like that.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Teddy_librarian4_start">I dunno what’s going on, either… But let’s stay sharp.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_malkuth_start">It’s alright! Angela will go back to normal if we unwind her step by step.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_malkuth_die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_librarian1_start">H-hold on. We aren’t gonna get bitten like back then, right?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_librarian2_start">That’s scary… It creeps me out to think that she’ll eat everything up…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_librarian3_start">Okay… She’ll be back to normal if we keep this up?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_Fairy_librarian4_start">In any case… I guess so?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_malkuth_start">We need to take a bolder approach.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_malkuth_die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_librarian1_start">Fight after fight… I’m starting to get tired.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_librarian2_start">Just how much has she had pent-up…?</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_librarian3_start">Let’s hold out just a bit longer.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_QueenBee_librarian4_start">There must’ve been some serious circumstances for her that we didn’t know…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_malkuth_start">I think we’re getting close to the end. Hang in there, everyone!</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_malkuth_die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_librarian1_start">Not sure if I can take any more of this… Welp, I should at least try.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_librarian2_start">We’d often trip on the vines that thing planted in the corridors.</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_librarian3_start">It’s withered and lifeless; it doesn’t look like a plant anymore…</text>
  <text id="M_Angela_SnowWhite_librarian4_start">…Withered, huh. Maybe it’s supposed to show the distress she’s gone through?</text>
  
  <text id="QueenBee_Malkuth_start">Be careful not to inhale the spores!</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_Malkuth_die">Maybe I was too overwhelmed with enthusiasm…?</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_Malkuth_kill">We had no choice but to break it down…</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian1_start">It seems she wants more and more drones to work for her.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian1_kill">Sorry about ruining your kingdom… It was a do or die situation.</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian2_start">If those teeth and that jaw crushed me…</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian2_kill">Sorry, didn’t really feel like becoming a busy bee…</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian3_start">What do you mean by ‘spores’, Miss Malkuth?</text>
  <text id="QueenBee_librarian3_kill">…My neck feels kinda itchy.</text>
  
  <text id="RedMercenary_Gebura_start">…Watch out. The Wolf is the sole reason for the Red Hood to exist, in a way.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_Gebura_kill">She was still devoted to her one duty.</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_librarian1_start">Dude, that’s tense… What’s up with these two, anyway?</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_librarian1_kill">That was a nasty crossfire we were caught in…</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_librarian2_start">This is why… We had to stop the two from facing each other at all cost…</text>
  <text id="RedMercenary_librarian2_kill">Feels weaker than before… But still scary nonetheless.</text>
  
  <text id="Wisdom_Chesed_start">You’re telling me, friend~ Surely, wisdom can’t be everything in life.</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_Chesed_kill">…Such a shame~ The wisdom it took didn’t fully belong to it, after all.</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_librarian1_start">It might have been nicer if it could accept itself as it is.</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_librarian1_kill">That’s not how you get smarter, buddy…</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_librarian2_start">Too bad it didn’t know better. So many poor employees died to its rake.</text>
  <text id="Wisdom_librarian2_kill">I guess it wouldn’t have become a wise person even with all the knowledge.</text>

  <text id="Woodsman_Chesed_start">The fellow’s chest is still hollow, I see~</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_Chesed_kill">Really makes you wonder what brought this hunk of steel to life.</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian1_start">…Yeah. I guess it still craves a warm heart to fill that void, right?</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian1_kill">Like with most Abnormalities… the last moment is always a sad sight.</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian2_start">Hey, by the way… I remember you being a pretty warm-hearted person.</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian2_kill">Gotta say, it doesn’t feel all that good to take away its… precious thing.</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian3_start">Seonbae… Don’t make grim jokes like that and just focus on the fight, please…</text>
  <text id="Woodsman_librarian3_kill">I dunno about you guys, but I don’t really feel sympathy for that thing…</text>

	<text id="Butterflies_yesod_start">Stay alert. It won’t hesitate to exploit your vulnerability.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_yesod_die">It’s entirely the fault of my carelessness that I’ve met such a fate.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_yesod_kill">…A peaceful death… Our work is done, so let us return.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian1_start">Those butterflies are so cold to the touch, it gives me goosebumps.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian1_kill">This frees our last librarian, right? Shall we give them a warm welcome?</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian2_start">Many of my coworkers had lain down in that coffin, yeah.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian2_kill">Still feels chilly… That left a bitter taste. Let’s head back now.</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian3_start">The swarm of butterflies sent a chill down my spine when it went past me…</text>
	<text id="Butterflies_librarian3_kill">I wonder if it’s comfy inside that coffin…</text>
  
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_yesod_start">It will be fine if we can manage to turn her back. Be prepared.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_yesod_die">…I urge you not to panic and focus on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_librarian1_start">You’re worrying too much. Take some deep breaths first.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_librarian2_start">I heard a similar situation happened before, so I’m sure we can overcome it the same.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_librarian3_start">Is she okay…? What if she doesn’t change back…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Murder_librarian4_start">Hahaa… This is freaky. I gotta be wide awake in times like these.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_yesod_start">Is everyone alright? Let me know if your body is having issues.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_yesod_die">…I urge you not to panic and focus on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_librarian1_start">You know, that weird machine that would spin like crazy and freeze on its own.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_librarian2_start">No problem on my end. By the way, that looks familiar…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_librarian3_start">So she’ll keep changing her form like that… I’m starting to get the pattern.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Helper_librarian4_start">I think I’m fine so far. Still, we’d better watch out.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_yesod_start">…I hope she comes back to her senses as quickly as possible so we can have some conversation on the matter.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_yesod_die">…I urge you not to panic and focus on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_librarian1_start">This might be an opportunity to understand her issues together.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_librarian2_start">It’s natural to feel lost, even we can experience it sometimes. It’s not a simple matter…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_librarian3_start">Not that we’re so much better at having a discerning eye…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Sing_librarian4_start">All we can do is help her face it rather than avoid it.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_yesod_start">I don’t believe there is right and wrong in this matter, it’s ultimately of how one accepts it.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_yesod_die">…I urge you not to panic and focus on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_librarian1_start">Well, we should concentrate on the battle for now.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_librarian2_start">The extent of understanding and forgiveness one can show is different for each person, after all.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_librarian3_start">Still, not everyone is going to show understanding for all the things she did.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Butterflies_librarian4_start">Maybe Angela had no choice…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_yesod_start">…We seem to have reached the end of it. Don’t loosen your grip just yet, everyone.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_yesod_die">…I urge you not to panic and focus on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_librarian1_start">The unstoppable bullet got a lot of my coworkers killed, too.</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_librarian2_start">I still remember that. The bullet flying in a precise, straight line…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_librarian3_start">I guess so… Let’s stay focused until the end…</text>
	<text id="Y_Angela_Der_librarian4_start">…It’s getting tougher to endure hits. Seems there’s only a little bit left to push through, yeah?</text>

  <text id="Wolf_Gebura_start">Heads up, it’s not as weak as it seems right now.</text>
  <text id="Wolf_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="Wolf_Gebura_kill">A being that was meant to be the bad guy… Aight, let’s head back now.</text>
  <text id="Wolf_librarian1_start">This guy looks pretty docile? Maybe that scary wolf was just Red Hood’s delusion.</text>
  <text id="Wolf_librarian1_kill">…It was a pretty pitiful thing, overall.</text>
  <text id="Wolf_librarian2_start">Huh, so you never got to see its other side ‘cause you were a new recruit? Let me tell you how ferocious it looked.</text>
  <text id="Wolf_librarian2_kill">Not so pitiful to me. He was destined to be bad, after all.</text>
  
  <text id="GreedKing_Tiphereth_start">Watch out. It’s reckless to step in her way without any preparation.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_Tiphereth_die">She already… read my moves…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_Tiphereth_kill">…It’s all the same. She was a magical girl no more.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian1_start">The gilded splendor is the same as before…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian1_kill">Well… It doesn’t make sense to wish for the happiness of others without your own.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian2_start">Definitely. I remember running for my life…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian2_kill">The hardened avarice won’t ever change, I suppose…</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian3_start">Whenever I saw it crawling from the other side of the corridor… It was terrifying.</text>
  <text id="GreedKing_librarian3_kill">How can something like greed be so dazzling…</text>

  <text id="Laetitia_Hod_start">I’m sorry for the kid, but… Maybe that could work out?</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_Hod_die">My body feels numb, what do I do…</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_Hod_kill">I’m feeling kind of guilty…</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian1_start">Hear me out; what if we used her hospitality to friends to our advantage…</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian1_kill">Friend, huh… Even that monster can be a friend to someone.</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian2_start">…That’s not the kind of gift you’d want, yeah?</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian2_kill">Doesn’t feel good to be taking this little fella away from her…</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian3_start">As much as it’s nice to care for your friend…</text>
  <text id="Laetitia_librarian3_kill">Innocence really can be the scariest thing… That was outright creepy.</text>
  
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_Hod_start">Let’s get ready. Don’t wear yourselves out, okay?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_Hod_die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_librarian1_start">No need to worry guys. We just need to trust Hod and follow her.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_librarian2_start">…This is the kind of stuff I’d see in a containment unit.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_librarian3_start">This can’t be real… What are we supposed to do…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_BlackSwan_librarian4_start">A-Are you saying that’s… what Miss Angela turned into…?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_Hod_start">I guess we can’t fully understand each other’s stories.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_Hod_die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_librarian1_start">That’s why we can’t be too hasty to sympathize with her.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_librarian2_start">You tell me. I’m not one to talk about what I never experienced.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_librarian3_start">I gotta wonder how lonely it must feel to be unable to build relationships, no matter what you do.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Laetitia_librarian4_start">…Such a cruel role she had to fill.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_Hod_start">…Okay. We’ve got to do what we must do right now.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_Hod_die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_librarian1_start">That’s right. There wasn’t a lot you could do about the situation.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_librarian2_start">Hod… Please don’t get too concerned over this.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_librarian3_start">True. …It’s freaky for sure. And I still don’t get what’s going on.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Bug_librarian4_start">Miss Angela is becoming even creepier…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_Hod_start">She thinks she has nothing for herself… I’m sure of it.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_Hod_die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_librarian1_start">Could it be about that… “perfect book” she was looking for?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_librarian2_start">Maybe it’s her own happiness…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_librarian3_start">Not sure what she’s desiring, though.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Red_librarian4_start">Desire and obsession soaked in blood…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_Hod_start">I think we’re almost done… Hang on tight.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_Hod_die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_librarian1_start">Well, anyway… We have a job to finish.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_librarian2_start">But… There’s no way a home earned this way could be comforting.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_librarian3_start">Was she only looking for a place to rest?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_Shy_librarian4_start">She could look that horrendous…?</text>

  <text id="Alriune_netzach_start">Maybe… We’ll need something that can understand that thing.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_netzach_die">Results aside, guess I can sleep tight now…</text>
  <text id="Alriune_netzach_kill">…The aroma won’t go away.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian1_start">That’s awful… Where’s that “deep forest” supposed to be?</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian1_kill">I get this burning smell inside my mouth.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian2_start">…Its weapon used to give off the same smell, too.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian2_kill">It certainly looked fancy…</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian3_start">Ugh… The aroma is as strong as ever.</text>
  <text id="Alriune_librarian3_kill">It was a beautiful scenery alright… But it wasn’t pleasing to look at.</text>
  
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_netzach_start">…One thing is for sure: We can save her.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_librarian1_start">What can we do? We gotta believe…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_librarian2_start">Netzach… Tell me there’s a way out of this…?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_librarian3_start">I think I heard of that…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_1_librarian4_start">Is something about to happen again…?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_netzach_start">Your own safety comes first… Tell me if you’re too exhausted for this.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_librarian1_start">We’re the only people who can do something about her here.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_librarian2_start">Looks like we’re caught in the middle of complicated matters…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_librarian3_start">Don’t be so down, will you? We have to give it a shot.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Spacepiece_librarian4_start">This isn’t normal… Can we get to the end of this…?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_netzach_start">Which means it’s getting more dangerous, too…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_librarian1_start">…Is it just me, or are things getting worse?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_librarian2_start">I guess borrowing power from them isn’t always a good thing…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_librarian3_start">It’s… possible to be possessed that way?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Kid_librarian4_start">Together forever, huh… She’s saying the same things he did.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_netzach_start">…You don’t have to try too hard to understand.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_librarian1_start">How are we gonna understand each other? It’s just unfair that she won’t even talk it out.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_librarian2_start">We can worry about that later.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_librarian3_start">I don’t get it. Why did she have to go so far…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Porccubus_librarian4_start">If she wanted to live so desperately, she should get how we feel…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_netzach_start">It’s nearly over. Just a bit more…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_librarian1_start">I’m sorry to push you guys, but let’s buck up till it’s over.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_librarian2_start">Please, we might get royally screwed if any of us leave the battle…</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_librarian3_start">You okay? Wanna step back for a bit?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Alriune_librarian4_start">…Huff, I’m not feeling very well.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_netzach_start">Let’s end this here and now so we don’t have to go back twice.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_netzach_die">…Sorry I couldn’t help much.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_librarian1_start">We didn’t do something wrong, did we?</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_librarian2_start">That form… looks like we’re her audience.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_librarian3_start">…Still as freaky as the first time.</text>
  <text id="N_Angeala_Orchestra_2_librarian4_start">What? …Why are we back here?</text>

  <text id="Snow_Roland_start">Well, damn… Everything froze over?</text>
  <text id="Snow_Roland_die">…This snowstorm is pretty chilly.</text>
  <text id="Snow_Roland_SaveLibrarian">Hey, you awake now?</text>
  <text id="Snow_Roland_kill">Whew… The chill still hasn’t gone away.</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian1_start">…Ah, I’m still feeling dizzy… but it’s nothing too bad.</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian1_SaveLibrarian">It shattered… Hey, come to your senses now.</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian1_kill">This palace hasn’t changed much from before.</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian2_start">Mmh… …Oh, I’m good now.</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian2_SaveLibrarian">We did it…! Can you move?</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian2_kill">Looks like spring is coming…</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian3_start">I’m alright for the most part… Thanks for saving me!</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian3_SaveLibrarian">I know you must be shocked, but take your time. And don’t try to get up too quickly…!</text>
  <text id="Snow_librarian3_kill">It seemed as if it would last forever… Though it melted away, in the end.</text>

  <text id="BigBird_librarian1_start">The most dangerous beast in the forest is the one we’re facing right now…</text>
  <text id="BigBird_librarian1_kill">I appreciate how the birdie wants to save us from the “beast”, but I’m really fine without its help…</text>
  <text id="BigBird_librarian2_start">I remember. We had to put that bird to sleep before we could work with it.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_librarian2_kill">…Did we kill it? Is it over?</text>
  <text id="BigBird_librarian3_start">Anyway… Lady Binah isn’t here to help us, so we should do this on our own.</text>
  <text id="BigBird_librarian3_kill">Thank goodness we could handle it…</text>

  <text id="Heaven_librarian1_start">…We shouldn’t look away, huh.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_librarian1_kill">Sigh… It looks as horrid as ever.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_librarian2_start">We’d better dispose of it quickly…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_librarian2_kill">Hokma, and everyone else… Are you alright?</text>
  <text id="Heaven_librarian3_start">We can’t let that thing multiply anymore…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_librarian3_kill">I’m not exactly tired… But I’m mentally worn out…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_Hokma_start">If you are prepared… then let us begin.</text>
  <text id="Heaven_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="Heaven_Hokma_kill">…Victory is within our reach. I urge you all to keep it up.</text>

  <text id="SmilingMountain_Gebura_start">We should take it down as quickly as possible.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_Gebura_kill">All that’s left in the end is a pile of dead bodies.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian1_start">…Ugh, this place reeks of filth.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian1_kill">Gross… It was just a big lump after all.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian2_start">It’ll be hell to deal with as it grows bigger…</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian2_kill">…What is making that thing smile like that.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian3_start">You heard Ms. Gebura. Let’s be fast.</text>
  <text id="SmilingMountain_librarian3_kill">Chilly… I’m still disgusted by it.</text>

  <text id="Waygohome_Chesed_start">It might feel like we’re not in our home anymore,
but let’s keep calm and get started~</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_Chesed_kill">Maybe it’s their appearance… My heart is aching~</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian1_start">…I don’t think I’ve ever seen them before?</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian1_kill">We sure would love to go back to our homes if we could.</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian2_start">Don’t tell me, are they related to the nightmarish duo from before?</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian2_kill">It would’ve been a real pain in the ass if they were in our facility.</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian3_start">I’m stumped on how we’re supposed to suppress them…</text>
  <text id="Waygohome_librarian3_kill">We’ve been seeing lots of new things here.</text>

  <text id="Servant_Tiphereth_start">We might be able to handle this if we figure out why she was consumed with wrath.</text>
  <text id="Servant_Tiphereth_die">She already… read my moves…</text>
  <text id="Servant_Tiphereth_kill">Upholding balance, huh…</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian1_start">So… We’re supposed to kill those wooden puppets?</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian1_kill">Yeesh… They’re all nuts…</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian2_start">She seems to be looking for something…</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian2_kill">Justice… Certainly reminds me of them.</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian3_start">What’s this now? …I’m seeing a bunch of wood dolls.</text>
  <text id="Servant_librarian3_kill">What caused her to be so furious, I wonder…</text>
  <text id="Servant_Wrath_win">We were… We were true friends. Right?</text>
  
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_Tiphereth_start">We don’t know everything about Roland, and we might not understand him fully… But we’ve still got to face him head on.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_Tiphereth_die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_librarian1_start">We’d do something, but there’s too little we know…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_librarian2_start">The power wasn’t just affecting Lady Angela?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_librarian3_start">Roland turned into that…?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Queenofhatred_librarian4_start">What? …Well this is new, alright.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_Tiphereth_start">It must feel hopeless for sure, more than words could describe…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_Tiphereth_die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_librarian1_start">And that poison is about to hurt us now.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_librarian2_start">Even if the fault lies on yourself, being ridden with too much guilt will eat away at you like poison.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_librarian3_start">I’ll never get it completely, since I haven’t experienced it myself.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_KnightOfDespair_librarian4_start">…I wonder how it feels to lose the very thing you wanted to protect.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_Tiphereth_start">The sadness of one’s pleasure being taken away will be the same, however big or small it may be.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_Tiphereth_die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_librarian1_start">Don’t you know how big of a bliss it is to live a peaceful life in this City?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_librarian2_start">As they say, being denied even the hope of having a tiny bit of happiness is such a sad thing.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_librarian3_start">It might get weakened for a while, but it won’t disappear for good.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_GreedKing_librarian4_start">Do you think there can be an end to greed?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_Tiphereth_start">I’m okay. Don’t worry about me and focus on the fight.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_Tiphereth_die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_librarian1_start">Things are getting tough. How’s Ms. Tiphereth doing?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_librarian2_start">Everyone taking care of yourselves?</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_librarian3_start">Can we really do this…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Servant_librarian4_start">This really is like a monster… He’s turning even creepier.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_Tiphereth_start">Don’t worry. I believe we can do it.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_Tiphereth_die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_librarian1_start">Ms. Tiphereth… What should we do…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_librarian2_start">It seems like there are lots of Abnormalities we never had the chance to see…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_librarian3_start">I haven’t seen anything about this one in the records…</text>
  <text id="T_roland_Fool_librarian4_start">What the heck is this… A clown?</text>

  <text id="Clock_Hokma_start">…What flows cannot be stopped, is it?</text>
  <text id="Clock_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="Clock_Hokma_kill">Alas, silence does not always bring about positive outcomes.</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian1_start">A price… for silence…? What is it trying to say?</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian1_kill">I guess the lesson was “Don’t waste your time.”</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian2_start">A scythe… clock? What does it mean?</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian2_kill">…Phew, I was in such a hurry; I’m outta breath.</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian3_start">Maybe there are more things we didn’t get to see before…</text>
  <text id="Clock_librarian3_kill">Silence and death are similar in nature… I suppose that’s not wrong…</text>
  
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian1_start">We used to joke about whoever got pecked by the bird being the bad guy, yeah?</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian1_kill">It looks even smaller when it’s in a cage…</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian2_start">Yeah. We even placed bets on who’d be taking the pecks!</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian2_kill">Yep. Something awful happens if someone hits it…</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian3_start">Everybody had to tighten up whenever it fluttered out of containment.</text>
  <text id="SmallBird_librarian3_kill">Hmm… That was a pretty safe method?</text>

  <text id="LongBird_Binah_start">How curious. To face a being lying dormant within a book in such a way…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_Binah_die">…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_Binah_kill">You have done well. Let us return and take a break.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian1_start">It is supposedly weakened… But we shouldn’t let our guard down nonetheless.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian1_kill">What does it mean to be fair, really?</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian2_start">Its scale was always tilted to one side, I wasn’t sure if its judgement could be trusted…</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian2_kill">Like the other birds we met, its motives might have been innocent.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian3_start">The sound of its scale tilting used to give me the chills.</text>
  <text id="LongBird_librarian3_kill">Justice… What is justice, I wonder.</text>

  <text id="Nos_Gebura_start">It looks awfully starved… We’d better be careful.</text>
  <text id="Nos_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="Nos_Gebura_kill">…A vampire, huh. Think I heard of it somewhere.</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian1_start">It seems to want something… Kind of horrifying.</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian1_kill">New Abnormalities keep showing up when you think you’ve seen them all…</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian2_start">It does. Doesn’t really look like a monster…</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian2_kill">Slurping blood? Yuck, that’s gross…</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian3_start">…Doesn’t it look sort of similar to us?</text>
  <text id="Nos_librarian3_kill">My body feels weak for some reason…</text>
  
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_Gebura_start">…Alright, we’re doing this.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_librarian1_start">Ms. Gebura! I think we’re all prepared!</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_librarian2_start">Well, if they could do it, we can do it.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_librarian3_start">So that was what the librarians downstairs were talking about…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Red_librarian4_start">That certainly looks dreadful…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_Gebura_start">You all remember it well. Let’s have a go at it, then.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_librarian1_start">That’s what Ms. Gebura taught us!</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_librarian2_start">Right. When one wields a sword, the purpose has to be clear…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_librarian3_start">Acting out of anger and grief is nothing more than a display of frustration.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Wolf_librarian4_start">A slaughter that’s lost its meaning…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_Gebura_start">We can discuss whether or not we’ll forgive the atrocity after we’ve finished this.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_librarian1_start">Maybe what he did was unforgivable…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_librarian2_start">How many people did he kill…? He’s scaring me.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_librarian3_start">Once you start looking back, you can’t easily stop.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Smile_librarian4_start">A mountain of bodies…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_Gebura_start">It won’t do good to force consolation on him too much.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_librarian1_start">I hope this’ll make him feel better…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_librarian2_start">I guess that says a lot about the emotions pent up in his heart.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_librarian3_start">They’re all violent ones…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nos_librarian4_start">Hey, that’s… the thing we saw for the first time recently.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_Gebura_start">…Maybe I can understand a tiny fraction of you, Roland.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_Gebura_die">Damn it, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_librarian1_start">Anyway… I think it’s almost over.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_librarian2_start">Hearing it mimic the voice of my coworker almost made me barf.</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_librarian3_start">That’s just the shape I remember… A creature trying to mimic humans…</text>
  <text id="G_Roland_Nothing_librarian4_start">Ugh… The nightmares are coming back…</text>

  <text id="Ozma_Chesed_start">That pumpkin must’ve been the only thing left by her side.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_Chesed_kill">I can’t say I like the outcome all that much~</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian1_start">I’m not even sure how to guess the preferences of things I see for the first time…</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian1_kill">Feels uncomfy… Happiness was all it wanted.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian2_start">Someone put a curse upon her. That’s messed up.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian2_kill">…I feel sorry.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian3_start">…That’s one terrible state for a princess to be in.</text>
  <text id="Ozma_librarian3_kill">I don’t feel… that good winning this one.</text>
  
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_Chesed_start">However this might go, let’s give it a shot~ Y’all know how, right?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_librarian1_start">Hey, counseling doesn’t work every time, either.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_librarian2_start">I’m not sure if this is a valid way to resolve ill feelings…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_librarian3_start">You’re telling me. I’ve never seen him so upset before…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Wisdom_librarian4_start">…I heard a lot about this, but it still managed to throw my mind into confusion.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_Chesed_start">That ‘forest’ will never go away.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_librarian1_start">And that might include us.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_librarian2_start">Could be the people he accuses of taking away his happiness…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_librarian3_start">What do the trees represent for Roland?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Woodsman_librarian4_start">That’s kinda scary…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_Chesed_start">…I’m sure anyone has a home in which to roost~</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_librarian1_start">Does Roland have a place to return to, Chesed?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_librarian2_start">Having no place for the mind to find peace must be a sad thing.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_librarian3_start">A place where one can rest easy must be home.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Waygohome_librarian4_start">Heading back home, huh…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_Chesed_start">Let’s not bother ourselves too much about it. Him coming to a realization on his own is the most vital part.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_librarian1_start">Yeah. We’ll never wholly understand every part of a different person.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_librarian2_start">…We aren’t exactly trying to pity Roland or anything.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_librarian3_start">That Abnormality was a being that became a monster again, I was told…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Ozma_librarian4_start">That’s sorta different from the horrible form we saw last time.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_Chesed_start">Yep. And we’ll get to realize that in time… Roland will, too.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_Chesed_die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_librarian1_start">Are those even things we have?</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_librarian2_start">Wisdom… Heart… Courage… And a place to calm oneself.</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_librarian3_start">Those are all things that are good by his standards…</text>
  <text id="C_roland_Oz_librarian4_start">Make people happy? …That’s totally a lie.</text>

  <text id="B_roland_Big_Binah_start">Indeed. We shall let him freely utter his sentiments first.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_Binah_die">…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_librarian1_start">Dunno… We’ve got to do what we can somehow…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_librarian2_start">Needs a lot of energy to take a revelation and actually change your mindset.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_librarian3_start">You’re right. Even minor thoughts are hard to change on my own…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Big_librarian4_start">I wonder if we can be of any help.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_Binah_start">I would suggest you be faithful to the present moment, rather than worry about the future.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_Binah_die">…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_librarian1_start">Hang on… We’re not gonna have to face what I’m thinking of at the end of this, are we?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_librarian2_start">Right now, we have that beast to handle…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_librarian3_start">Depends on the person.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Small_librarian4_start">Is it right for someone to impose their own definition of justice and punish others based on it?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_Binah_start">Let us suspend discussion on the advisability of it for now.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_Binah_die">…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_librarian1_start">If you believe it’s righteous, then it becomes the righteous thing; isn’t that how it works?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_librarian2_start">Determining that is a subjective issue in the first place…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_librarian3_start">You can’t really draw a line in the sand between right and wrong.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_Long_librarian4_start">An unjust scale… If I can call it that.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_Binah_start">That is the reason we are aiding him.</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_Binah_die">…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_librarian1_start">I suppose just seeing it doesn’t count as facing it properly, right?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_librarian2_start">Who knew we’d have to face THIS fear again?</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_librarian3_start">It really feels like the end…</text>
  <text id="B_roland_End_librarian4_start">Lady Binah… It seems we’ve almost reached the conclusion.</text>

  <text id="BlueStar_Hokma_start">If your faith in a certain thing is strong enough, your mind will not sway for other temptations.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_Hokma_kill">…I urge you to rest first. Let us organize once you have come to your senses.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian1_start">If we don’t stay sharp… We might be dragged to that place.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian1_die">Ahh… It’s here… Please take me…!</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian1_kill">That was revolting… I really don’t feel like getting all up in there.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian2_start">Sigh… It wasn’t easy having to deal with it sucking up employees.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian2_die">I can hear it now! The voice… It calls for me!</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian2_kill">I sorta felt I… missed it… for some reason.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian3_start">Here and the outside… There are fanatics everywhere.</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian3_die">Haha… Haa… I pity the fools who didn’t receive this call…</text>
  <text id="BlueStar_librarian3_kill">Man… It was brutal. I almost got vacuumed in.</text>
  
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_Hokma_start">Faith is bound to be challenged by irony.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_librarian1_start">Well… Whatever the belief is, it’ll probably be in vain.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_librarian2_start">Maybe there’s something you believe in, even if it’s not anything grand?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_librarian3_start">Faith… Faith, huh… I don’t really believe in stuff, come to think of it.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_doctor_librarian4_start">We’re… gonna have to deal with that horrible thing soon, aren’t we?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_Hokma_start">And it will be such a harsh thing to do.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_librarian1_start">There’s got to be a way to refute religion, though.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_librarian2_start">And it’s a hassle to deal with the blind ones…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_librarian3_start">No one who seeks salvation here is normal…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_1Phase_librarian4_start">…Well, damn. I didn’t want to face it ever again.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_Hokma_start">We ought to keep faith with unwavering resolve.</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_Hokma_die">…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_librarian1_start">…Hokma, sir. Is there another way we can do this?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_librarian2_start">Did we… do it wrong? Where did we…?</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_librarian3_start">I thought it was finally over…</text>
  <text id="H_Angela_whitenight_2Phase_librarian4_start">It… revived?</text>
</localize>