<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_1">When I cover my ears, I can only hear my own voice. I can pay full attention to the sounds I make.</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_2">If I mistake a gentle voice for something aggressive, it’s their fault for speaking like that. Am I right?</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_3">… …</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_4">It’s simple. I just don’t have to look, do I? I don’t have to face that darkness.</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_5">I’m not hearing anything I don’t wanna hear!</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_6">…</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_7">I don’t have to hear to guess what they’re saying. I bet they’re slandering me.</text>
	<text id="ChildCovering_nomal_8">… … …</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_1">Seeing, hearing, and speaking evil are all deeds that I can consciously prevent myself from doing.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_2">However, that alone won’t purge all evil from the world.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_3">A prudent sight capable of distinguishing good from evil is needed.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_4">In contrast to sharing joy with others, sympathizing with the sorrow of others is certain to be an unduly shallow exercise.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_5">Only I can soundly feel the pain of the sorrow I am wallowing in.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_6">Turn a blind eye to all that tries to hurt me.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_7">Turn a deaf ear to words that will lead me down the wrong path.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_8">Turn a mute mouth to unnecessary evil.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_9">And last of all, act not. Make myself happy that way.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_10">What does goodwill mean to me.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_11">No one’s going to cry on my behalf even if I’m sad.</text>
	<text id="TheCryingChildren_nomal_12">I don’t want to hear anything. I don’t want to see anything, or speak anything…</text>
</localize>