<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="Index_Yan_1">To …. Pack a lunchbox and consume it on top of a trash can in the streets of District 11 at 1 PM today.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_2">To …. Bake dacquoise while the hour hand rests between 7 and 8, and eat it while watching a movie.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_3">To …. Initiate a game of Never Have I Ever with the first five people you encounter. When one folds a finger, break it.</text> 
  <!-- 손가락 접기 게임 (Finger Folding Game), also referred to as 이미지 게임 (Image Game) or 손병호 게임 (Son Byeong-ho Game), is a drinking game where a group of people take turns to make a boolean statement, such as "If you're wearing glasses, fold a finger!". Those who fold all five (or ten depending on the format) fingers have to drink a shot. --> <!-- This is NEET's note -->
  <!-- This is actually relatively identical to the English speaking game "Never Have I Ever"/"Ten Fingers", only real difference is the phrasing. - Watson -->
  <text id="Index_Yan_4">To …. Neatly clip the nails of the sixty-second person you come across.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_5">To …. Pet quadrupedal animals five times.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_6">To …. Spin a wheel and throw a cake at the person determined by the result.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_7">To …. Consume eight crabs stored at room temperature and ripe persimmon at once.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_8">To …. At the railing on the roof of a building, shout out the name of the person you dislike, then jump off. The height of the building does not matter.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_9">To …. After a meal, discard all dishes that were used to serve it.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_10">To …. On the morning after receiving the Prescript, drink three cups of water as soon as you get up.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_11">To …. Race against residents that live in the same building as you to District 7. Measure the distance every twenty-three minutes and disqualify the one farthest away from the destination.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_12">To …. Within three days, knit a scarf with a butterfly pattern.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_13">To …. Dial any number. Give a New Year’s greetings and words of blessing to whoever receives the call.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_14">To …. See green from a white wall.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_15">To …. When hungry, consume a Cheeki’s cheeseburger with added onion.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_16">To …. Fold thirty-nine paper cranes and throw them from the rooftop.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_17">To …. At work, cut the ear of the first person to fulminate against you.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_18">To …. When your eyes meet another person’s, nod at them.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_19">To …. Return to your home this instant. You may leave once a dog barks in front of your house one time.</text>
  <text id="Index_Yan_20">To …. Wear light green clothing and take 10 steps in a triangle-shaped alley.</text>
</localize>