<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_1">Once we reach the end of this… We could all become happier.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_2">Humans cannot find redemption on their own, after all.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_3">I wanna get out into the world full of diverse ingredients, toot sweet!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_4">Arf, arf! Neiiigh!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_5">I only hope that no one will have to suffer as I did.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_6">The ideals and enlightenments of individuals are obsolete.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_7">I’m starving!!! Yeah! Can I have a taste of you all first?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_8">Cluck cluck!!! Ruff!!! Neigh, bawk bawk bawk!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_9">A place where no possessive desires or the grief of loss exist…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_10">Follow this flow which will guide us to bliss…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_11">It must be one full of clean and pure stuff… all top-shelf ingredients!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_12">Bawkbawwk!!! Woof!! Arf, rarf rarf!!!!!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_13">Indeed. We are mere components, content to exist…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_14">Please, believe us. Only faith can lead you to salvation.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_15">I can already smell something fishy… I’m loving it!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_16">Neeeiiigh!!! Neigh!!! Arf!!! Bawk.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_17">To become prosperous beings that own nothing yet have everything.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_18">We will wash off the rust of worldly filth, and rotate together as brand new gearwheels.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_19">Gee… The wait is so long, my mouth is gonna run dry!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_20">Bwakbawk. Bawk. NEIIIIGH!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_21">We will shape that world together. Please consider the positives.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_22">Accept this boon. The harder you try to break free from the current, the closer you’ll get to misfortune…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_23">Cuisine unlike anything you’ve ever had… Don’t you want to try it? Doesn’t the thought make you salivate? Hawhawhaw!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_1_24">NEEEIIIGH!!!!! RUFF!!!!! NEIGH!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_1">Ohohoh! Let’s host an even more dreadful performance!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_2">Brutal and hideous… We all have that nature deep down.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_3">This is such an invigorating sensation… I don’t feel stifled… It’s refreshing, rather.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_4">A round of applause for the crew that will illuminate the stage~!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_5">So why’re you ashamed to show ‘em?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_6">When this performance is over, the strings that have bound mankind will be untied…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_7">Now, now! There’s no time to waste! The flower doesn’t wait for the rain, you know?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_8">You masqueraded yourselves to look nice on the outside. You’re no different from us on the inside!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_9">Then, everyone can revel in true freedom!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_10">Now each of us is giving off a… sour smell~ Good, good! The stench smarts my nose!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_11">Yes. You’re merely being tugged along, your worth weighed on a scale. Don’t you find that much creepier and apprehensive?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_12">Don’t you wish to cut down the strings tugging at you against your will?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_13">Please don’t let the curtains be pulled down so carelessly, this stinky performance has to go on!!!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_14">A shoddy facade is gonna ruin the moods of both parties, so instead of that…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_15">It’s not too late. Perhaps you ought to change your mind.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_16">A world filled with smiling spider buddies! I’ve been waiting for this day with a snapped neck~!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_17">Better to be shameless about it. Be honest with yourselves.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_18">I, and the Ensemble, can help you.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_2_19">I know you hate complicating your thoughts. Get simple!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_1">How pitiful… You fight for the rules that have confined you. Just look at yourselves!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_2">Had you thought the same thing as us… We may have had been able to collaborate.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_3">Can’t you feel this tremor…? Could there be an overture with a rhythm more beautiful than this?</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_4">The time when we can be our true selves…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_5">Tis a shame. Alas, we do not intend to persuade you, so please understand.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_6">We’ll complete our own score… One that can be played indefinitely, even if there seems to be an end!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_7">Can you not understand? The joy of basking in this unbound freedom is palpable.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_8">Purely out of our own delusion, we invited sins, and were punished with the concept of death…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_9">So you will take the honor of remembering the first note of this everlasting performance…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_10">Ah… Yes. This is what I’ve truly wished for…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_11">Still we are trapped inside a frame, crushed under the fetters of our sins.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_12">We will continue our venture, playing variations as we seek new things.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_13">The freedom I’ve seen and heard were all temptations trying to lure me into tighter shackles!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_14">Thus, there exists a limitation, an end in the form of death…</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_15">…Now, it’s time to mark your end and our beginning.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_16">…Well, I should be thanking you really. And… sorry, I guess? Sorry that we’re moving ahead while leaving you behind.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_17">I urge you to join us and escape the decadence of flesh. Find your true selves!</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_18">Your performance may be reaching an end, but I do hope you’ll shine gorgeously in your own right.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_19">…We’re about to part now, Angelica. Sorry for what’s happened.</text>
	<text id="BlueReverberation_3_20">I hope you can stay with me until the end of the performance, at least.</text>
</localize>