<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="Roland_Black_Malkuth_1">We just might be able to make it!</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Malkuth_2">You’re right. So don’t worry too much!</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Malkuth_3">We shouldn’t fall back any more than this… Let’s keep focused for now!</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Malkuth_Die">…I talked big and failed to live up to it, again.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_1_1">This is a little scary… I’ve got to keep on my toes.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_1_2">If we can’t stop him here, who else will be there to do it?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_1_3">That means we’ve got to take this rather seriously…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_2_1">Are we gonna be enough to handle this…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_2_2">We have to do this… Let’s go.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_2_3">Things will go south if we can’t stop him here and now.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_3_1">To think we’d be receiving Roland… I never guessed it…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_3_2">I’m getting worried…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_3_3">Have the other floors… failed already?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_4_1">…For real? I’m getting a bad feeling about this.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_4_2">Damn… Can we take on him on our own…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_M_Librarian_4_3">We might be on our last legs now…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Yesod_1">Let us prepare for the encounter ahead first.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Yesod_2">Roland… I will not let you proceed any further.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Yesod_3">Letting him advance further will be dangerous… I advise utmost caution.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Yesod_Die">…I urge you not to panic and concentrate on the task at hand.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_1_1">This is an emergency. You can air your grievances about betrayed friendships later.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_1_2">Stay sharp. The other librarians could be put in danger.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_1_3">…Alright. This is the last stand, huh.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_2_1">This is not the time to be swayed by personal feelings.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_2_2">Will you just snap out of it?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_2_3">He won’t give us all the time in the world to prepare.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_3_1">I can see where Roland’s coming from, to be frank.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_3_2">…This seems different from what I know, by a lot.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_3_3">I’ll do my part, so don’t worry about me.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_4_1">…I thought I knew him pretty well.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_4_2">I suppose we’ll have to receive him… like we always have for others.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Y_Librarian_4_3">We definitely have to be careful… Is everyone alright? Ready?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hod_1">Yeah, you’re right. We should focus on what we need to do…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hod_2">That’s true. I hope… the librarians on the other floors are safe.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hod_3">The situation looks dire…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hod_Die">…I was, nothing but trouble until the end. I’m sorry.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_1_1">This isn’t the time to be reeling from shock, is it? Get ready everyone.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_1_2">If we don’t hold on tight and stop him here… The other floors will meet the same fate.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_1_3">Don’t worry. I’m certain we can put an end to this.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_2_1">Mr. Roland must’ve suppressed it all for a long time.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_2_2">We have ourselves to worry about, I think…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_2_3">That’s right. If he’s here, that probably means…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_3_1">Not that I don’t get him…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_3_2">I don’t see us as qualified to reason with him. We’ll just do what needs to be done, I suppose.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_3_3">It seems all the other floors fell… This could be really bad…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_4_1">I can’t believe this… Why…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_4_2">How are we going to dissuade Mr. Roland…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_H_Librarian_4_3">H—He’s here already…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Netzach_1">That depends on what each of us thinks… We gotta believe.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Netzach_2">I can’t guarantee that we can beat him, but we still gotta try… Let’s do as much as we can.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Netzach_3">……Aight. Don’t hesitate.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Netzach_Die">…Sorry brother, I couldn’t help much.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_1_1">Can we bring him to his senses safely this time…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_1_2">Yeah… Didn’t expect him to come all the way here.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_1_3">…Let’s get ready, then.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_2_1">What can we do? We shouldn’t just neglect him like it’s none of our business.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_2_2">This is driving me nuts… He must be way strong.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_2_3">I know I should believe that we can do it… But I’m still so scared.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_3_1">Not sure I have the stomach for it…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_3_2">I’m anxious… Are we gonna be okay?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_3_3">The responsibility feels… a bit depressing.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_4_1">I never thought we’d face Roland this way…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_4_2">I am… ready, I think. How’re the others?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_N_Librarian_4_3">Have all the other librarians been… defeated?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Tiphereth_1">Whatever the case, get your head in the game! You’re not gonna loiter around idly, are you?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Tiphereth_2">As much as I’m sorry for Roland… This isn’t the time to talk.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Tiphereth_3">Stick to the usual. I trust you all.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Tiphereth_Die">…Sorry. I wasn’t much help.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_1_1">Though… many things will be different from that time.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_1_2">Good point. What we’re doing isn’t all that noble either, yeah?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_1_3">Ms. Tiphereth… Do you think we can handle him?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_2_1">Well, we’ve been through this once.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_2_2">It’s about keeping one’s place. Nothing more, nothing less…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_2_3">Not good… We’ll be in serious danger at this rate.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_3_1">We should try as much as possible.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_3_2">Although we got fooled by him… I can sympathize with Roland a little.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_3_3">Are we the… only ones left?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_4_1">Even if he comes back to himself somehow… Will this all be resolved?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_4_2">He took part in inflicting upon others the same kind of pain he’d suffered, just for this moment…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_T_Librarian_4_3">…The whole place might go down.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Gebura_1">We’ve gotta do our damnedest to do our one job with courage: Protect.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Gebura_2">Don’t let defeat get to you before the fight even starts.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Gebura_3">…Yep. We have to stop him from going any further.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Gebura_Die">Damn it all, I wasn’t hoping to retire this way…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_1_1">Yeah. We might take a blow as soon as we let our guard down.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_1_2">Gebura, ma’am? We can… take care of this, right?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_1_3">Sigh… Nothing else to fall back on now.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_2_1">Better be on guard and keep an eye open for trouble…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_2_2">Not sure if it’ll be easy, though.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_2_3">Wait a minute, does this mean… we’re the only survivors?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_3_1">He seems kind of… different from that time.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_3_2">Maybe the same method as before will be effective.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_3_3">Roland’s gone and done it, huh…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_4_1">Revenge… Wrath is especially terrifying if its goal is clearly set.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_4_2">This feels risky… What do you think?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_G_Librarian_4_3">Ms. Gebura… He’s finally arrived.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Chessed_1">Let’s save the talk for later~</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Chessed_2">Sorry, Roland~ We’re not about to back off so easily.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Chessed_3">…Yeah. Let’s start this calmly.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Chessed_Die">I guess this is as far as I can go…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_1_1">We need to focus more on what we can do now.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_1_2">For the sake of those other librarians… We have to stop him here.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_1_3">We can’t let him destroy everything we’ve worked hard for to this point…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_2_1">There’s no use agonizing over stuff we can’t do anything about…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_2_2">…If we give up here, the others will be in danger as well, right?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_2_3">We can’t let any more trouble happen.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_3_1">Yeah. Both we and Roland have our own stories.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_3_2">He’s going to bring us down one by one…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_3_3">If we follow the principles… there shouldn’t be an issue.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_4_1">Chesed was right… It’s unfortunate that people have their own reasons as to why they can’t back down without a fight.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_4_2">…Do we have to do this like the last time?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_C_Librarian_4_3">I’m… worried. I’m not sure if we can take him down.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Binah_1">Indeed… Let us begin at our own pace.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Binah_2">Perhaps the child could not handle his emotions.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Binah_3">It would seem that no more words are needed.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Binah_Die">…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_1_1">Well, we aren’t ones to argue about that…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_1_2">…I wonder if we’ll come out fine in the end.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_1_3">However, if we let him breach this line of defense… It will pose serious risk.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_2_1">He’s doing this solely for revenge…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_2_2">Although it seems some floors got roughed up already…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_2_3">Can we actually handle him, though…?</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_3_1">…I’ve been played like a fiddle.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_3_2">I wouldn’t want the other floors to suffer such damage.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_3_3">This is what it boils down to in the end.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_4_1">…It’s certainly not easy to stand against someone I used to work with.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_4_2">Knowing us… I believe we can manage this.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_B_Librarian_4_3">I will try not to be a burden…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hokma_1">It wouldn’t be too late to converse with him after this situation has been settled.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hokma_2">…There is no other option, so we will have to engage thusly.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hokma_3">We cannot afford another defeat. …Sturdy yourselves.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Hokma_Die">…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_1_1">I still think it’s a good idea to talk, though…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_1_2">I’m not a fan of calming people through violence, but…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_1_3">Alright, then… I will do my utmost…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_2_1">He could take it as cheap pity.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_2_2">He’s lashing out so wildly…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_2_3">Regardless of the circumstances, don’t get intimidated and back off.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_3_1">It’s not something we can fathom, if we even have the right to do that.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_3_2">I suppose he’s gone through a few other floors first.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_3_3">…Things are not looking good, Hokma, sir.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_4_1">…That’s terrifying. I can only imagine how much he’s been keeping in.</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_4_2">It took a while for him to come here, does that mean…</text>
	<text id="Roland_Black_Ho_Librarian_4_3">He’s here at last…</text>
</localize>