<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize>
  <text id="expend_default">Would you like to expand {0}?</text>
  <text id="expend_malkuth">Good day, manager! Would you like to expand the Control Department?</text>
  <text id="expend_malkuth_first">Hello manager! Each day you will need to expand one department! Are you ready to open up the Control Department and begin managing Abnormalities?</text>
  <text id="expend_yesod">Greetings manager. Would you like to expand the Information Department and prepare for management?</text>
  <text id="expend_yesod_first">I am in charge of the Information Team and its department. I'll give you a proper greeting later. Are you planning to open up the Information Department before starting the day?</text>
  <text id="expend_netzach">Hey, you sure you wanna expand Safety before the day starts?</text>
  <text id="expend_netzach_first">Hey, I’m, uh… the guy in charge of the Safety Team. We can exchange names later. Wanna open up my department and skip over to managing?</text>
  <text id="expend_hod">Do you want to expand the Training Department and get going with management? I’m sure it’ll be very useful, manager!</text>
  <text id="expend_hod_first">Hello manager, I’m in charge of the Training Team! Are you thinking of opening up my department today?</text>
  <text id="expend_tiphereth">So are you going to expand the Central Command Department today?</text>
  <text id="expend_tiphereth_first">Good day manager, we are in charge of the Central Command Team. Will our department be opened up today?</text>
  <text id="expend_geburah">Thinking of expanding Disciplinary today? If you are, let’s do it quickly.</text>
  <text id="expend_geburah_first">I’m the head of Disciplinary. You opening up my department today?</text>
  <text id="expend_chesed">Gonna expand Welfare today and head onto managing the Abnormalities? Don’t worry, I’m not pushing you or anything. Just chill and take your time…</text>
  <text id="expend_chesed_first">Morning to you, my good manager sir. I’m in charge of Welfare. Are you going to be opening up my department today?</text>
  <text id="expend_binah">So you desire to broaden the Extraction Department?</text>
  <text id="expend_binah_first">How nice to see you again. As you can see, I’ve been placed as the leader of the Extraction Team. I’m sure we’ll meet again soon.</text>
  <text id="expend_chokhmah">Hello again. Will you be unfolding more of the Records Team?</text>
  <text id="expend_chokhmah_first">Good morning. Here is where the Records Department will be situated, if you decide to open it. In this place, we record and control everything.</text>
</localize>