<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize>
  <text id="ordeal_start_reward">Qliphoth Overload Reset</text>
  <text id="ordeal_end_reward">+{0}% Energy Quota</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dawn_type">The Dawn of Green</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dawn_name">Doubt</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dawn_start">One day, a question crossed through my mind. Where do we come from? We were given life and left in this world against our own volition.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dawn_end">To live was a process full of pain.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_noon_type">The Noon of Green</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_noon_name">The Process of Understanding</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_noon_start">In the end, they were bound to life. We existed only to express despair and ire.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_noon_end">We will understand life and the soul with our own hands.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dawn_type">The Dawn of Crimson</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dawn_name">The Cheers for the Beginning</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dawn_start">Let us light a flame yet more radiant in our lives; for life is a candlelight, destined to snuff out one day.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dawn_end">To live is to yearn and fight for our desires.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_noon_type">The Noon of Crimson</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_noon_name">The Harmony of Skin</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_noon_start">We marched from time to time, and we would share our pleasure.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_noon_end">The collision of one life with another, skin harmonizing, painting a yet more beautiful appearance.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_noon_type">The Noon of Violet</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_noon_name">Grant Us Love</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_noon_start">We could only hear the weakest and faintest of their acts. We sought for love and compassion from them.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_noon_end">We cannot understand them, nor will they understand us.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dawn_type">The Dawn of Amber</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dawn_name">The Perfect Food</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dawn_start">A perfect meal, an excellent substitute.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dawn_end">We ate incessantly to live. The inevitable diminution, the waste…</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dusk_type">The Dusk of Amber</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dusk_name">The Food Chain</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dusk_start">To accustom oneself to the taste was an inevitable process.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_dusk_end">We could live. We could continue eating.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_dawn_type">The Dawn of Violet</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_dawn_name">The Fruit of Understanding</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_dawn_start">To gain an understanding of what is incomprehensible, they dream, staring.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_dawn_end">They complied with nothing in their bid to understand. They simply did so.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_midnight_type">The Midnight of Green</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_midnight_name">Helix of the End</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_midnight_start">The tower is touched by the sky, and it will leave nothing on the earth.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_midnight_end">Who pays for the suffering and neglect of the lives given to us?</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dusk_type">The Dusk of Crimson</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dusk_name">The Struggle at the Climax</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dusk_start">Throwing away our old bodies, we all become one, infinitely continuing the red march.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_circus_dusk_end">One day we will know, and tomorrow we will march hand in hand.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dusk_type">The Dusk of Green</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dusk_name">Where We Must Reach</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dusk_start">We constructed a looming tower to return whence we came.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_machine_dusk_end">There wasn’t an answer. We didn’t find a single thing we wanted. We only witnessed the death of life itself.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_midnight_type">The Midnight of Amber</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_midnight_name">The Eternal Meal</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_midnight_start">They fought amongst themselves to eat the others.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_bug_midnight_end">And the stronger side survived. That, simply, is the story.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_scavenger_noon_type">The Noon of Indigo</text>
  <text id="ordeal_scavenger_noon_name">The Sweepers</text>
  <text id="ordeal_scavenger_noon_start">When night falls in the Backstreets, they will come.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_scavenger_noon_end">When the sun rises anew, not a scrap will remain.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_midnight_type">The Midnight of Violet</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_midnight_name">The God Delusion</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_midnight_start">We incessantly tried to accept it. We wanted to understand them in our heads by any means, regardless of the consequences.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_outtergod_midnight_end">For the sake of not crumbling in on oneself. The idea that they may impossibly exist, or that they are unreachable and forever enigmatic no matter the path. Unacceptable…</text>
  <!--해결사 속성별 이름-->
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_red_name">Red Fixer</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_white_name">White Fixer</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_black_name">Black Fixer</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_pale_name">Pale Fixer</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_claw_name">The Claw</text>
  <!--해결사 크리쳐 이름은 위에 있음-->
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dawn_type">The Dawn of White</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dawn_name">A Request</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dawn_start">From meaningless errands, to exploration, to contract killing; they will do whatever you wish, so long as you pay them sufficiently.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dawn_end">They work in the Offices, Syndicates, and the Wings. Their tasks vary from banal things to something truly sublime.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_noon_type">The Noon of White</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_noon_name">Armaments</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_noon_start">They search constantly, be it for the Backers of the Wings, the Inventions of the Backstreets, the Reliques of the Outskirts, the Artefacts of the Ruins…</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_noon_end">As they have always done, they will overcome all that impedes them, weapons in hand.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dusk_type">The Dusk of White</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dusk_name">The Fixers</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dusk_start">The colossal tower of light was titled The Library. It is only natural for the Fixers to be drawn to such a mystic place of life and death.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_dusk_end">Bookhunters… One day they will rummage through The Library reigned over by the Pale Librarian. They are what shall become of the Fixers.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_midnight_type">The Midnight of White</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_midnight_name">The Claw</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_midnight_start">To know and manipulate all the secrets of the world; that is the privilege of the Head, the Eye, and the Claws. It is their honor and absolute power.</text>
  <text id="ordeal_fixer_midnight_end">No one dares to stand against them. As long as they exist, the tale of the Nest will never reach its close.</text>
</localize>