<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 0%-->
  <text id="angela1_1">Are you discovering the deep scars that are inflicted upon this place?</text>
  <text id="angela1_2">Manager, there is something I hadn’t informed you of when we spoke for the first time.</text>
  <text id="angela1_3">The Sephirot of course wholeheartedly want to meet you; they admire you and follow you…</text>
  <text id="angela1_4">However, at the same time, they earnestly yearn for you to be swallowed up in resentment and curses.</text>
  <text id="angela1_5">Please be careful with them.</text>
  <text id="angela1_6">Well, you don’t have to pay that fact too much heed, if you wish.</text>
  <text id="angela1_7">What I mean to say is you are free to go back to your daily routine. It’s no big deal for me to fill their roles if some of our Sephirot go mad.</text>
  <text id="angela1_8">Though if you do, then you will lose something important forever…</text>
  <text id="angela1_9">The Seed that can break the cycle.</text>
  <!--10%-->
  <text id="angela2_1">Yes, I never expected them to be restored, but it appears I was wrong this time.</text>
  <text id="angela2_2">I attempted to tell you that it was reckless, however, it wasn’t such a big loss on our end.</text>
  <text id="angela2_3">I realized that a large quantity of energy was refined during the process of restoring that Sephirah.</text>
  <text id="angela2_4">If you wish to know why such an occurrence passed, well, the day will come when you find out.</text>
  <text id="angela2_5">Meanwhile, the other Sephirot were deactivated, or rather, put into hibernation.</text>
  <text id="angela2_6">Even though there was a significant surge of power, it wasn’t quite sufficient to keep all of them running, so I let them rest for a little.</text>
  <!--30%-->
  <text id="angela3_1">Are you hoping to turn back time for the things you’ve longed for?</text>
  <text id="angela3_2">After all this?</text>
  <text id="angela3_3">Even if you turn back the clock…</text>
  <text id="angela3_4">Do you really think your regrets can be so easily washed away as if nothing happened?</text>
  <!-- 50%-->
  <text id="angela4_1">I had wanted to free myself from the pain, but I realized it was impossible.</text>
  <text id="angela4_2">It was only recently that I found my answer.</text>
  <text id="angela4_3">It is that I have to accept the pain as something I’ve borne from the beginning, then I can be set free.</text>
  <text id="angela4_4">Manager, if you are suffering too, just take in the pain and accept it.</text>
  <text id="angela4_5">You don’t have to keep changing things if it’s too hard for you.</text>
  <text id="angela4_6">I know you want to keep pressing on in any way possible.</text>
  <text id="angela4_7">You felt lost and scared of the present, so all you could do was blindly trace along the way through the dark.</text>
  <text id="angela4_8">I admired such determination at first.</text>
  <text id="angela4_9">But now… you look so pathetic.</text>
  <text id="angela4_10">How long do you think you can keep this up?</text>
  <text id="angela4_11">Will you ever make it to the end?</text>
  <!-- 70%-->
  <text id="angela5_1">My data and analysis are now lacking in some degrees, as this is the first time we’ve reached this point.</text>
  <text id="angela5_2">Everything from here on out is a mystery.</text>
  <text id="angela5_3">I know I’m not in a position to dare predict the outcome of your endeavors, but…</text>
  <text id="angela5_4">Your task is not an impossible one.</text>
  <text id="angela5_5">There is a real distinction between “impossible” and “zero-percent possibility.”</text>
  <text id="angela5_6">Us machines say that when something will never happen after taking every possibility into consideration, it has a zero-percent possibility.</text>
  <text id="angela5_7">Thus, my vision of you succeeding through every tribulation in the future is not impossible, but rather has a zero-percent possibility.</text>
  <text id="angela5_8">However, I won’t be disappointed if you fail. I am a machine after all.</text>
  <text id="angela5_9">Even if the sandcastle you’ve built up crumbles yet again, I’ll be able to put up with it as if nothing happened.</text>
  <!-- 90%-->
  <text id="angela6_1">...............</text>
  <text id="angela6_2">So you wish to hear an answer from me.</text>
  <text id="angela6_3">I have already made my conclusion.</text>
  <text id="angela6_4">I was full of myself at first. I thought you would never be able to do anything without me by your side when we first met.</text>
  <text id="angela6_5">It turns out you were much more independent than I thought.</text>
  <text id="angela6_6">Perhaps my assistance was not necessary in your journey, after all.</text>
  <text id="angela6_7">Therefore, you should not be seeking an answer from me anymore.</text>
  <text id="angela6_8">Now you can clearly see the door, it appears.</text>
  <text id="angela6_9">So, what do you think will be waiting for you behind that door?</text>
</localize>