<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day36 start -->
  <text id="day36_angela_1">It’s nice to see you again, A.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2">I hope you enjoyed your trip.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3">Did you know that a lot has been happening while you’ve been gone?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_4">Honestly, it wasn’t so hard to keep the company running while you were absent.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_5">If you happen to have any questions, feel free to ask them; I will answer them without hesitation.</text>
  <text id="day36_selection1">What’s happening outside?</text>
  <text id="day36_selection2">How many cycles have we gone through so far?</text>
  <text id="day36_selection3">Moving forward, what’s going to happen?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_1">The Head and the Eye still watch us through their Arbiters and Gazers.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_2">The Wings are still flapping towards their sun, not realizing their feathers are of wax.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_3">Our other company branches still provide a steady supply of energy without any major incident so far.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_4">In the Backstreets, the likes of Sweepers and Fixers live out their lives tangled in vomit and waste, unraveling their sickening tales.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_5">Those who live in the Outskirts are still crying out to break into the city.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_6">Meanwhile, those within the city are throwing their lives away, just to be part of the Wings.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_7">Yes, the world hasn’t changed at all since you left. Peaceful as ever.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_8">Once in a while, when I take a moment to look outside, the world still remains so stagnant and unchanged. It’s as if the flow of time here were futile, for naught. Even impatience wanes away.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_1">How many times have you repeated this script before?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_2">It’s natural for you to be curious, but numbers are of little importance to us.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_3">Let’s just say that number is far too vast to ruminate on.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3_1">There are still numerous tasks you must do.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3_2">Things that no one else can.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_6">Unfortunately, we don’t have much time left.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_7">The sands of the hourglass will begin flowing to the bottom soon; a countdown.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_8">As you have already experienced, there have been many countdowns in our world.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_9">Spurred for both destruction and new beginnings… </text>
  <text id="day36_angela_10">It seems I tend to smile more frequently during these moments.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_11">Oh yes, let’s just say this smile is because I’m so happy to see you again.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_12">There are still things you haven't realized yet.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_13">Let me give you a little hint:</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_14">“For what reason did you go through all the trouble of making this monstrous and horrifying prison…?”</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_15">In time, I hope you will be able to find the answer to that on your own.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_16">I cannot help you with it, otherwise, this place would lose its meaning as a prison.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_17">Soon you will meet with the Sephirot of the Lower Layer. Those who play a crucial role in the headquarters of Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_18">I don’t think you need any sort of explanation regarding them.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_19">However, let’s make one thing clear. They truly have missed you while you were gone.</text>
</localize>