<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day46start -->
  <text id="day46_abel_1">A long time has passed since my loved ones left with their broken bodies and hearts.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_2">We’ve finally met, after taking such a long detour…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_3">I sent you a letter one day.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_4">That old, strange letter, that had the same name for sender and recipient.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_5">It told you that we would meet soon.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_6">……..</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_7">Why do you hesitate? Please, come with your mind at ease.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_8">I hope this environment satisfies you. I tried my best to recreate our office.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_9">You need at least one place in life to feel comfortable, don’t you?</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_10">However, I speculate you feel that this place is a bit more… serene, than you might remember, so to say.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_11">There are many reasons for that.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_12">This is a reflection of your heart, after all. The emptiness in your mind must be what makes this place so void.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_13">We weren’t particularly fond of untidiness. But there she was, always making a mess out of an organized room.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_14">There were times when we were used to such messiness, giving up on cleaning the room…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_15">Sadly, our hearts couldn’t bear to recreate such a moment.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_16">I am sure that now you know…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_17">This space changes to the rhythm of your heart.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_18">This office is born from your heart, siphoned up from your deepest subconsciousness.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_19">Yes, many parts of this facility were extracted and created from our minds.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_20">How did you think building such enormous underground structures in such a short period of time was possible?</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_21">We needed multiple extractions until we finally solidified amorphous images into something tangible.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_22">We repeated it so many times, until the memories were blurred and emotions were dulled, to a point where even the original sin was forgotten…….</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_23">Yes, there truly were countless repeats.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_24">It must have been roughly ten years outside, while this entire facility has been trapped in the cycle for a length of ten thousand years.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_25">This eternity is fascinating.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_26">All humans are given only one life to live.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_27">The future comes to us like the relentless waves of the sea.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_28">We cannot go against them. We are merely pushed back.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_29">TimeTrack’s technology could only reverse time in a very limited area.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_30">This tech was used for trivial things, such as granting an infinite moment of death to a condemned man.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_31">Or to show to those whose days are numbered their happiest moments.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_32">However, when combined with our energy tech, this small technology could bloom into something bigger.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_33">We invested in them without hesitation, even though they required a massive amount of funding and energy.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_34">That’s how TimeTrack’s second invention came to life.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_35">If time could be reversed infinitely, we could reach the sky that seemed unreachable.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_36">Unfortunately, breaking an absolute law of nature cost us a lot.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_37">Although we could rewind time infinitely, it always left some form of distortion. Perhaps because this technology still has not been perfected.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_38">No man could keep their sanity intact in this place.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_39">But here you are. You’ve reached this point, even though you limped and groveled along the way.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_40">Of course, it wouldn’t have been possible if not for Angela. But it is a herculean achievement that you went through that journey.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_41">Please, let your body and mind rest, if just for a brief moment. You must be exhausted.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_42">The path after this will be brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_43">Extremely brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_44">I, well “us”. We whom you will meet again will also be brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_45">They will not let you pass as simply as I do.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_46">If by any chance, you think you’re not ready yet, it is okay to go back to the first act.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_47">If you’ve made it here once after such a long and hard time…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_48">You will surely come here again, no matter how long it takes.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_49">We literally have all the time in the world. There is no need to hurry.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_50">Just keep in mind that the situation will be much different if you move forward from here.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_51">You will be given harsh trials, and faded, saturated questions we could not answer.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_52">And I am sure you already know this:</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_53">You can reverse time…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_54">But you cannot reverse a tale.</text>
</localize>