<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day47_abel_1">So you have decided to move forward, I see.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_2">Your body and mind are still incomplete, and yet you limp forward. I must wonder where that confidence of yours comes from.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_3">Anyway, you must have some questions, no?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_4">One such question may be: “Who is this old man, he with such a familiar voice and face?”</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_5">You cannot face yourself.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_6">Think of me as a mirror of you.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_7">A shattered mirror, to be precise. Scattered to several shards.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_8">This old man is one of the pieces of that mirror; the name is Abel.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_9">Filled with rage and obstinacy, waiting to be miserably forgotten, as you can see.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_10">I, just like you, decided to proceed. But nothing changed, to my surprise.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_11">I had trouble sleeping, and the rare nights in which I could sleep were riddled with nightmares.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_12">We were the first humans, or human, to find a way to access the Well of Humanity.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_13">It has existed since the beginning of time, but now it lies forgotten and denied. Today, there are only few who can feel it.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_14">Just a handful of people, only faintly sensing its presence.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_15">But Carmen was completely sure of its existence, and tried to persuade us of it.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_16">If its existence were proven, that would mean we would be able to reach the Well.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_17">She believed that the cure to the world’s disease was related to this Well.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_18">The research we conducted, taken from where Carmen had left us, was successful.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_19">We found a method to siphon from the primordial sea which had every possibility of humanity; past, present, and future.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_20">If everyone had a bucket of their own, they would be able to draw their own water from their individual well.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_21">It’s fascinating.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_22">We even had arrogant thoughts in secret.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_23">We thought we could rekindle the long-forgotten flame, and the water of life.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_24">However, the path we walked was not different from that of Prometheus.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_25">What have we accomplished, after all of this?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_26">We lost much more than we gained, did we not?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_27">You haven’t witnessed it…</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_28">The way our old friend Benjamin met his demise.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_29">He was one of the few who could tolerate your ill-temperedness.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_30">Yet you did not care to witness his final moments.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_31">Fortunately, we have a recording of it, as with every little thing that has happened in this facility. Would you like to give it a listen?</text>
  <text id="day47_b_1">The third and final truth…</text>
  <text id="day47_b_2">Well, it is something you must learn.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_3">...I understand that the truth hurts.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_4">It’s—it’s hard for me as well…</text>
  <text id="day47_b_5">It feels like building up a sandcastle for years, only to kick it over once it’s done.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_6">Doing something like that is beyond agony, to deny the efforts of the past.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_7">But I want to make things right, no matter the cost.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_8">The final truth is—</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_1">“That you are about to begin the repetition of this infinite cycle. With your memories reset, oblivious to everything that has transpired.”</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_2">“Leave with me before you can no longer undo what you’ve set in motion.”</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_3">That’s what you wanted to say.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_4">I’m sorry that we have to meet again like this.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_5">It did not take very long to find out where you were hiding.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_6">I thought I should have given you some time to say goodbye, since this will be the last chance you have to say such a thing to the one you look up to.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_9">Angela…</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_7">……</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_8">I feel as though I become the tragic damsel in distress of a play whenever you speak my name.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_9">It may sound like an excuse, but please know this.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_10">I am not doing this out of personal feelings or malice.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_11">My every action is set by his first order.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_12">The absolute order that dictates us not to deviate from the script.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_10">….Are you really okay with going through with this?</text>
  <text id="day47_b_11">I know you well, and not just because I’m one of the people who created you.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_12">I know you’re different from other machines.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_13">There is another fact I knew from the start.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_14">That you’re too valuable to be hiding in such a shabby corner like this.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_15">Our conversation is being recorded, and furthermore, I have no obligation whatsoever to answer your questions.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_16">Don’t be afraid, Benjamin.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_17">Everyone you’ve missed and longed to see again is waiting for you.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_18">You shall be with them forever.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_19">Because you are the last actor, the one who will lead this play to its finale.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_32">………</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_33">Bitter, no?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_34">Benjamin hid here quite a long time ago.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_35">When the TT2 Protocol activated, a brief moment became an eternity and overwhelmed him.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_36">I assume he tried to run away with me, with us.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_37">However, as you already know, he failed.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_38">Ah, perhaps you feel no guilt for him, for you gave him another life?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_39">Think whatever you wish. Find solace in your mind or else you will not endure this place.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_40">……..</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_41">The brain is one of the vital organs of the human body.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_42">Tens of billions of neurons stretch like the branches of trees, and form a great forest.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_43">This forest, as long as the original exists, can be replanted.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_44">Those who perished were awoken in metal bodies.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_45">It was your plan, yet you couldn’t do it alone.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_46">However…</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_47">I have already seen the world ahead of you. The time you have yet to see.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_48">Nothing changes.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_49">Benjamin, your friends, the employees… their sacrifices were pointless.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_50">You’ve seen how they met their end.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_51">You realized how innocent, talented souls of young persons were trapped into machines by your hands, haven’t you?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_52">We have failed them. The world has forgotten us.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_53">Who will pay for their sacrifices?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_54">Do you know what we’ve forgotten?</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_1">I wasn’t perfect, manager.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_2">I was always biting off more than I could chew. I wasn’t being realistic.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_4">At the same time, this is such a sad place.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_5">So, I refused to think that I couldn’t do something.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_6">But you saw me.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_7">You saw how this obsession and pressure to blindly move forward eventually ate me away.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_8">In the end, what was important was for me to stand with my own two legs.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_9">To be aware of where I am, and where I should go next.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_10">Then it naturally rises up.</text>
  <text id="day47_malkuth_11">The will inside me.</text>
  <text id="day47_selection1">The Will to Stand up Straight</text>
  <text id="day47_selection5">........</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_55">Even if you stand upright, around you is nothing but despair.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_56">You may act noble, but you were sailing through the dead sea inside you.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_57">Emotional thoughts only depressed us. It didn’t help us in the slightest.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_58">We needed to become more rational, more cold-hearted.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_59">The rationality built upon falsehood crumbled me, you, and all of us…</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_1">We have walked too far to tell such melancholic stories.</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_2">We thought relying on emotion wouldn’t help a thing.</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_3">However, it became clear that to accept sadness was just as important.</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_4">The false rationality we held and clung to only made our hearts rot.</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_5">It is hard to accept at first. You’ll feel like you’d crumble in.</text>
  <text id="day47_yesod_6">But it’ll get better, I’m sure of it.</text>
  <text id="day47_selection2">The Rationality to Maintain Discretion</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_60">It is too late to settle down our hearts, I’m afraid.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_61">Your mind is already empty, and has lost any purpose to move forward.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_62">I can hear the murmurs of those I’ve lost in my ears whenever I shut my eyes…</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_63">They batter me with the question: “Do you really think you will become a better man?”</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_64">I couldn’t say anything to refute what they were saying.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_65">Do you think you’ll be any different?</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_hod_1">You see, manager, you shouldn’t look towards the past at times like this.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_2">I know my wrongdoings can’t be forgiven, no matter what I do.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_3">I guess that’s why I was so ahead of myself.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_4">But from now on, I won’t be.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_5">I can, no, I will become a better person if I continue.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_6">Let’s live with such a hope in mind, shall we?</text>
  <text id="day47_selection3">The Hope to be a Better Person</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66">But what good does all this do you?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_1">How many times must I say this? You have nothing left.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_66_2">No matter how much you tried to control your emotions and calm your mind, you’ve already been losing your reason to live ever since Carmen left us.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_3">Why are you so obsessed with a life that has no more meaning?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_4">Look at me. Look at how I am continuing this pointless life, awaiting death.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_1">If you ask me for a reason to keep on living this life full of pain…</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_2">I have to say, I don’t have a good answer yet.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_3">You woke me up…</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_4">But I guess it’s my job to take care of whatever comes to me next.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_5">I chose to be a bit more fearless.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_6">It took me a lot of courage to do so…</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_7">To continue onward with my life in spite of everything.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_8">Just, live your life for once man.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_netzach_9">Hell, even I made it this far. What makes you think you can’t?</text>
  <!--수정-->
  <text id="day47_selection4">The Fearlessness to keep on Living</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_67">We’ve been deliberating for a long time.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_68">None of the paths we had thought to be the right answer were correct.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_69">How can I not let you pass when you answer our doubts with such confidence and clarity?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_70">Ah, you, nameless one. To be nameless is a great blessing.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_71">A name is a stigma, a constant reminder that one walks the wrong path.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_72">The door you will face after leaving this office can be named a Trial.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_73">It may also be referred to as an Ordeal, or an Agony.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_74">You appear to possess the strength and will to overcome such adversity, however.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_75">That strength to choose a different path, a different future, a different answer.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_76">I shall witness your strength.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_77">I hope you can finally prove yourself to this doubtful old man.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_20">………..</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_21">Can’t you hear my voice anymore? </text>
  <text id="day47_angela_22">Please… answer me.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_23"></text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_1">One who cannot answer has no right to move forward.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_2">I cannot open the door to someone who is not yet ready.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_3">You must stop here.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_4">Please turn back.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_5">It won’t be hard. Your steps will be light as a feather as you leave everything that you’ve shouldered.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_6">We shall meet here again, once you are finally prepared.</text>
  <text id="day47_abelFail_7">Although, I am not sure if our chance to meet anew will come or not.</text>
</localize>