<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day41 start -->
  <text id="day41_angela_1">They say the world was a place where one couldn’t find happiness with their own way of life anymore.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_2">That it was a world where everyone had to fool themselves into thinking that fitting into a structured mould was happiness.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_3">Nobody sought history or religion anymore. No one needed those pillars.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_4">Under the guise of new innovations that were needed in the world, companies emerged using technologies known as Singularities.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_5">Production of a permanent food supply, the manufacturing of customized living creatures, transport of cargo at speeds that would seem like teleportation, Artificial Intelligence that was more real than people, the technology to preserve the present by binding time, et alia.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_6">Similar to the food chain, small companies began to disappear, or were eaten by the larger companies…</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_7">At some point, they were called the Wings of the World, and soon a Head rose to control those wings.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_8">People started to derive their purpose for existence from belonging to the Wings.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_9">However, the truth was, everyone was slowly melting like the wings of Icarus.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_10">They may appear to be encouraging the development of the world for the better, but their nature is no different from ours.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_11">There’s always a price to pay; any sane person would know that the deeds the Wings commit in the name of the betterment of society are in fact the most humiliating aspect of these corporations. They are the disgrace of the world and its people.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_12">Lobotomy Corporation’s rival energy corporations aren’t that different from us, I presume. Who knows? Maybe they really are twisting dimensions to garner energy from hell as the rumors say.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_13">In every man, the two instincts, the primal essence of life and death coexist.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_14">The Wings only guided our instinct of life.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_15">However, if one instinct were to dominate too much, the other would begin to make its move, slowly and unbeknownst to us, from the depths.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_16">Soon, a world where everyone wants to return to nothing will arrive.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_17">Into the stillness of silence before the birth of mankind.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_18">She who loved sunshine, who wanted to give hope to mankind but failed.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_19">When the hand that only wanted to embrace humanity with warmth was ruthlessly severed, you clutched the void, and saw the crack between the boundaries that were never shown to others.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_20">Left alone, you decided to instill possibility and potential into all mankind.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_21">Hope and despair are intertwined in that possibility, making it impossible for anyone to know the answer.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_22">“If all repressed things can be extracted from the earth…” you said to yourself.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_23">In those days, you looked absolutely terrible.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_24">Many coworkers—friends—were worried about you and tried to comfort you, but you didn’t care. You wouldn’t listen to anything.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_25">I guess you still needed them at some point.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_26">Seeing as you were the one who locked them away in here, barely holding on to the husks of their dead bodies…</text>
</localize>