<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="angela_name">Angela</text>
  <text id="b_name">B</text>
  <text id="x_name">X</text>
  <text id="a_name">A</text>
  <text id="malkuth_name">Malkuth</text>
  <text id="yesod_name">Yesod</text>
  <text id="netzach_name">Netzach</text>
  <text id="chesed_name">Chesed</text>
  <text id="employee1_name">Employee #1</text>
  <text id="employee2_name">Employee #2</text>
  <text id="employee3_name">Employee #3</text>
  <text id="employeeTwo_name">Both Employees</text>
  <text id="employee_name">Employee</text>
  <text id="james_name">James</text>
  <text id="hod_name">Hod</text>
  <text id="no_name" xsi:nil="true" />
  <text id="ujin_name">Eugene</text>
  <text id="tiffany_name">Tiffany</text>
  <text id="gebura_name">Gebura</text>
  <text id="tiphereth_a_name">Tiphereth</text>
  <text id="tiphereth_b_name">Tiphereth</text>
  <text id="malkuthRobot_name">Malkuth</text>
  <text id="malkuthRobot_right_name">Malkuth</text>
  <!-- 글씨 뒤집혀져서 오른쪽 따로 생성함-->
  <text id="tipherethRobot_a_name">Tiphereth</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 a 기계-->
  <text id="tipherethRobot_b_name">Tiphereth</text>
  <text id="chesedPast_name">Chesed</text>
  <!-- 과거의 헤세드-->
  <text id="christopher_name">Christopher</text>
  <text id="isabel_name">Isabel</text>
  <text id="c_name">???</text>
  <text id="m_name">???</text>
  <text id="mm_name">???</text>
  <text id="nobody_name">???</text>
  <text id="binah_name">Binah</text>
  <text id="hokma_name">Hokma</text>
  <text id="hokmaPast_name">B</text>
  <text id="malkuthPast_name">Elijah</text>
  <text id="yesodVomit_name">Yesod</text>
  <text id="yesodRobot_name">Yesod</text>
  <text id="yesodPast_name">Gabriel</text>
  <text id="netzachPast_name">Giovanni</text>
  <text id="netzachRobot_name">Netzach</text>
  <text id="hodRobot_name">Hod</text>
  <text id="tiphereth_aPast_name">Lisa</text>
  <text id="tiphereth_bPast_name">Enoch</text>
  <text id="chesedPastPast_name">Daniel</text>
  <!-- 대과거 헤세드-->
  <text id="binahShadow_name">???</text>
  <text id="rabbitUnknown_name">???</text>
  <text id="rabbit_name">Myo</text>
  <text id="geburaPast_name">Kali</text>
  <text id="hodPast_name">Michelle</text>
  <text id="h_employee_name">H Corp. Employee</text>
  <text id="binahPast_name">Garion</text>
  <text id="hokmaPastReal_name">Benjamin</text>
  <text id="abel_name">Abel</text>
  <text id="abram_name">Abram</text>
  <text id="carmen_name">Carmen</text>
  <text id="adam_name">Adam</text>
  <text id="ayin_name">Ayin</text>
  <text id="announce">E. Broadcast</text>
  <text id="people1">Fleeing Man</text>
  <text id="people2">Mutating Man</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1">Hello, X.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2">I give you a warm welcome to Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3">I am Angela, your advisor and secretary. My role as an AI is to assist you in adjusting to your new workplace, so please have no worry in speaking with me or asking any questions.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_r1">It’s a pretty name for an AI, wouldn’t you say so?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_r2">It’s quite rare for an AI to have a name.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_r3">Even an AI can have a nice name, did you know that?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_r4">Have you ever met an AI with such a suave name?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_r5">I honestly quite like my name. How do you feel about yours?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_4">I was born from one of the ‘Wings of the World.’ It signifies that I am one of the best to exist in this age.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_5">Ah, I know what you must be thinking.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_6">Your eyes show that you think I look too human to be an AI, am I wrong?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_7">However, there is a great difference between us. I am bound here. I cannot go wherever I please like you do.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_8">I may be able to operate the systems of this corporation to open a door or prepare a cup of coffee for you, but I cannot take a step outside of this building to bask in the sunlight or feel the gentle breeze.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_9">Now, in regards to my appearance, as you can see…</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_10">The color of my hair is that of the morning sky after a light shower. The tone and shape of my voice is taken from the wisest person in the world. Lastly, my face is picturesque of the person who had the most beautiful smile.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_11">...</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_12">Haha. Don’t worry, that was a joke. There can be no such person on this Earth.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_13">My appearance was designed with attractiveness to the largest number of people possible in mind.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_14">If the way I look is pleasing to your eye, then I am working as intended.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_15">Moving on, Artificial Intelligence is much more efficient in comparison to humans in terms of multitasking.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_16">I am the best in a majority of work fields.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_17">I am able to handle the work of several dozen people at once.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_18">I’m certain many people have lost their jobs because of me. It’s such a shame.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_19">Well, enough with introductions. Is there anything that you would like to know?</text>
  <text id="day1_selection1">Could you inform me about the company?</text>
  <text id="day1_selection2">Tell me more about yourself.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_1">That is not a bad thing to ask about.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_2">Let me put it this way.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_3">Your world is constantly growing, and the demand for energy is exponentially increasing as technologies advance.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_4">All conventional energy sources combined could not sustain the world further.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_5">In search of a solution, we happened to stumble upon mysterious beings whom we dubbed Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_6">Then, we figured out that energy could be harvested from these ‘Abnormalities’ via a “special method.”</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_7">“To isolate them in a controlled environment, and then to harvest energy from them.”</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_8">Our corporation became one of the Wings of the World for this discovery that benefits humanity in two ways.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_9">Once you are fully placed into the role as the manager, you will be able to access all current information on the Abnormalities from the Encyclopedia.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_10">It is very important that you know and understand these beings well to be successful in your position.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_11">For now, the Encyclopedia’s pages lay blank, but it will be filled out little by little.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_1_12">Don’t concern yourself too much with it. It is the task of your subordinates to pen it.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_1">How should I describe this in layman’s terms?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_2">I heard that it took an enormous amount of time and effort to create me.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_3">All kinds of new algorithms and features were developed, inscribing a new chapter in the history of Artificial Intelligence.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_4">And I serve the company.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_5">In search of a solution, we happened to stumble upon mysterious beings whom we dubbed Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_6">Then, we figured out that energy could be harvested from these ‘Abnormalities’ via a “special method.”</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_7">While AIs as a concept have become so commonplace that they are seen and used everywhere in this day and age.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_8">I am quite different in comparison to the rest of the pack.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_9">That is, I can closely imitate human emotions. This is not a simple task, as emotion is a highly sophisticated originally biological system that is substantially more unpredictable and complex than any other.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_2_10">Along with other functions at my disposal, I will be your perfect partner.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_1">You have joined the company at an opportune moment, by the way.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_2">Lobotomy Corporation is always looking for ways to improve its harvesting processes.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_3">Our systems are continually updated to support this.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_4">Speaking of which, there was a new update to the system right before you arrived.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_5">That means the working conditions have been improved upon, compared to those of your predecessors.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_6">Think of it as a small welcoming gift.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_7">Best of luck for us.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_8">I was just about to mention you. You don’t understand the concept of patience, do you?</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_9">Oh, pardon my manners, Manager. I was talking to one of the other AIs that work here, I should introduce her to you.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_10">Our facility is a huge one, and even I would have trouble managing it on my own; so someone determined that there should be an AI to assume head control of each department.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_11">If I were to be considered the cerebrum, they would be the cerebellum.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_12">Naturally, of course, I should be your most trustworthy and capable companion among all the AIs.</text>
  <text id="day1_angela_3_13">Well then, shall we greet her now?</text>
</localize>