<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day4_angela_1">Do you take pride in what you do here?</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2">If not, this recent news will likely change your mind.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3">After your arrival, the rate of energy output has increased by 13%.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_4">If you still don’t feel the significance of this figure, then let me add that it’s a record breaking percentage.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_5">How do you feel?</text>
  <text id="day4_selection1">I can take pride in that.</text>
  <text id="day4_selection2">I'm not sure…</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_1">Ever since you began working here, the company has been taking strides in improvement.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_2">This means you are performing your role well.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_3">This shows that there should only be good news to come.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_4">A machine such as myself doesn’t flatter easily.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_5">It is good to know that you’re happy with your work.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_6">I remember your face the very first time you came here.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_7">You were so withdrawn…</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_8">Face all gray and grim.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_9">And you were all nervous about my presence.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_1_10">Don’t worry, it’s okay for you to be happy now.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_1">Why do you say that?</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_2">Is it not normal to be happy in a situation like this?</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_3">For your information, I had practically run here.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_4">All just to deliver this great news to you.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_5">That’s a figure of speech of course, but I did not expect you to react like this.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_2_6">It would be nice if you were a bit happier.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_1">Today’s a rather special day.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_2">Do you see that bottle of champagne on the table? Allow me to pour you a glass. Shall we toast?</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_3">Ah, today’s occasion is not something as monumental as someone’s birthday, or the company’s day of founding.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_4">You lost an employee for the first time yesterday.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_5">In fact, many more shall follow. I’m telling you this just in case you were unexpectedly shocked by the news.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_6">They had known the risks from the beginning. The company grows, fertilized by their sacrifices. It’s as simple as that.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_7">I am sure they would have felt proud of themselves as they took their final breath.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_8">Accepting their deaths with equanimity would be the greatest respect you can pay to them.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_9">That is why I popped this bottle of champagne I’ve kept for so long.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_3_10">Three cheers for the deceased, in memoriam of their noble sacrifices!</text>
  <text id="day4_selection3">&lt;i&gt;I’ll drink the champagne.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day4_selection4">I don’t want to drink right now.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_4_1">Allow me to give you a small bit of advice.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_4_2">To properly drink a glass of champagne, one should gently hold the lower stem of the glass, and then take it in lightly, savoring the bubbles.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_4_3">Perfect, just like that.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_5_1">Oh, do you want to save it for later?</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_5_2">That’s fine, there will be many more occasions on which to toast.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_5_3">However, manager, please refrain from drinking alone when I’m not around.</text>
  <text id="day4_angela_5_4">A toast is only worthy when there’s a companion around to clink glasses together.</text>
</localize>