<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day48_abram_1">………………</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_2">Do you remember when we still knew the warmth of the sun?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_3">We’ve become too cold to continue cherishing such a thing.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_4">No, in fact, we weren’t meant to bask in such warmth in the first place.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_5">You feel it too, don’t you?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_6">I can see you already feeling the nostalgia in the air right as you stepped into this room.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_7">....... </text>
  <text id="day48_abram_8">There is a tale of two doors.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_9">Those two doors that never wanted to be opened, but had to be.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_1">Hey, A, it’s me. Are you there?</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_2">Can I come in?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_12">I didn’t want to listen to what would come next.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_13">I wanted to pretend I wasn’t in the room…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_14">Because I knew what she was going to tell me.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_15">Sometimes, her thoughts could be extremely reckless.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_16">It really frightened me whenever she did that…</text>
  <text id="day48_selection1">&lt;i&gt;Open the first door&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_17">I saw her eyes right after opening that door.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_18">Those eyes, soaked with red, as she had to endure cruel reality.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_21">She walked into your lab and started illustrating her hypothesis. Carefully, yet decidedly.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_22">You wanted to tell her it was preposterous, but like always, she had you persuaded.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_23">You had no choice but to admit it was the only way.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_23_1">What made me, us, so upset…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_24">Was how much it hurt to listen to her put it so calmly, as if it were none of our business.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_25">And how much we loathed ourselves for just having to tolerate it.</text>
  <text id="day48_people_1">We just can’t seem to get any further than this.</text>
  <text id="day48_people_2">However, we will break through somehow.</text>
  <text id="day48_people_3">We’ve got Carmen with us after all!</text>
  <text id="day48_people_4">Don’t worry, I think it’ll all work out.</text>
  <text id="day48_people_5">The biological scans show that Carmen is the fittest candidate… But, we haven’t run a precision test yet though… So if we want to find another candidate, we can always…</text>
  <text id="day48_people_6">Carmen can…</text>
  <text id="day48_people_7">Carmen is…</text>
  <text id="day48_people_8">Carmen would…</text>
  <text id="day48_people_9">Carmen….</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_1">You should’ve been the one to die…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_26">The research wasn’t bearing fruit, people were growing tired, yet their eyes glittered with expectation...</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_27">She was on the edge. One more step would make her fall.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_28">Then that day, when Enoch’s breath stopped, she finally realized…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_28_1">That her path was always in her sight.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_28_2">Just one glance below the fall…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_28_3">And she’d never lift her head again.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_29">She wouldn’t respond, no matter how many times I yelled.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_30">Only the sound of flowing water filled the air…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_31">I just kept yanking the doorknob like I were insane.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_32">Yet I hoped it would never open…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_33">I hoped and prayed countless times…</text>
  <text id="day48_selection2">&lt;i&gt;Open the second door&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_33_1">The first thing I saw once I opened that door was a pair of closed eyes.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_33_2">My eyes began to soak with red as I realized that hers would never open again.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_34">She stepped into the bath herself…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_35">So that not a fragment of needless emotion, like guilt, would pile up on us.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_36">I… we saw with our eyes, so clearly.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_37">She was bleeding out and delirious, but still she held on to life.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_38">We violated her body with our own hands, and buried her underneath the ground.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_39">……</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_40">Why was she so cruel, and why did we have to become so cruel?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_41">We asked this question without an answer, to the toast that celebrated our success blossomed with death.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_42">However…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_43">I have found a way to redeem us, at long last…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_44">You have come to the right place.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_45">This is the room where she sleeps.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_46">Don’t worry, she won’t wake up with this much noise.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_47">Can you meet her again?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_48">Let’s do it like this.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_49">Ask her, she who was always watching you from the beginning.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_3">……….</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_4">I have something I should confess. I actually have a much weaker heart than everyone thinks.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_5">I always say stuff like “count on me” and “just follow me” in front of everyone…</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_6">But I’m never sure about the things I do.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_7">If anyone were harmed or put in trouble because of what I do…</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_8">I would definitely be shaken and end up hating myself. I know that.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_9">That’s why I need to ask you for a favor.</text>
  <!-- 음악 전환-->
  <text id="day48_carmen_10">No matter what I may become, please finish what I started.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_11">We humans have weak hearts. One crack and it will easily crumble. I am no exception to this, but you…</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_11_1">You’re not the same as the rest of us, right?</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_11_2">No matter how cruel this world may get…</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_12">You’ll endure through it.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_13">There is only one way out, and it’ll never change.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_15">You know what I’m trying to say, right?</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_16">........</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_17">Are you unsure?</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_18">I have this routine I do whenever I’m afraid of the path I have taken.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_19">It’s like... being a plant, photosynthesizing.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_20">Ease up your tension, and just close your eyes… Yes, just like that.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_21">Make yourself as comfortable as possible, so that your mind finds itself comfortable too.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_22">It tickles, no? But just wait.</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_23">Now…</text>
  <text id="day48_carmen_24">Fade away without a trace…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_50">.............</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_51">Yes, I was the only one.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_52">I was the only one who could fulfill her ideal.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_53">I was the only one who could finish it…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_54">Only me…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_55">However, she never told me this path of hers would be riddled with such vicious thorns and spikes...</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_56">…..</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_57">This is the Bucket created from Carmen’s sacrifice.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_58">This bucket is the beginning and the end destination of this place.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_59">Cogito is endlessly produced here, spewing out life and death.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_60">When we saw that the bath was overflowing, we thought everything was over.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_61">However…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_62">We couldn’t have been more wrong.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_63">She’s “alive” right now, as this.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_64">She saw every path we walked.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_65">In reality, her ideal was simply too grand in the first place, and our power too miniscule to fulfill it.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_66">She sacrificed everything of hers without a trace left behind, but I…</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67">You and I, we remember the things we’ve done to become a Wing, to stay a Wing.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_1">It was revolting at first.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_2">But you see how we acclimated to it after the first few times?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_3">We flawlessly realized our hideous actions just like all the other Wings.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_4">No, not just that. We even evolved our own unique cruelty that can’t be found in any other Wing.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_5">The story of how human sacrifices are required to fulfill our ideal needed to be continued.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_6">So we had to put on the guise of simply being manic about energy production.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_7">Though we know the truth too well.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_8">Were we really only pretending, while we were so indifferent towards the countless deaths?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_9">Probing and combing through the brain of a woman to blend into the world, to evade the Head and the Eye? </text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_9_1">Throwing a person into the jaws of a monster just to gain some energy?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_9_2">Reincarnating your colleagues just to make them live through the same agony again?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_10">Do you really think those are things any normal person would do...?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_11">Yet we closed up our eyes and ears, and numbed ourselves. We eventually felt nothing for what we do.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_67_12">I named myself Abram to remember your, our sins; sacrificing the innocent.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_68">What did I even expect to achieve, doing all this, founding a showy corporation… I don’t even know anymore.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_69">Does it really matter at this point?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_70">No, it doesn’t.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_71">We were wrong from the start, our very existence is wrong.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_72">You and I, all that’s left for us is atonement.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_2">You already knew.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_3">You know we didn’t meaninglessly embrace this pain.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_4">Tiphereth knew that a long time ago.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_5">I guess that’s why he always walked ahead of me.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_6">One day, I realized that you were also looking towards somewhere with a clear vision, just like he did.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_7">I just didn’t want to admit that I was lagging behind. I think that’s why I was always so frustrated.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_8">I’m the Sephirah of the Middle Layer, head of the Central Command Team. I can’t afford to fall behind like that, now can I?</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_9">That’s the reason why I said I’ll count on you, and hold expectation.</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_10">Promise to show me someday…</text>
  <text id="day48_tipheretha_11">And show the world the fruit of our pain and labor.</text>
  <text id="day48_selection3">The Expectation for the Meaning of Existence</text>
  <text id="day48_selection6">..................</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_77">You’ll fall onto the ground no matter how much expectation and hope you have.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_78">You know what? Photosynthesis is for plants after all. Things that actually take sunlight. </text>
  <text id="day48_abram_79">It was never for something like you and I.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_80">Don’t you know this already? We drove Carmen to death, we just saw that…</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_1">I was always furious without any real reason.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_2">It always felt like I’m missing something. But I never knew what that something was.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_3">I vented this anger of mine in a rather bad way, as you saw.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_4">This madness without purpose would never go away.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_5">If you didn’t stop me, it would have grown bigger and bigger; it would have eventually devoured me.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_6">Look, we’re never going back to how it was before.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_7">The situation’s changed way too much.</text>
  <text id="day48_gebura_8">But I was able to keep my promise with her because you stopped me, at the very least.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_gebura_9">You also have to remember this.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_gebura_10">She would want you to protect what we have left, rather than just languish in guilt.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_selection4">The Courage to Protect</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_81">.....</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_82">Yes, she entrusted us with what’s left.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_abram_83">But we were not the person who Carmen thought us to be, no.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_abram_84">The only person that believed in us was gone.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_abram_85">There was no one left around us.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_chesed_1">Manager, do you know why I chose to join your small company, instead of any other grander Wings?</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_2">Of course, Carmen’s moving speech did pique my interest, not gonna lie.</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_3">However, the decisive factor for me…</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_4">It was because I liked how everyone here trusted Carmen.</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_5">You know how meaningless the word “trust” is nowadays, don’t you?</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_6">…That’s not all, manager.</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_7">Carmen trusted in you entirely until her moment of death.</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_8">Everyone else who remained did too.</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_9">Why do you think I decided to stick with you until the end?</text>
  <text id="day48_chesed_10">Just look around you now.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_chesed_11">Everyone gathered here just for you. And they’re waiting expectantly.</text>
  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day48_selection5">Those who are Faithful and Trustworthy</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_92">How can you be so certain?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_93">Carmen lies here, neither alive nor dead.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_94">How can you walk towards the unpredictable future, leaving her behind here?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_95">We are obliged to remain trapped in this cycle of eternal punishment.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_96">Yet still you want to reach for tomorrow? You want to escape this endless regret and atonement?</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_97">There is one final door past here that wasn’t written in the story.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_98">It’s one I can’t open.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_99">It only opens to those who are not soaked in regret.</text>
  <text id="day48_abram_100">Think you can open it?</text>
  <text id="day48_selection7">&lt;i&gt;Open the final door.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day48_angela_1">……</text>
  <text id="day48_angela_2">Why do I see only darkness?</text>
  <text id="day48_angela_3"> Why does my voice not reach you at the finale?</text>
  <text id="day48_angela_4"></text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_1">...... It figures you can’t give me an answer.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_2">Seems you finally accepted it.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_3">You and I, we’re failures.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_4">Look on the bright side though.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_5">Even though we’re failures, we managed to achieve at least one thing.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_6">We’ll be able to see…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_7">Carmen again like this.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_8">Although we can’t take a nap, lying in the field under the warm sun like we used to…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_9">She’s alive, she’s watching us.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_10">Don’t worry, she’ll understand.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_11">She’ll tell you that even though you couldn’t make it to the end, you did a good job getting here at least. You’ll have eternal rest with her.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_12">We should have just listened to Benjamin in the first place…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_13">My biggest regret, biggest sin, is that I didn’t stop when I should have.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_15">……</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_16">Carmen is our sun, so it doesn’t matter if we stay underground forever.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_17">Attention. Attention to all employees. We offer you our congratulations for the start of your honorable retirement. This broadcast is pre-recorded.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_18">Let us sink now, Carmen.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_19">I know you can’t hear my voice…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_20">But I don’t care.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_21">I won’t try to open any more doors…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_22">I hope that I’m with you when I open my eyes again someday.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_23">We thank you for your hard and earnest work, and have great, respectful gratitude for your efforts and loyalty…</text>
  <text id="day48_selection8">&lt;i&gt;Close the door…&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day48_abramFail_24">....... Goodnight.</text>
</localize>