<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day34 start -->
  <text id="day34_carmen_1">Ease up your tension, and just close your eyes… Yes, just like that.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_2">Make yourself as comfortable as possible, so that your mind finds itself comfortable too.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_3">It tickles, no? But just wait.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_4">Now, fade away without a trace…</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_5">Feel the water and air during the different seasons, inside a different dream and a different body, forgetting and remembering everything.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_6">You’ve already become something.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_7">I don’t know what it is.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_8">But I’ve already left for somewhere long ago.</text>
  <text id="day34_carmen_9">Please don’t look for me, I will no longer be able to teach you. </text>
  <text id="day34_malkuth_1">But Mister A, please! I want to be part of the Cogito experiment! I’m all ready, I can prove it! </text>
  <text id="day34_a_1">(The particles scattered across the floor are sparkling in the light.)</text>
  <text id="day34_malkuth_2">K-Kill… me…. Please k-kill me A…. I’m sorry…. I’m so sorry…. </text>
  <text id="day34_angela_1">Just as you commanded, I have written up the job application form for our corporation.</text>
  <text id="day34_angela_2">The reception is good. Everyone thinks that it’s a new employment method that does not concentrate on just one’s abilities.</text>
  <text id="day34_angela_3">The number of applicants is projected to meet the initial calculation.</text>
  <text id="day34_angela_4">The experiments are almost complete.</text>
  <text id="day34_angela_5">We will soon hire people according to the order of priority you’ve stated.</text>
  <text id="day34_angela_6">I’ve also arranged a meeting with TimeTrack. </text>
  <text id="day34_angela_7">…Are you thinking about those who have left you?</text>
</localize>