<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day5_angela_1">Our founder, A, has said this to me many a time.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_2">“Each successful experiment makes you a better person.”</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_3">The greatness of this company was founded on multitudes of trials and hardships.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4">So you too, shall become great.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_5">Each day in the company is another small experiment towards shaping your life for the better.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_6">How has your day been today?</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_7">Well, of course it was fine. Let’s spare the pleasantries, no?</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_8">Manager, how has your life been?</text>
  <text id="day5_selection1">An absolutely horrid one.</text>
  <text id="day5_selection2">Nothing spectacular, just ok.</text>
  <text id="day5_selection3">It could be better.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_1_1">…</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_1_2">Ah, excuse me. Your answer surprised me.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_1_3">I have no knowledge of what it is like to live a horrible life.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_1_4">I am afraid I cannot sincerely console you.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_1_5">However, perk up just a little, many things will change if you stay here.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_2_1">Leading a normal life could be considered an achievement in this day and age.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_2_2">Although, one can always improve the quality of their life.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_3_1">I cannot see the color of your life as you do.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_3_2">While I am unable to console you with empty words such as “that’s not true.”</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_3_3">Many things will change while you are here. That much is clear.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_1">This is a simple metaphor, but…</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_2">The seed of a tree will not grow just anywhere.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_3">It requires fertile soil, the right temperature, and fresh water.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_4">However, most seeds fall on barren soil.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_5">For those malfallen seeds, stretching out their roots and sprouting even small leaves are challenges full of pain.</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_6">I cannot provide you with water or sunlight…</text>
  <text id="day5_angela_4_7">However, I will do my best to tend to the soil.</text>
</localize>