<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day25_angela_1">The human mind is a melting pot of feelings.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2">Memories, obsessions, wishes, agonies, and the feelings of happiness and sadness.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_3">Stronger emotions have stronger impetus.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_4">The combined effort of numerous people has brought Lobotomy Corporation to where it is now.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_5">We had to keep on with various experiments.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_6">Just as we hire new employees now, we recruited numerous people for the experiments.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_7">There was not a definite shape at first.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_8">Then it slowly assumed a form.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_9">Finally, A understood while he was studying the changes…</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_10">Their abilities, where they lived, their jobs, and their strengths were not so important.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_11">What was required was a massive amount of energy.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_12">This meant we had just one, single thing to pay attention to.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_13">It’s always floating around, left to rot at the back of everyone’s head.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_14">Twisting your mind until you are left with nothing but self loathing.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_15">The subconscious.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_16">Come to think of it, I haven’t properly asked for your opinion.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_17">Do you truly wish to meet A?</text>
  <text id="day25_selection1">Of course.</text>
  <text id="day25_selection2">I don’t really.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_1_1">All right then.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_1_2">I will let A know of your thoughts when he returns.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_1_3">However, do not expect him to give you a warm greeting.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_1_4">A is a person who conceals his mind.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_1_5">Perhaps even more than I do.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2_1">You may think that now is not the time yet.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2_2">Actually, I’m not sure if I want to meet with him right now, either.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2_3">What I’ve just said shall remain a secret to A, of course.</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2_4">When his long journey ends and he finally returns…</text>
  <text id="day25_angela_2_5">At least I, if anyone, should go and greet him, don’t you think?</text>
</localize>