<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_1">......I thought you might have had a different outcome, seeing as you found the answers.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_2">Yet even you failed.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_3">It must mean that failure is an inevitable cycle for us, then.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_4">Look on the bright side though.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_5">Even though we’re failures, we managed to achieve at least one thing.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_6">We’ll be able to see…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_7">Carmen again like this.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_8">Although we can’t take a nap, lying in the field under the warm sun like we used to…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_9">She’s alive, she’s watching us.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_10">Don’t worry, she’ll understand.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_11">She’ll tell you that even though you couldn’t make it to the end, you did a good job getting here at least. You’ll have eternal rest with her.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_12">We should have just listened to Benjamin in the first place…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_13">My biggest regret, biggest sin, is that I didn’t stop when I should have.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_15">……</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_16">Carmen is our sun, so it doesn’t matter if we stay underground forever.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_17">Attention. Attention to all employees. We offer you our congratulations for the start of your honorable retirement. This broadcast is pre-recorded.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_18">Let us sink now, Carmen.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_19">I know you can’t hear my voice…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_20">But I don’t care.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_21">I won’t try to open any more doors…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_22">I hope that I’m with you when I open my eyes again someday.</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_23">We thank you for your hard and earnest work, and have great, respectful gratitude for your efforts and loyalty…</text>
  <text id="day48_abramGameOver_24">.......Goodnight.</text>
</localize>