<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day42 start -->
  <text id="day42_angela_1">It’s been quite a while since your first encounter with the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_2">I should suppose that you have become a bit more familiar with them.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_3">Let me ask you this question again: What do you think Abnormalities are?</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_4">Oh please. You can’t still believe that Abnormalities are just bizarre alien creatures that appeared all of a sudden, and that we need to isolate them, do you?</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_5">Abnormalities are not the evil monsters that you read about in old fairy tales.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_6">They are not some supernatural gods that descended upon us to judge our sins, either.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_7">There is an old River that has been flowing at the very bottom of the world for many an age.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_8">It is the source of everything, but has been forgotten by mankind.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_9">Nobody knew of its existence, but somewhere in the world there are very small gaps, or holes. It is through those which the river gently finds itself a stream.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_10">For instance, strange beings would sometimes crawl out of such a gap somewhere in the ‘Black Forest’, located in the Outskirts.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_11">Obviously, the amount was simply too insufficient for Lobotomy Corporation’s energy needs.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_12">Our Singularity is not that we produce energy from the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_13">Rather, it is the ability to create Abnormalities themselves.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_14">Their forms were incomplete because they came from a forgotten place; we were scared of them because they were incomplete. It is because of that terror that they have been sealed underground.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_15">However, Abnormalities are part of the Seed. That’s what I meant by “possibility”.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_16">The Seed is not something that can be made in just a day, or be created on its own.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_17">We realized that if we wanted to fix a broken system, we couldn’t just sit around in a sunny spot, waiting for the clouds to part.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_18">What should we do after planting the seeds, you ask?</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_19">We can’t control the entire process, we have to leave them to sprout on their own.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_20">Aren’t we allowed that much hope at least?</text>
</localize>