<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1">Do you wish to know why it has come to this?</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1_1">It is due to your lack of self faith.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1_2">Faithless actions only result in a dreadful death.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_2">Do not worry; I shall demonstrate, for I know everything.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_3">You are me, and I am you.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_4">I am the only one of us who realized the one truth, and stood atop the world itself.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_5">I am the you who shall leave the paths I walked once, and choose to join the world she truly wanted to create.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_6">And you and I, we shall be the us who can do whatever we imagine from now on.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_6_1">M-Monsters! Help me, please!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_6_2">Something weird’s g-growing out of me. L-Look at this, ahahahahaha!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_7">Behold.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_8">Witness how this loss-ridden world is perfected by us.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_9">The foolish god named rationality ruled over this world until this moment.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_10">No, to call it a god is an overstatement. It is simply a tragic illusion.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_11">We shall drag it down from the heavens with our own hands and open everyone’s eyes to the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_12">Yes, the world Carmen yearned for will soon unravel before your eyes.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_13">Let us create this paradise, you and I.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_13_1">Even the Head and the Eye are merely human. They cannot stop those of us who have accepted the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_14">You know that everything we witnessed in this land is only a shadow, and that you never saw the truth until now.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_15">With this, the plump fruit of redemption will reach everyone’s hearts.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_16">Those abandoned, those who hold power, those with wealth, those who remain hopeful, all of them.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_17">The tree of humanity will reach the root of this world.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_18">Again, behold.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_19">Did I not declare that all shall be free in the end?</text>
</localize>