<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day9_angela_1">Manager, among these three letters of the alphabet: A, B, or C; which would you select?</text>
  <text id="day9_selection1">I’ll pick A.</text>
  <text id="day9_selection2">Why not B?</text>
  <text id="day9_selection3">C sounds nice.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_1_1">So you’ve picked one? Good. Now please listen carefully.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_1_2">The letter ‘A’ is a fascinating one. My name starts with it as well.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_1_3">Those who choose A are sensitive to the opinions of others about them, and are result-oriented people. As such, they are excellent listeners, and are loved by many. People will flock to them.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_2_1">So you’ve picked one? Good. Now please listen carefully.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_2_2">People who choose B are detail-oriented. They are rational, realistic, and honest to their needs, even to the point where others may perceive them as snobs. However, the pursuit of practical interest and the tendency to avoid loss will lead them to success.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_2_3">Personally, I dislike the letter ‘B’. </text>
  <text id="day9_angela_3_1">So you’ve picked one? Good. Now please listen carefully.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_3_2">Alright, the letter ‘C’. Not a bad choice.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_3_3">Persons who select C believe that the process is more important than the outcome. Therefore, they are good at planning ahead and enjoy change. They will be able to gain insight and attain inner growth without being confined by the rules.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_2">This is a new pastime among the employees. I find it rather uninteresting.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_3">There is no scientific basis behind the observations, but it is admittedly a little fun to waste time with these “tests”.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_4">You know, maybe I could imagine…</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_5">Whether I would have been this or that kind of person if I were human.</text>
  <text id="day9_angela_6">Is it too odd for me to think about that?</text>
</localize>