<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <text id="day3_angela_1">Greetings, manager.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2">It marks three days now that you have worked here.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_3">The number three is a mysterious one.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_4">In age old fables, it is common for a mysterious entity to appear and tell the protagonist to utter three wishes.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_5">Sadly, I am not a mage or billionaire that can grant your wishes.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_6">However, I do happen to know what your predecessors wished for.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_7">There were many aspirations. Common among them was the seeking of some kind of “growth”.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_8">To lead the company to prosperity, to achieve spiritual maturity, you name it. Each had wanted to flower in a different way.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_9">Which of those two would you want?</text>
  <text id="day3_selection1">I wish for the company to prosper.</text>
  <text id="day3_selection2">I wish to mature my spirit.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_1_1">Your future is determined by what you do at this moment.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_1_2">Currently, you work for Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_1_3">In our company, you will see things that cannot be seen, and you will feel things that cannot be felt. You shall do impossible things.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_1_4">May your wish be granted.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_1_5">Perhaps you will become the best manager I have seen yet.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_1">…</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_2">Come to think of it, there was another manager who gave me such an answer.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_3">As you know, “spiritual” is a rather obsolete term in today’s world.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_4">So I asked them for the definition of spirit.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_5">Then that manager told me…</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_6">Well, I unfortunately do not recall the details of that conversation.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_2_7">Even an AI cannot store every bit of data. Unnecessary information should be deleted for smooth operation.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_3_1">So, you may be asking yourself if your predecessors managed to fulfill their wish.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_3_2">Hm, I suppose what happened to the others is not important, after all.</text>
  <text id="day3_angela_3_3">I do promise to cheer you on for the journey to your final goal, though.</text>
</localize>