<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day22 start -->
  <text id="day22_a">&lt;b&gt;To the new manager:&lt;/b&gt;&#13;&#10;I’ve heard that you are a very valuable asset to the corporation, contributing greatly to the prosperity of our company. I ask that you please keep up the good work with your capable assistant, Angela. You will not find me in this place at the moment, but I believe we will be able to come face to face soon. Lobotomy Corporation will never forget your devotion and effort.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&lt;i&gt;I look forward to meeting with you. Kind regards,&#13;&#10;A, CEO of Lobotomy Corporation.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  
  <text id="day22_a_1">To the new manager:</text>
  <text id="day22_a_2">I’ve heard that you are a very valuable asset to the corporation, contributing greatly to the prosperity of our company. </text>
  <text id="day22_a_3">I ask that you please keep up the good work with your capable assistant, Angela. </text>
  <text id="day22_a_4">You will not find me in this place at the moment, but I believe we will be able to come face to face soon.</text>
  <text id="day22_a_5">Lobotomy Corporation will never forget your earnest devotion and effort.</text>
  <text id="day22_a_6">I look forward to meeting with you. Kind regards, A, CEO of Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_1">You’ve received a document written by A himself?</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_2">Perhaps you’re being recognized now.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_3">A is on a rather long journey currently.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_4">As all journeys have to end, the final destination will be home; this place.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_5_r1">Sometimes, I imagine myself on a journey too.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_5_r2">Have you ever taken a trip somewhere?</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_5_r3">If I were to ever leave this place, traveling is the first thing I would want to do.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_5_r4">Perhaps human life in itself is one long journey?</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_6_r1">Accumulating memories while looking at a world I have never seen before.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_6_r2">In fact, they say preparing for a trip is a rare luxury nowadays. </text>
  <text id="day22_angela_6_r3">I’d be able to walk around as much as possible, taking in the scenery as if I were capturing a million photos.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_6_r4">Could this moment be a part of your journey as well?</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_7">The day still lies cold, but we know that the winter frost is almost over.</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_8_r1">Can you see the flowers budding up through the snow?</text>
  <text id="day22_angela_8_r2">This winter was much colder than usual. </text>
  <text id="day22_angela_8_r3">However, the end of winter does not necessarily mean that spring is coming.</text>
</localize>