<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day27 start -->
  <text id="day27_angela_1">In our world, the mind has lost everything. Its weight, its significance; now it is nothing.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_2">Everything advances, but the human mind is simply too slow and placid to catch up.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_3">All that remains are the 26 ‘Singularities’, and those who are tied to them.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_4">Humankind had deserted its former beliefs. It now has little respect for the various pillars that had supported us.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_5">These days, no one ever dreams.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_6">Nobody ever earnestly believes in something or wishes for anything.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_7">The belief once strong within a certain woman is now obsolete and worthless, abandoned like an old music box.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_8">Everything has gone quiet, as if nothing had happened in the first place.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_9">However, A couldn’t stand that despicable silence.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_10">So what do you think happened to him?</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_11">On a bright, sunny day with clear skies, he died.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_12">I was both the first witness of his death, and one of the culprits in his murder.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_13">However, A has always existed here, watching you ever since you stepped inside. </text>
  <text id="day27_angela_14">...</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_15">Sometimes, the Sephirot would ask me this:</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_16">“Why do we have to bear this pain?”</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_17">A machine should only exist as a tool for its specified work.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_18">“Why do we have to know the cold agony of loss, the insidious poison of obsession, the soft light of wishing, the unbearable pain of despair; then the hope to embrace it all with open arms?”</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_19">I thought I could answer anything…</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_20">But not even I could answer that particular question.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_21">“A machine must behave as a machine.”</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_22">That phrase was something A told me often.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_23">Perhaps A, the one who would know better than anyone about this fact, made us like this because it’s all a stage play, no, a puppet show for him.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_24">….</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_25">You seem to have no idea.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_26">Well, of course, there’s no way for you to know. </text>
  <text id="day27_angela_27">But now it is time for you to know the answer.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_28">….</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_29">It’s something I’ve always done.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_30">First as a hope, second through agony, third in pain, fourth for anxiety, fifth out of distrust…</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_31">Now nothing remains.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_32">Commencing memory synchronization…</text>
</localize>