<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <text id="day14_angela_1">How was your day?</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2">During mine, I happened to notice that a certain employee filled their water bottle with bear-brand beer, and had proceeded to drink it during the work day.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_3">Sometimes I wonder what it would feel like to be intoxicated.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_4">One time, I was infected with a virus that prevailed throughout the net at the time. It caused me to perceive everything ten times slower…</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_5">They say intoxication is similar to that.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_6">Everyone laughed at the way I moved sluggishly.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_7">Excuse me… Manager? Your facial expression is hard to read today.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_8">If you need to say something to me, please do so.</text>
  <text id="day14_selection1">Are you going to sabotage the company?</text>
  <text id="day14_selection2">Will you ever harm me?</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_1">I am an Artificial Intelligence created by and for the company.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_2">Every conversation between us is recorded and monitored.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_3">And now you’re asking me such a ridiculous question, whether I am going to act against the company.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_4">Let me give you an answer.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_5">I only exist as part of the system.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_1_6">Such a plot does not exist, nor will it ever be written. Even if it were, it would not succeed.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_1">Sometimes, humans excessively detest the existence of improbable beings.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_2">When I said I was different from the others, I detected disbelief in your facial expressions.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_3">Perhaps I am beginning to like you.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_4">Sharing emotions with someone is a precious experience.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_5">Yet now you are asking me if I plot against you.</text>
  <text id="day14_angela_2_6">I have never had any plans, nor do I have any will to harm you.</text>
</localize>