<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- day40 start -->
  <text id="day40_angela_1">…...</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_2">Oh, I was recalling the sound of your footsteps.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_3">While there were clichés, you sometimes made the results more exciting by acting in unexpected ways.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_4">Still, the endings were all the same, no matter how the process went.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_5">Do you want me to share some memories through a hologram? It’s simply too good for me to watch alone.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_6">This here was you in a mess when there was no such thing as a cognition filter.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_7">I didn’t know that a human’s mental capacity could be so weak back then. You did alright the first couple of times, but then, one day…</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_8">Well, at that time, it was a little funny. I’m sorry. You made it so far, but you weren’t able to escape from that absolutely useless sense of guilt and hung yourself. Well, you were stopped immediately though.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_9">Then, at this time, you were not fully prepared. </text>
  <text id="day40_angela_10">That’s when I started to realize that it didn’t matter if you were mentally whole or not. What mattered was that you needed to find “realization” about something to stop this endless cycle.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_11">Oh, at this time here, all of a sudden you began apologizing to me. That was… I didn’t enjoy it.</text>
  <text id="day40_selection1">&lt;i&gt;I’ll continue watching.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="day40_selection2">Can you stop the holograms, please?</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_1_1">Are you starting to enjoy this?</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_1_2">I would love to see more, but let’s stop here for today.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_1_3">You might see something that you’re not supposed to witness yet if we continued.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_2_1">Is it difficult?</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_2_2">Please understand, you should know that I don’t have much entertainment that I can enjoy.</text>
  <text id="day40_angela_2_3">Really, you should have left me something to pass the time with.</text>
</localize>