<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- intro 뒤에 붙는 ta는 티페리트a 이고 tb는 티페리트b 입니다. 둘은 쌍둥이라는 설정입니다. 티페리트 a는 여성 어린아이이며 티페리트 b는 남성어린아이입니다.-->
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta1">Heya, manager. I’m Tiphereth!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb1">Nice to meet you. I’m Tiphereth, too.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_selection1">Are you two twins?</text>
  <!--선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_selection2">Do you two share the same name?</text>
  <!--선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta1_1">Of course we are, isn’t it obvious? We’re twins.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1번을 고른 경우 -->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb1_1">But if your question is whether we are biological twins, then no.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta1_2">In other words, trying to differentiate us is meaningless.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta2_1">Of course we are, isn’t it obvious? We’re twins.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2번을 고른 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb2_1">But if your question is whether we are biological twins, then no.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta2_2">In other words, trying to differentiate us is meaningless.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta2">We’re in charge of the Central Command Team. The department for Central Command is a huge one, so there are two of us to handle everything.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb2">Like two peas in a pod.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta3">Isn’t that fortunate?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta4">Seeing as you’ve survived your duties long enough to meet with us, I won’t have to bore the both of us with the basics of things like what Abnormalities are and how to manage them, right?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta5">If you turn out to be a disappointment, know that not even your status as the manager will let you get away with it.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb3">I know you’ll do fine, manager.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta6">Here’s a word of advice. I’m nothing like those Upper Sephirot you’ve gotten used to, so don’t treat me like I’m one of them. They’re a bunch of idiots.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb4">But in technical aspects, we’re not so different.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta7">What I’m trying to say is, the Uppers are only good at pretending to be busy when they don’t even have much work to begin with. I can’t even believe we’re all considered to be Sephirot!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta8">Hmph. Anyways, the Central Command Department is where the true story starts. I don’t care if it disappoints you or gives you encouragement, all I care about is that you have good performance in your work.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb5">I hope that you’ll find some encouragement here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_n1">Hey, Tiphereth.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 네짜흐-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta9">…..</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb6">Hi, Netzach.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_n2">Since you’re both Tiphereth, I guess that counts as you both greeting me... Here’s the plan for the joint operation drill between the Safety Team and the Central Command Team tomorrow. Please look it over.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta10">Look it over? I bet I’ll have to rewrite the entire thing from scratch!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb7">Just leave it over there, Netzach. I’ll give it a review and let you know.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta11">Tiphereth, you’re too soft. There’s no need to be kind to an addict like Netzach, you might end up catching “Upper Layer Syndrome” that way. Speaking of, that plan of yours came two days later than I requested!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb8">But Netzach can work fine when he’s motivated to. You know that.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta12">Results are not the problem here. The point is, Lady Angela is way too easy on us. If I were her, I would have punished this addict right at the first infraction.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_n3">That’d please Yesod alright. Why don’t you two go and have some serious discussion on implementing a penalty point system? I bet it’ll be productive…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta13">Oh, just be quiet! Buzz off to that Upper Layer of yours where you belong.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_n4">I was about to. See ya, Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb9">Yeah, bye Netzach.</text>
  <!-- 네짜흐 퇴장-->
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta14">Huff. The Upper Sephirot have it way too easy. Not that the Middle Sephirot are any better in my eyes…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb10">I like our Middle Sephirot, they’re cheerful and make me laugh!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta15">How many times do I have to tell you? You shouldn’t laugh so easily. We have to be strict, stern, and stoic! We’re the centermost, the Central Command Team!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb11">Don’t worry, Tiphereth, I know. By the way, don’t we have something to discuss with the manager?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta16">Oh, manager, you’re still here? Well, I have an assignment for you. Don’t even think about slacking off.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_tb12">The manager will do fine, like he always does.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth1_intro_ta17">And he could fail too, like he always does.</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta1">It seems the employees have become more talkative these days.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb1">They seem more motivated than usual. It’s rare to see such a lively atmosphere; it’s even getting me excited.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta2">“Lively” isn’t really the right word. It’s more like, excited over a trivial thing. All because of a new manager. That’s nothing special to us.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb2">Be more understanding, Tiphereth. This is Lobotomy Corporation. News is rare other than the usual word of someone’s death. The employees need something to talk about.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta3">Well, if it makes them more efficient at work for even a short time, then yes, I’ll be understanding. What I can’t get is why they’re so noisy about it all.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb3">Weren’t you excited the first time a new manager came in as well?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta4">Well—yes! Because it was the very first time!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb4">It’s still worth the excitement, even if it’s not the first time to happen.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb5">Do you remember? Back then, when we made a bet over whether the manager could save an employee who was at 95% mental corruption.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta5">Of course I remember. I bet that he couldn’t, and you placed your bet on them being saved.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb6">Yeah, though the employee died, unfortunately.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta6">I was so happy with my victory, I insisted on keeping up our bets, even though the result always ended up the same.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb7">Right, but then you stopped making the bets at one point.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta7">Well, because you always lost. Winning wasn’t fun anymore.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb8">I never bet without thinking it through, though. I always placed my hope in him, thinking: “Maybe this time”.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_ta8">It’s a shame that you never got to win once.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb9">Well, maybe if we had infinite time, I guess a day would come when my hopes could come true.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb10">What do you think, manager?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_selection1">I could hedge on it happening.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth2_selection2">Don’t bet on a pipe dream.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb1_1">I agree with you, manager.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1번 고른 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb1_2">Perhaps the bet could have turned out differently if we’d met sooner.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb2_1">Even if you say so, I still want them to live.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2번 고른 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth2_intro_tb2_2">I’ve always had faith in you, and I still trust you to save them one day.</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
    <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb1">…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb2">If you’re looking for Tiphereth, she’s still at the Middle Layer meeting.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb3">…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb4">I’m bad at holding conversations. I kinda miss the managers who were more talkative at times like this.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb5">Hey, there’s something I wanted to ask.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb6">Have you noticed that someone’s memory and emotion bleeds and seeps out of us?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb7">As you’ve seen, we act angry, feel happy, want things, and look sad, even though we’re machines.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb8">We even have our own weaknesses.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb9">Why is that? What’s inside of us?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb10">If “something” is really inside us, then why? Why make something imperfect, planting weakness?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb11">I tried to find the answer…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb12">But I really couldn’t get it.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb13">I’m sure you have that answer.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb14">Locked away somewhere in your memory.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb15">Maybe there’s a reason why there has to be imperfection?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb16">We’re machines, yet, not machines…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb17">Not… machines…</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 b 기계 과부하 상태-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta1">Hey, are you two having fun without me?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta2">...</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta3">Tiphereth, it’s troublesome to have a conversation that’s this fun.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a1">It appears it is time for another replacement. The cycle is getting shorter and shorter.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta4">But it can be rebuilt anytime we need, right?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a2">Well, it’s still an asset to the corporation, so I would prefer not to have it go to waste.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a3">Tiphereth, perhaps we should explain it to the manager first.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta5">Huh, why?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a4">I’ve told you, Tiphereth, the human mind is a fragile thing. It’s not capable enough to perceive the existence of beings like us in our wholeness.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta6">I mean, it’s not that gross. It’s nothing compared to, like, decapitating an employee, or slicing open their torso with their guts spilling out.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a5">Humans are susceptible to the unknown. The scene doesn’t always have to be graphic to break the mind.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta7">Ugh… there’s so much to be mindful of…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta8">Why can’t they just replace managers with machines? We could simply replace them whenever they try to do something stupid, like how we replace Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_a6">Tiphereth, there are things only humans are able to take care of. The founder of Lobotomy Corporation must have had a reason for assigning a human manager.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta9">Well then… off we go to “storage”. That’s one of the few locations where the Cognition Filter is weakened.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb18">I know that place.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta10">Tiphereth, what are you talking about? It’s where we always go during work.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb19">I don’t mean that.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_tb20">I remember what happened there last time.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta11">…..</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta12">You do? That’s great.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth3_intro_ta13">Thank you for helping me, like you always do.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a1">Manager, how do the Sephirot appear to you?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a2">You must see them as humans, just like yourself.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a3">Irritation, smiles, desire, and frowns color their faces… A range of emotions much more human than myself, perhaps.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a4">However, are you aware of a key fact?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a5">If there were to be any AI in this place that would be sophisticated enough to be considered as a human in terms of appearance…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a6">Only I would fit that criteria.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a7">Haven’t I been telling you since the beginning?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a8">I am the one and only truly superb AI here.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a9">To witness the essence of things is not at all important in this place.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a10">All that you see is distorted and filtered quite heavily.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a11">“Everything here is constructed just for you.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a12">Perhaps you could understand it better, if I put it that way.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta1">I won’t have to introduce myself again, will I?</text>
  <!-- 플레이어에게 더 이상 사람이 아닌 기계로 보이게 된 티페리트 a-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a13">Here is Tiphereth, whom you should already know.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_selection1">Are you really Tiphereth?</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta1_1">What kind of stupid question is that? Who do you think it would be otherwise?</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1번 고를 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta2_1">It looks like you’re surprised, but I’m sure we already told you several times that we’re machines.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2번 고를 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta2">That dumbfounded expression never ceases to amuse me.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta3">To tell you the truth, this part is usually where it gets boring, but that great expression of yours does give me a chuckle.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta4">You don’t happen to think I’m the only one, right? Every Sephirah you’ve seen is just like me, and the same goes to the Sephirot you’ll meet in the future. </text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta5">All thanks to that stupid “AI Ethics Amendment”.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta6">Next, here is…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta7">The place where we were born, and where we will return to someday.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta8">Maybe, after everything is over, we will rest here, singing the song of our hometown.</text>
  <!-- 프레셔가 내려와서 티페리트 b를 뭉갠다.-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta9">I hope your next version will last longer, Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_a14">Well then, Tiphereth, I will send the next one over whenever he’s ready.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta10">Thank you, Lady Angela.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm1">So this is where everyone was! It took me long enough to find you guys, since you weren’t at the meeting room.</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta11">What’s happening, Malkuth?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm2">Netzach asked me to fetch a document from the other Tiphereth!</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta12">Oh, I’m afraid it’s not ready yet. Something urgent turned up. And make sure to tell Netzach that he should show up himself next time.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm3">Well, Netzach said he’s a bit busy. I’ll tell him to visit you another time then!</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta13">Why are you Uppers all the same? Netzach isn’t busy at all! He just doesn’t want to move!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm4">But I’m having fun with this errand!</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm5">Oh, you’re replacing Tiphereth right now. Looks like the cycle’s getting shorter. It must be concerning, Tiphereth!</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tta14">Don’t worry about me, just be mindful of your notebook! It looks like it’ll fall apart to shreds at any moment by the looks of it.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_mm6">Oh, it is! Thanks for your concern. It was a pleasure to see you too, manager!</text>
  <!-- 화자  말쿠트-->
  <!-- 장소 이동-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tb1">…</text>
  <!-- 교체 된 새로운 티페리트 b-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tb2">Nice to meet you. I’m Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta1">You can skip the introductions, Tiphereth. Right now, it’s time for you to examine the plan Netzach gave us.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_tb3">All right.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta2">....</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_selection3">He seemed to want to say something to me.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_selection4">What happens to him now?</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_1">What would a broken machine have to say, anyways?</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1번 고른 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_2">Tiphereth is overloaded.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_3">He did seem to have some issues from the beginning…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_4">But it’s only gotten worse with time.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_5">We have been replacing the machine often, resetting it and leaving only a small portion of the data intact.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta3_6">Yet the same error always occurs at the same point.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_1">What do you mean, “What happens to him now?”</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2번 고른 경우-->
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_2">Ah, are you talking about the machine we just discarded?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_3">New errors could pop up if the old one is not completely terminated.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_4">And that’d be very troublesome on my end.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_5">While “I” am in charge of Central Command, there are two of us at the same time. </text>
  <text id="tiphereth4_intro_ta4_6">I always feel like I need more than “two” of me around here.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <!-- ta1은 티페리트 a를 지칭하며 ta2는 티페리트 b를 지칭합니다. -->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta1">I wanna go home…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb1">Sister, we probably aren’t going to go back to our old house anymore. Try to think of this place as your new home.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta2">How can you even call this place home? It’s too different from our real home, and there’s no mom…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb2">Well… What if we said Carmen was our new mom then?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta3">No…. This isn’t the same at all…. Let me go home, please….</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta4">Enoch, why do you keep trying to participate in those weird experiments?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta5">You know we don’t have to.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta6">Besides, Carmen told us that we didn’t have to worry about anything here, too.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb3">Of course, it’d be really fun to spend time with you here, without a care in the world.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb4">Sometimes I imagine a future like that.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb5">It would be a very happy one.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb6">But, how would we be able to find meaning in our lives there?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb7">There are children abandoned in the Outskirts who are dying every day.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb8">We were only able to live on thanks to an unexpected turn of events.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb9">Settling for simple comfort in this place is not what I was born to do.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb10">And it shouldn’t be, either.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta7">Your words are too hard for me. Why do you have so many thoughts on your mind?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta8">They say too much thinking might make you a weird person.</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb11">You know, Lisa, I think I’ve always been sad.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb12">I never loved my own life for even a second.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb13">How nice would it be to live in a happy world next time?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta9">Enoch… Are you hurt?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb14">No, it doesn't hurt one bit.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb15">Please don’t be sad. I know something good will happen next time.</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 b 죽음--><!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a1">It seems you’re awake.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a2">You are in Lobotomy Corporation, and I am the one who woke you. The both of you are “Tiphereth”.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a3">You will be working as my assistants, helping me with amazing work from here on out.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta10">Why do we have the same name?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a4">Because there is no point in distinguishing between you two.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb16">Hi, nice to meet you, Tiphereth.</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta11">I keep making silly mistakes, Tiphereth…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb17">Don’t worry, I’ll help you. I’m sure you’ll be fine on your own pretty soon.</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta12">We made it so far! The other Sephirot wouldn’t have dreamed of working this fast!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta13">We might be even better partners than we thought!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb18">Yeah, I think so too.</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb19">I wonder, why do we “exist” here?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta14">Why do you worry about that? We’re a part of the Central Command Department, and we’re sitting on a mountain of work to do. We just need to focus on the task at hand.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb20">We’re radically different from normal machines.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb21">I think about you, and you think about me. We both ponder about things, feel pain, and recognize our own existence. There must be some reason for it.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta15">Be careful, Tiphereth. If Miss Angela finds out you're wondering about things like that, she won’t be happy about it…</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta16">Lady Angela, what will happen to Tiphereth?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a5">Apart from the fact that his condition is abnormal, his excessive questioning will affect the manager’s duties as well.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a6">Since this behavior is unacceptable under any circumstances, I’ll have to reset him to the default status now.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a7">Don’t worry, you’ll be alright. You are simply going back to your first day at the company.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta17">But, Lady Angela… Tiphereth has spent so much time with me…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a8">You’re really starting to act like a child now, Tiphereth. Why don’t you say your goodbyes then? Though, you two will meet again soon anyway.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta18">Tiphereth, Tiphereth, I’m sorry… Tiphereth…..</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb22">Why are you crying, Tiphereth?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta19">I’m sorry, I couldn’t do anything for you…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb23">Please don’t be sad. I know something good will happen next time.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta20">Yeah…</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름), 다시 현재 (관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta21">You’re here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta22">Sometimes, I spend my time here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta23">It makes me think about a lot of things.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta24">…......</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta25">Tiphereth always looked at the world one step ahead of me.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta26">He was seeing his own world that I will never come to know.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta27">We were always next to each other, but in reality, we were never truly together.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta28">Do you know that feeling of missing someone, even though they’re standing right beside you?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta29">I don’t care at all about the meaning or purpose of existence that Tiphereth talked about.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta30">I just wanted the two of us to happily stay here together. That was all.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta31">But this place won’t allow us to have even that small luxury.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta32">There are countless of Tiphereth’s dead bodies piled up here, can’t you see?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta33">I’m standing here stepping on their remains.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta34">Trampling over all the memories, reminiscences, and time that I spent with Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta35">I’m standing on top of it right now, but I still don’t get it. I still can’t reach the world Tiphereth saw.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta36">I sing the song of our hometown and mourn for Tiphereth even though this will never reach him.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta37">Care to join me?</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 b 등장-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb24">Tiphereth, what are you doing here?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta38">Just reminiscing on old memories.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb25">What memories?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta39">The good old days, when we were together.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb26">You’re right, we had lots of fun together.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta40">….</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_tb27">Come back to me soon, Tiphereth. I’ll be reading the rest of the report.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta41">I will.</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (과거회상 잠깐)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta42">You can replace the machine and transfer the key memories all you want, but that still won’t bring back the Tiphereth I knew!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a9">Does that really matter, though? Tiphereth will continue to smile at you, and he’ll spend time with you just like before.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_a10">Kindly refrain from bringing up such wasteful matters, Tiphereth. It’s completely meaningless here.</text>
  <!-- 화자: 앤젤라--><!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름), 다시 현재 (관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta43">...…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta44">I don’t really like you.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta45">The new manager would always have some kind of influence on Tiphereth, and that would eventually lead to yet another breakdown.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta46">It will be the same, time and time again.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta47">We will discard Tiphereth again and again, and he will stray further and further from what he used to be.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta48">What I’m scared of most is seeing Tiphereth burn to a husk, worn down from all those overloads and resets.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta49">For now, he can at least look normal and talk with me, pretending to feel nostalgia for the old memories that were forcefully added back.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta50">But he’s been getting more and more unstable, as a matter of fact. We’re basically pumping electricity into a machine that’s already teetering to keep it running.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta51">You can make as many copies as you want of his body, but he only has one soul.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta52">His one and only soul, and look what we’ve done to it…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta521">………....</text>
  <!-- 중간에 껴놓은거라서 번호 이상함.-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta53">You, let me ask you a favor.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta54">You’ve been good at doing favors for me so far. You should be able to manage this one.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta55">Could you get rid of Tiphereth, permanently?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta56">Angela would say that there’s a reason for the two of us working here together. She’d say that we are two, yet one.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta57">But I can handle the Central Command Department all by myself. I proved myself a long time ago.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta58">Please let Tiphereth rest in peace, as if I were alone from the beginning, before it gets any worse.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_selection1">&lt;i&gt;I can’t respond.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <!-- 선택지 한개-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta59">Why aren’t you saying anything?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta60">In fact, Lady Angela doesn’t care about us at all!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta61">Whether there’s one Tiphereth or two, whether one just became a moving piece of useless scrap for whatever reason, or if one were overloaded and dumped on top of countless other discarded Tiphereth, left to melt in the storage, she wouldn’t care!</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta62">But you’re different, you’re supposed to be different!</text>
  <!-- 화면 전환 (A의 시점)-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A1">There were many abandoned children in the Outskirts.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A2">These children were one of the many end results of the countless conflicts among the Wings within the City.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A3">Aside from disease and hunger, the most frightening enemy for the children were the ones referred to as the ‘Sweepers’.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A4">The Sweepers usually preyed upon the children, but sometimes they would “accompany” them. Both were worst case scenarios for the children.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A5">One Fixer of ours was exploring the Outskirts and came across those children.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A6">We could easily guess why she bothered to report her findings to us.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A7">We also figured that she had spent quite a bit of time agonizing over whether to report it or not.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A8">Carmen personally asked her to bring the children here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A9">To take two children into the City from the Outskirts required an extremely complicated procedure, but no one complained.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A10">The two children didn’t look like siblings, but they depended on each other even more so than siblings by blood do.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A11">The girl was easily frightened and wouldn’t open up very much to us.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A12">However, the boy started to show interest in our experiment.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A13">I saw it in his eyes.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A14">He had already seen and experienced so much of this world’s despair and misfortune; his eyes no longer looked like those of a child.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A15">“Please allow me to participate in the experiment,” he said.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A16">Carmen spent many nights thinking about his earnest request.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A17">Then finally, we…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_selection2">Approved his participation.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_selection3">Approved his participation.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_selection4">Approved his participation.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A18">Where did we want to go while holding a child’s hand?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_ta63">You should’ve been the one to die…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_c1">Yeah… I— I should have died…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A19">Lisa’s vicious mumbling likely had no weight to it, but I knew one thing.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A20">I knew Carmen’s answer was sincere.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth5_intro_A21">Ever since that day, her wound quietly deepened.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta1">Enoch?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta2">Have you ever heard of the Nest?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta3">I hear they throw a festival every single day there.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta4">I wanna dance, Enoch.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta5">I wanna stomp my feet and let happiness take over my body.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb1">Lisa, if you take a bit of time to look around here, it’s quite nice too.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta6">But we aren’t allowed to go anywhere. Carmen just wants to keep us confined here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb2">She’s a good person. I hope you’ll open up to her soon.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta7">I don’t want to get to know anyone else, all I want is to be with you.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb3">I can’t promise to be next to you forever.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb4">There’s a lot of things that I’ve been mulling over for quite some time, and I thought I may find some answers for them here.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb5">Some of my thoughts may be so absurd that the answers to them might not exist at all.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb6">Or, even if the answers do exist, they might vanish too soon...</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb7">But, in the process of searching for those answers, I will be able to cast off my shell.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb8">Then I can fly away at last, leaving my heavy body behind...</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta8">Sometimes, I have no idea what you’re talking about.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta9">I don’t know where you want to go, but promise that you’ll take me with you, Enoch.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb9">…….</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta10">Oh, A is here, so I guess we gotta go now.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta11">It’s gonna get dark and cold soon. Let’s head inside.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb10">Yeah, soon… Soon cold days will come…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A1">Even though I never had thought of them as family or someone that I needed to care for…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A2">I made it my job to bring the children back home, to ease Carmen’s busy schedule.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A3">I see them.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A4">Those young kids running towards me.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A5">Those children who survived the Outskirts.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_A6">The two we saved.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <!-- 화면 전환 (시간의 흐름), 다시 현재 (관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta12">I thought I could do it all on my own.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta13">I wanted to show Tiphereth how mature I became when he got back one day.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta14">But there was no end to the disappointment, and Tiphereth never got any better.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta15">I couldn’t stand the silence without an answer.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta16">So I thought.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta17">I thought that I’d rather…</text
  ><text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta18">That I’d rather hide my disgust and guilt I was so used to, as if the feelings never existed in the first place.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta19">But whenever I see Tiphereth’s empty smile, my heart feels as if it were being covered in dark ash, while shattered into millions of pieces.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta20">I knew Tiphereth could never go back to how he used to be.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta21">I was aware that we could never return to the happy days we spent together.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta22">But I was about to abandon Tiphereth just because it was too hard for me to endure…</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta23">All while knowing that he was the one who suffered the most…</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 b 등장-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb11">Tiphereth, are you done with all of your busywork?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta24">.............</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb12">We’re going to be late. Let’s get going, the sun will set soon.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_tb13">Please hurry, Lisa.</text>
  <!-- 티페리트 b 퇴장-->
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta25">Right, my name was Lisa once.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta26">Tiphereth doesn’t remember his name anymore, but from time to time he calls me by my cast-off name.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta27">What did Tiphereth want out of all this, even after sacrificing himself?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta28">What was he waiting for, even when he was being discarded?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta29">Was it all worth it to him?</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta30">I don’t know.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta31">I’ve never, ever held any expectations in my life.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta32">But, I’ll try counting on you now.</text>
  <text id="tiphereth6_intro_ta33">I want to believe that there’s a reason for every sacrifice that was made, and to know that eventually, everything will be okay.</text>
</localize>