<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_h1">Oh, umm… Hi…</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h2">.....</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h3">You’re not angry, are you...?</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h4">I’m Hod. I’m in charge of the Training Team.</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h5">We’re… um… what we do is... You know accidents happen in the company.</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h6">But Lady Angela said that about half of those accidents could be easily prevented if the employees showed… more initiative.</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h7">So the Training Team provides employees with a work manual and sufficient training. You know, to try and reduce the number of accidents. We also help employees that are transferring to different departments in adapting to their new workplace…</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h8">Umm, I’m not very skillful in many areas, but I’ll try not to be a hindrance, at least...!</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h9">In fact, I’ve been testing out a new employee program these days…</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h10">I don’t know if it will work out, but… umm...</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h11">Oh, you want to know more about the program?</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h12">As you know, the company is… quite demanding. Even though we run consistent check-ups, many of our employees regularly lose their sanity…</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h13">I know exactly what it’s like.</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h14">I mean, I don’t directly interact with the Abnormalities, but I know what it feels like to lose yourself...</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h15">I’m not sure if employees will like my new program, or if it will prove to be helpful... I can only hope…</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_no">(You and Hod hear a knock at the door)</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_t1">It’s all thanks to you, Miss Hod. I feel so much better after talking to you as you suggested. I’m finally free from all those horrible thoughts that used to haunt me every morning.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 티파니 직원-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_h16">No, no, it was your courage to bare your heart to me that really solved the problem. I just showed you where to start. </text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_t2">I mean it. I’d have probably hung myself by now if it wasn’t for you. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 티파니 직원-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_t3">Anyway, Miss Hod, you really did save my life. I’m so fortunate to have you as my Sephirah. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 티파니 직원-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_t4">You’re a really, really good person.  </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 티파니 직원-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_h17">….! Thank you, Tiffany! I’m so glad to see you getting better. I heard you’ll be transferring to a different team soon, I hope you do well there. Please make sure to not forget the conversations we had. </text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_t5">Of course, miss. I won’t.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 티파니 직원-->
  <text id="hod1_intro_h18">You see that, manager? My program’s really working!</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h19">I want to be as helpful a person I can be here.</text>
  <text id="hod1_intro_h20">Because, the harder I try, the more lives I can save...</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h1">Thank you so much for doing that favor for me, manager!</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_h2">I’ve been feeling really confident lately!</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a1">Hod, I hear you have a new distraction.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h3">Ah, Lady Angela! Are you talking about my counseling program? Thank you!</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a2">Yes, shut it down immediately.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h4">But, why? My program has been helping the employees…</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a3">Don’t delude yourself, Hod. You don’t sincerely believe that counseling can be of any help in this place, do you?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h5">But… But I want to continue it... As long as there’s an employee who needs me… What about Tiffany? She… she said my program helped her cope with her stress…</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a4">Tiffany? Tiffany Brown, who recently transferred to the Safety Team? She was suffering from bipolar disorder and an addiction to Enkephalin. We expunged her records this morning.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h6">She… what?</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a5">She has terminated her contract with the company in a completely permanent fashion. Her mental corruption was at peaks higher than 90% when she committed suicide.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a6">I bet she said something like this whenever she came to you:</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a7">“Miss Hod, you’re helping me so much! But I think I’ll need a bit of Enkephalin on top of your counseling to ease my melancholy! It’s just a little extra, of course...”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a8">You prescribed highly addictive substances as if you were handing out candy to children.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h7">....</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a9">And what about Netzach? You gave him the substance as well. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a10">I temporarily gave you access to Enkephalin because I determined you could use it for your “counseling program” to reduce the stress level of the employees, and yet you’ve only been creating drug addicts.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h8">Netzach… He told me that he wanted to introduce the program to his team…</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a11">And you fell for it? You should have noticed that he was lying as soon as you saw his hazy eyes.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_h9">....</text>
  <text id="hod2_intro_a12">Hod, your naive compassion is only driving things to become worse around here. Your program is hereby terminated.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a13">And as I have told you and the other Sephirot countless times: there is nothing as redundant and pointless as building a personal acquaintance with the employees here. Especially for a Sephirah like you.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="hod2_intro_a14">The employees will do anything to coax whatever they desire out of you. They have nothing left to lose; they won’t even feel any guilt about it.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_n1">Hod, please do me a solid… Angela somehow knows that I have the stuff.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 네짜흐-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_n2">I assure you, it’s just for counseling purposes.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 네짜흐-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_h1">Netzach, actually…</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_e2_1">I heard Eugene’s been forced into that counseling program.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 지나가는 직원 2-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_e1_2">This is ridiculous! That guy’s already got his hands full, and now he has to take her stupid counseling?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 지나가는 직원 1-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_e2_2">Poor Eugene. What can an employee do against a Sephirah’s orders, anyway?  </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 지나가는 직원 2-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_e1_3">I doubt she really cares about us. She’s just doing this to make herself feel superior!</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 지나가는 직원 1-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_e2_3">More work for us, I guess.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 지나가는 직원 2-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_n3">Just ignore them, Hod. They’re always so negative.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 네짜흐-->
  <text id="hod3_intro_h2">...</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h3">Could I have some of that, Netzach?</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h4">Oh, hey, manager. Congratulations on your success.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h5">Uh… well this is just for counseling, yeah.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h6">...</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h7">Why does everyone hate me?</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h8">Why won’t they appreciate my kindness?</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h9">I thought I was the nicest Sephirah who cared the most for the employees.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h10">The other Sephirot are so occupied with their own work that they don’t even care about how their subordinates end up.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h11">The corporation treats them as if they’re expendable resources.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h12">I’m different! I really do care about them!</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h13">I’m not a “Cold-blooded Machine” like Yesod.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h14">I’m not haphazard like Malkuth.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h15">And I’m definitely not a “oh-it-can’t-be-helped” person like Netzach.</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_h16">Just, why…</text>
  <text id="hod3_intro_x1">(Hod seems to be getting lost in her own thoughts.)</text>
  <!--에피소드 4-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_h1">Is it true, Tiffany...? All you wanted out of me was some Enkephalin?</text>
  <text id="hod4_intro_no1">“But you lied.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_h2">What lies? I’ve never lied to you…</text>
  <text id="hod4_intro_no2">“You always lie to us when we’re in a vulnerable state.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no3">“What’s the point of your ‘counseling’. The only one you’re trying to comfort with your lip service is yourself.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no4">“You thought that the momentary satisfaction could make you a better person?”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no5">“That’s not true, not at all.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no6">“No matter what you do, you’re never going to become a good person, and we’re all going to die in the end.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no7">“Feeding your ego through ‘kind’ acts makes you a better person?”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_no8">“You must be so hopelessly delusional to think that.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_h3">No…</text>
  <text id="hod4_intro_no9">“We will all die.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <text id="hod4_intro_h4">I want to be a good person…</text>
  <text id="hod4_intro_no10">“For what?”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 환청-->
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="hod5_intro_n1">Don’t worry, Hod, that’s a very common side effect when you first take Enkephalin.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n2">It’s just like a light hallucination.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n3">It’ll disappear after two or three times, so don’t worry about it too much.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n4">For me, it was an employee whose face had half melted. ‘Crawled over my feet and grabbed me by the shoulders, asking me why I let her die.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h1">That wasn’t a hallucination or anything...</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n5">Then what? Are you trying to say that dead employees are suddenly coming back to life?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h2">You know, like, unbelievable things happen here, so maybe it is possible for dead employees to come back, as if nothing happened, right?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n6">...I’m not in any state to say this, but you don’t look too good. Why don’t you skip today’s meeting?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h3">I can’t do that, we have an Abnormality Response Training today… They need me to run the drill properly…</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_n7">You’re really something, huh. I don’t think there’s another Sephirah here who cares about their employees as much as you do.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h4">...Right?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h5">Look, Tiffany… I was right….</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h6">I’m a good person… I’m a good Sephirah…</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h7">Hello everyone, today we will—</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no1">(“Are you still trying to play the ‘good Sephirah’?”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h8">—be focusing on Abnormality Response Training.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no2">(“How many times do I have to tell you? You’re only a sad piece of rusty scrap metal putting on the act of being a good person.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h9">Now, I want everyone to pay close attention here. The Abnormality we’ll suppress today needs to be handled a bit differently than the others.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no3">(“If you hoped that living such a lie would ease your conscience, that’s really selfish.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h10">Starting now, I will be explaining the method I devised. Please listen carefully.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no4">(“At least the other Sephirot are humble enough to admit that they’re not perfect.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h11">Quiet!</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h12">.........</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h13">Oh… Sorry… Where were we…</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e1_1">Excuse me, Miss Hod, I have a question.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h14">Yes, what is it?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e1_2">Do you think that this training will make any difference? I mean, against that Long Bird, it feels like whoever will die or live is all predetermined, and there’s nothing we can do to change it.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h15">….…Well, it should yield a better result than just doing nothing. At the very least, we can prepare a preventative measure rather than just wait helplessly to—</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e1_3">It’s just all about luck. We’d be better off and more comfortable to simply accept that we can die at any moment while working. </text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e1_4">A hunk of junk like you wouldn’t understand. In a critical situation, nothing really helps.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no5">(“Just know this.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no6">(“You won’t reach that paradise no matter what you do.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h16">I’m doing this all for you guys, even the counseling campaign…</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e2_1">Now that you mention it, that compulsory counseling campaign is such a pain. We’d rather have a break time instead.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_e3_1">Why is our department the only one that has to deal with these programs?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no7">(“It will keep repeating itself. Live with eternal sorrow and remorse in that metal mass.”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h17">Well, I—! …</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h18">All of you would be dead by now if I hadn’t helped you!</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h19">Why aren’t you thanking me?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h20">Do you want me to get rid of you like Malkuth does, before you even make the littlest complaint?!</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h21">Don’t you say that I’m the bad one here!</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no8">(“Are you finally admitting to your awful nature?”)</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h22">….Tiffany, why are you doing this to me?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no9">“I am not Tiffany, look at me.”</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_no10">Can’t you even distinguish your own voice anymore?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h23">.......</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_h24">Yes, are you still having that sweet nightmare?</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A1">When I read the article detailing Michelle’s suicide, it was just as our experiment was starting to show some progress.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A2">Michelle was the youngest among us. She was a timid and innocent employee.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A3">It made her an easy target. Maybe it was her fate to be used as a pawn of the Wings that were alert to us, or of the Head that would watch over us constantly.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A4">You likely didn’t know things would go the way they did. You’d never have thought that a puny kid like you would bring about our demise. You’d never have believed that the situation would end up so much worse than your intentions.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A5">You probably tried to comfort yourself in the end, telling yourself that you did the best you could. That in this world, in that moment, there wasn’t any other option for you.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A6">But Carmen was the person who was trying to change this world, the world you resigned yourself to.</text>
  <text id="hod5_intro_A7">If we meet again in hell, will I finally be able to forgive you?</text>
  <text id="hod5_selection1">Crumple up the newspaper.</text>
  <text id="hod5_selection2">Crumple up the newspaper.</text>
  <text id="hod5_selection3">Crumple up the newspaper.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="hod6_intro_a1">Do you believe that there is truly inexcusable behaviour?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_a2">Nobody is perfect.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_a3">If we realized that in forgiving others, your enemy didn’t deserve forgiveness but rather that you needed peace, would things be better?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A1">Are you sure you can really join our experiment in such an unstable situation?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A2">Michelle, let me cut to the chase; we are performing experiments that go directly against the Head’s ideals.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A3">If your beloved parents, or your precious friends try to coax you, are you confident that you’d be able to refuse them?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A4">.....</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A5">She wasn’t able to say anything to my browbeating. Carmen broke the silence instead.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_c1">Don’t be too harsh on her. She’s amazing to be here at such a young age!</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A6">Just like everyone else, Michelle liked Carmen. That was not trickery or a show. She wasn’t the manipulative sort of person who’d keep up such a facade, either.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A7">I should’ve made her give the answer she avoided speaking no matter what.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A8">Did Michelle receive what she wanted?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A9">I don’t know.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A10">Did she accomplish her purpose by trampling on us, and Carmen?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A11">I’ll never know.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A12">Do I have any right to bear hatred towards her?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A13">The answer was “no”. I was no different from her.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_A14">To be honest, I never wanted you to die in misery, like that nasty tabloid article gossiped.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h1">Were you able to successfully face yourself, manager?</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h2">When I awoke to find myself here, I thought this could be my second chance.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h3">I thought I could redeem myself and liberate myself from my mistakes.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h4">What I did can never be undone. A sunken pebble can never float to the surface again.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h5">I wanted to be a kind person. I wanted to show everyone that I might be okay here, somehow.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h6">Was I truly being considerate of others? Silly me, there’s no room for something like that here.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h7">I was a hypocrite, all those “nice” acts were for myself.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h8">I’ll keep trying to be a better person, even now.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h9">It may be specious, and some people may hate me for that, but as long as my efforts can save a person's life or give a person the consolation they need…</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h10">I will live on, with that pride as a stepping stone.</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h11">So, manager…</text>
  <text id="hod6_intro_h12">Let’s keep trying together, in this interminable hell.</text>
</localize>