<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_x1">(You can hear rushed footsteps from behind.)</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1">Manager, manager!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2">I arrived just on time, right? The time iiiiiis… only about one minute late. Well, I guess it still counts as “on time!”</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m3">Congratulations on joining Lobotomy Corporation, manager!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_a1">I do not want to disturb this touching moment, Malkuth, but every second counts in Lobotomy Corp. Please make your introduction as brief as possible and go prepare for the meeting.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m4">Hmm… Seems Miss Angela isn’t in a good mood today…</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m5">But hey, at least the other Sephirot are looking forward to meeting you!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m6">Well, maybe... not all of them…</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m7">Oh, where are my manners! My name is Malkuth! I’m in charge of the Control Team!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m8">Since we’re the Control Team, we have a great deal of responsibility!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m9">I’ll try my best to help you by improving the basic functions of this facility, manager!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m10">I’m sure you’re a bit nervous right now.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m11">It takes a bit of time to get used to things around here. I know from experience!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m12">But don’t worry, I’ll be sure to help you!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m13">I am, umm, not exactly the best at everything. I used to be a problem Sephirah, you know.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m14">I would sew buttons onto a shirt in the wrong direction, or add salt instead of sugar to food…</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m15">But still, you can do it! Just like I managed to, I’m sure you will succeed, manager!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m16">I’ll give you an easy task since it’s your first day here!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m17">I wish you the best of luck!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_x2">WHAMWHAMWHAMWHAM</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_e1">I can’t take it anymore! Manager, you’re in there, right?</text>
  <!-- 이 문단 수정함.-->
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_e2">I have to get out of here, please. I know you’re capable of it, you’re the manager! You’re not the same as the rest of us! You can do anything! </text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m18">Why do you want to quit? Don’t you like working here in the Control Team? Every day here is a delight for me!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_e3">It’s so horrible, I can’t take it anymore! I’ll go insane! Nothing here is normal! </text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m19">Do you really think you can’t handle it? </text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_e4">Please… I don’t want to be here… Let me out of here, please…</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m20">Manager, even though you’re the head of this facility, that employee belongs to my department, so I believe I can take care of this! Let me handle this, please!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_selection1">&lt;i&gt;I’ll let her handle it.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_selection2">&lt;i&gt;I should intervene.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1_1">Thanks for acknowledging my position!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1_2">Please don’t be alarmed! These kinds of things happen quite often.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1_3">Oh, right, it must be the first time you’ve seen something like this.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1_4">Usually Miss Angela or I handle this kind of stuff. </text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m1_5">It's just a tiny hiccup. Nothing for you to worry about!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_e5">No, please, manager! Please…!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_1">…</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_2">Then please keep this in mind, manager. </text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_3">Once they say they “can’t handle it,” they are no longer part of my Control Team.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_4">The Control Team is on the top of all the Sephirot, just like the central nervous system of a human being. If we go down, it’s only a matter of time until everyone else goes down too!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_5">At first, it was hard for me to get used to as well.</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_6">But I worked really, really hard!</text>
  <text id="malkuth1_intro_m2_7">So please don’t say something as meaningless as you “can’t handle it.”</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a1">There was a bit of a confusion last time, wasn’t there?</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a2">Usually, I am in charge of the security of your office.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a3">However, it seems that I failed to pay close enough attention to the Sephirah meeting room.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a4">I heard that a Control Team employee has “resigned” from the corporation.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a5">Good job. </text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a6">You do know what it means to “resign” here in the company, don’t you? </text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a7">…</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a8">I’ll take that as a no.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a9">I do sometimes miscalculate what information I should deliver to you and what I shouldn’t.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a10">Some aspects of our company that I considered natural and obvious may come as quite a shock to you.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a11">We have a variety of roles here. </text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a12">It’s like a well-structured play. Every actor has a role and they must be faithful to their part without any error, synergizing with each other.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a13">Now, imagine that one of the actors decides to leave the stage because they didn’t like their role. </text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a14">The actor should have played their predetermined part at the predetermined timing before making their exit stage left.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a15">But to leave the stage without fulfilling their part means that the life of the role and its actor are finished.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_a16">That is what we mean when we say someone “resigns”.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m1">Great job, manager! You did exactly what I asked of you!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m2">I knew you could do it!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m3">You’ll never guess how much I rooted for you back there.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m4">As for me, the day went alright; we covered a joint emergency-protocol drill for my team!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m5">Not a single dropout or injury!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m6">Everyone did a good job!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m7">Not to say that it was perfect, though. </text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m8">By the way, manager, have you seen something creepier than the Abnormalities?</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m9">Those entities that wander the facility, unable to be contained. And sometimes, they manifest themselves in the corridors.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m10">The drills do no good when you encounter them, since we don’t have enough data on them. So we always have to stay alert!</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m11">No matter how meticulous our plan is, we can’t control the unknown.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m12">Sometimes, when I encounter them, I get a strange feeling.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m13">It’s not like fear or anything… Some other sensation.</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m14">Strange, isn’t it? I feel nauseous, like something within me is palpitating out of control, and it feels… like I’m no longer myself...</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m15">How could I describe it? Like something’s wriggling inside of me…</text>
  <text id="malkuth2_intro_m16">Little... by little…</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m1">You did it again! And you did it flawlessly, too!</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m2">I myself have a lot of work to do.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m3">If you look at my notebook, my to-do list is always so full.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m4">But I know I can get through it. I should do my best. Like I always have!</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m5">I know I’m slower than the others.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m6">I always have to check my list or I’ll miss something important.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m7">That’s why I have this notebook with me all the time. Can’t leave any mistakes, you know?</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m8">I’ve been carrying it for so long that it’s almost worn out.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m9">It’s been with me ever since I began working here as the Sephirah of the Control Team.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m10">I know Lady Angela worries about me from time to time.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m11">But I’ve got everything under control.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m12">I feel like this is the kind of life I’ve been yearning for ever since a long, long time ago. Maybe even before I was capable of thinking.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m13">It feels as if I’ve wished for the same thing before, in some other place that wasn’t the Control Team…</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_a1">Malkuth, please finish the report I requested by the end of today.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m14">Sure thing boss! I’ve got it right here on my list. I’ll have it turned in by the end of the day!</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_m15">Well, I should get going now, it’s a pleasure talking to you, manager! </text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_a2">The AIs here, they’re all unstable… with the exception of me.</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_a3">It’s especially bad for Malkuth. You’ve noticed, haven’t you?</text>
  <text id="malkuth3_intro_a4">I can’t complain, though. It only makes it easier for me to control her.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_y1">We need to be honest here, Malkuth. You simply cannot suppress the Ordeals with the employees you currently have at your disposal.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_y2">Trust me, I am the head of the Information Team. Even if your team were to suppress the Ordeals on their own, there’s too great a risk of extreme mental damage to your employees.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m1">But Yesod, we only need to consider the mortality rate of the Agents and the possibility of the Abnormalities breaching.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_h1">Malkuth. Lady Angela’s said that one crazy employee will kill ten others...</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m2">I am the Sephirah of the Control Team.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m3">I may make outrageous mistakes in all other aspects, but this role I know better than anyone else.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m4">I know how to handle employees on the verge of insanity. I even wrote down a code of conduct for it.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m5">Honestly, it feels like I’m the only one who follows the guide. Am I wrong?</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m6">Please tell me if you happen to need it. I can always share a copy with you.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_h2">I— I’m fine, but that code of yours…</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m7">I don’t need weak employees in my department.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m8">Weakness means elimination, the death of your place in my department.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m9">To work for the Control Team, the department that leads the corporation, signifies that you should be more capable than everyone else.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m10">Manager, please say something to them.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m11">You’ve been watching what’s happened to those weak-willed employees from the comfort of your office, haven’t you?</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m12">Can any one of you guys say something?</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m13">.......</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m14">Well, thanks so much for visiting me! It’s made me so happy!</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_m15">We should meet up again sometime, all of us Upper Sephirot!</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_a1">I have an announcement to the Sephirot of the upper layer.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_a2">The mental corruption levels of the Control Team’s employees exceeded the maximum threshold. And just what did the other Sephirot do in the meantime? Sit and watch?</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_a3">The Control Team has failed to handle the Ordeals.</text>
  <text id="malkuth4_intro_a4">Supplement the staff immediately and suppress the Ordeals. I will ask for support from the other departments.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m1">Oh, hello ----, sir!</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m2">Sorry, I’m quite busy. I still haven’t finished even half of what I’ve written down in my notebook.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m3">..............</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m4">Hey, I heard extraction experiments are going to be conducted.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m5">When I looked over the list of participants, I couldn’t find my name on it.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m6">I mean, there’s probably a ton of reasons behind it, maybe I’m just not good enough for the experiment yet…</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m7">But, may I join the experiment too?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m8">.........</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m9">I’ve learned a lot here.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m10">I’m sure I can help you in some way.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m11">I’ll be sure to not disappoint!</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m12">Hello, manager!</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m13">.......</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m14">It’s sad to not have enough talent, isn’t it?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m15">If someone doesn’t look back towards you, what does that mean?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m16">That they don’t acknowledge you.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m17">That they don’t even care about what expression you may be making.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m18">That they feel no need to see what you’re doing, as they’ve already come to a conclusion.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m19">Have you ever clawed and scraped at the floor, writhing in pain?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m20">It really does sound excruciating.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m21">But in reality, the moment I completely lost my fingernails, I felt nothing.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m22">You stare at the flesh where your fingernails used to be, and just before you lose consciousness…</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m23">When you feel that you aren’t yourself anymore, you start to laugh frantically.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m24">Even though it’s not funny at all.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m25">And on the ground you catch a glimpse of someone’s shadow, and their feet as they look down on you.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m26">Guess whose feet those were.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m27">When the person who disliked looking back so much finally turned around, everything was over.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m28">Did you see the fragments of despair from there?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m29">Or were you staring at the bits of my fingernails scattered on the floor?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m30">That was the exact moment I knew true helplessness.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m31">Without you, I’d never have known the feeling. Thank you so much!</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m32">Now, what about you, manager?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m33">Have you ever felt helpless to control anything?</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m34">When unbearable things pour down from somewhere that isn’t your body and overwhelm you; it just feels so awful to be helpless, being out of control of yourself.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m35">….....</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m36">Come on, please tell me.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m37">So I can feel rewarded, just a bit.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A1">Elijah was impatient, and her impatience caused many common mistakes.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A2">She once went on a long, winding filibuster of why she needed to finish the experiment, but I don’t remember the details.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A3">Whenever she was told that she wasn’t ready yet, I could see the strong desire in her eyes. It was a craving, a bizarre obsession.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A4">If another person had been in my place, they may have turned around for the sound of her hasty footsteps.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A5">Cogito was something that she couldn’t access at her level of authority.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A6">The only task she was ordered to do was record the changes that occurred in the test subjects.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A7">She was aware that at the moment Cogito was absolutely not ready for human use.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_A8">When I finally realized what was going on, half her teeth had fallen out, and…</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_intro_m38">...ill me… Please… K— Kill me…</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_selection1">Ignore her.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_selection2">Ignore her.</text>
  <text id="malkuth5_selection3">Ignore her.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m1">Hello, A, sir!</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m2">I’m really, really glad to join this team!</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m3">I forgot to introduce myself! My name is ------! I’ll try my best to be helpful to the team!</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m4">Oh, I was writing a report. Where’d it get off to?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_A1">Nothing could be achieved through passion alone.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_A2">It was obvious what mistakes impatience could cause, so we needed to take our time.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_A3">The situation wasn’t bright enough for me to remember everyone’s name or personally respond to meaningless gestures.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_A4">It was only after a very long time that I realized giving praise once in a while may have been a good idea.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m5">.…......</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_selection1">Is everything alright?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_selection2">&lt;i&gt;I’ll say hello.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m6">You’re so silly.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m7">I think you confuse us for humans from time to time.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m8">I feel like I had a real dream for the first time in a while.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m9">The other Sephirot told me that I damaged the facility a lot.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m10">......</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m11">Have you ever felt it, manager?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m12">That feeling of sailing the ocean without a map or any kind of guidance.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m13">The feeling of groping blindly through a vast darkness.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m14">It feels like I’m an island on that vast ocean.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m15">I work in the Control Team.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m16">Nobody knows how much pressure it is to be in a position to command everyone else until they’ve truly tried it themselves.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m17">I’m sure you know how it feels, manager.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m18">Everything starts tumbling down on top of you when you start thinking you might not be able to handle it.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m19">Have you ever looked into the eyes of a dying employee?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m20">Don’t look away from them, saying that there’s nothing you can do for them.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m21">Don’t just be sorry for the dying sacrifices.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m22">Don’t blame yourself, thinking that you could have done better.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m23">Only after you can confront those moments as they are…</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m24">Will you be able to see other things.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m25">I saw you overcome unavoidable trials. Those of which probably originated from me.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m26">To be honest, I wasn’t sure you would make it.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m27">…Am I being too forward?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m28">We can’t change the past, I know.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m29">I don’t expect you to be a shining beacon or a lighthouse in the vast ocean, or that this place will suddenly become all peaceful and warm.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m30">But…</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m31">Maybe we can just try and wait, right?</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m32">We’ll take in all those horrible moments.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m33">Though I want you to be the one to bear the suffering, manager.</text>
  <text id="malkuth6_intro_m34">....Like we are now.</text>
</localize>