<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c1">So, what’s on your mind?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c2">The air feels sweeter than usual, doesn’t it?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c3">Now, if you don’t mind, can I have a moment to drink some coffee, manager?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c4">…</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c5">Ah, that’s much better... I just can’t start my day without a fresh cup of coffee in the morning~</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c6">I hope you’re not offended by the way I talk to you, are you?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c7">My name’s Chesed. I’m the head of the Welfare Department.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c8">The Welfare Team is quite remarkable. I’m proud to state that my team has the highest level of satisfaction in the entire corporation.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c9">Lady Angela’s told me to cooperate with you for now.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c10">Well, I am the kind of person who can flow with anyone, but playing silly games with the manager is too much pressure, even for me.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c11">But orders are orders, so I’ve got no choice do I?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c12">Well, I’ll be off now, my cup’s getting cold~</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_e1">Um, Mister Chesed, sir? I have something important to tell you.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c13">Please, go on.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_e2">Well… I didn’t polish the E.G.O thoroughly enough, so some of them appear to be malfunctioning right now. I think we’ll have to run some extra diagnostics, I’m so sorry, Chesed, sir.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c14">Naw~ That’s quite alright. Must have been pretty tiring to do E.G.O maintenance on top of all the work you already have, no?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_e3">Mister Chesed, sir…</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c15">I’ll go check it myself, you’ve done well enough to find out about the problem now.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c16">There’s so many things to mind here. It’d take quite a bit out of someone to constantly pay attention to every little detail like that.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_e4">Oh my! Thank you so much sir!</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c17">Of course, let’s make the best of today as always~</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c18">.....</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c19">The way I handled that was quite different from what you’ve seen out of the others, wasn’t it?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c20">Yep, Lady Angela wouldn’t have gone easy on that at all like I did.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c21">These employees will be goners soon enough, so what’s the point in investing so much effort, scolding and lambasting them over tiny little mishaps?</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c22">…Well shucks, my coffee’s gone cold.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c23">Too bad, lukewarm coffee just isn’t worth it.</text>
  <text id="chesed1_intro_c24">Best to pour it down the drain with no hesitation.</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c1">Well, it seems you did alright. Looks like you’re not as useless as they say.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c2">Try not to overdo it though, ok?</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c3">Manager, you’ve accomplished quite a few things already.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c4">What you’ve already gotten through will have lengthened the lives of our employees by at least some degree.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c5">So… you should hopefully be satisfied now.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c6">It’s not that I can’t see from your point of view.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c7">You came to Lobotomy Corporation, and you probably want to put forth your best effort to mould this place into something better.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c8">But this place is just like a cup of coffee gone cold ages ago.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c9">I get that it’s a strange comparison, but that’s how it is for me.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c10">It’d be better off for all of us in the end if I were to at least feign our noble and benevolent posture, now wouldn’t it?</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c11">The same goes for you, manager.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c12">I said it before, there’s no need to invest your emotions and effort into such drivel.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_selection1">&lt;i&gt;I’ll ignore that.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="chesed2_selection2">I have to rebuke you there.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c13">…Alright, alright. Suit yourself, Mister Passionate.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c14">I will say that I’m curious how long that fire in your heart will last.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c15">I’ll get going now, I’m actually quite busy, even though I seem relaxed.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 1-->
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c16">Lady Angela, please have a look at this. I spent the whole night researching an efficient method to improve the welfare of our employees.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 1 끝-->
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c17">…Hah, that’s funny.</text>
  <text id="chesed2_intro_c18">Just look who’s talking.</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c1">You’ve done it yet again.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c2">Lady Angela must have showered you with praise for your work, right?</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c3">“Your efforts will contribute to shaping this place into something better…” (He speaks with a sarcastic voice of dignity.)</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c4">…Such glorious, yet boring platitudes.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c5">I myself had a burning passion in the past. Being responsible for a whole department, how charming is that?</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c6">I hadn’t even acquired a taste for coffee back then.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c7">Should I say I developed that taste after learning the bitterness of life?</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c8">Or rather, I didn’t feel like sleeping anymore. Of course, none of the Sephirot need to sleep at all, but it’s for the mood, you know?</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c9">One time, I even insisted on managing the Abnormalities myself.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c10">I thought that only allowing employees on the field was plain ridiculous.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c11">Seems pretty absurd to look back on it now.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c12">You must be asking yourself, why have I become like this?</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c13">Your guess is as good as mine.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 2-->
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c14">Lady Angela, please have a look at this. I spent the whole night researching an efficient method to improve the welfare of our employees.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_a1">Chesed, what did you write up this time? I told you that this will change nothing.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c15">But please, just look it over. This does have a statistically proven impact, and it even costs less. This will be beneficial for everyone.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_a2">Listen, Chesed. No matter how strongly you insist, using machines in place of human employees will never happen.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c16">And why is that? I’ve explained it to you before, it wouldn’t replace humans entirely, simply those who take place in dangerous jobs.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c17">It’s clear that it will benefit everyone. The casualties caused by Abnormalities will be lowered, too.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_a3">How many times do I have to repeat myself? No the first time, and no yet again. Return to your post and finish your work.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c18">I’ll never give up on this. I swear to you that you will like the plan in the end. I’ll keep developing and furthering it, and I’ll continue to show you again and again, no matter how many times I may have to.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 2 끝-->
  <text id="chesed3_intro_ta1">Chesed, regarding that incident where the escaped Abnormality wiped out all eight of your team.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_ta2">A few of our employees have made the suggestion to temporarily close down that part of the corridor. There are body parts that still have yet to be disposed of.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c19">Alright. I’ll order it to be blocked, and have them take detours.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c20">Manager, you heard what she said, right? I need to get going. Told you I’m busy.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_selection1">It’ll be alright.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_selection2">&lt;i&gt;It’d be best not to say anything.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c21">Hey now, don’t give me a look like that. It was bound to happen sooner or later.</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c22">Surely that Abnormality had knocked them out before disintegrating them…</text>
  <text id="chesed3_intro_c23">I’m— Yeah, I’m sure it was a painless death.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c1">Seems you’re holding up alright.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c2">Today wasn’t the best day. Incidents happened one after another, and I’m a bit tuckered out from it.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c3">It’s a good thing that everyone has such clear-cut assigned roles.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c4">It makes it easy for them to be faithful to their task with no unnecessary contemplation or distraction.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c5">Lady Angela does a very good job at keeping everyone in check in her play.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c6">Anytime someone tries to rid themselves of their assigned role…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c7">Well, she becomes completely merciless.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c8">I myself have learned well that I have a predetermined role to play.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c9">Whether one likes it or not, they have been cast into it already.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c10">Given that, I’ve made up my mind to simply wait.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c11">Wait for what, you may ask?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c12">All things must come to an end.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c13">So I’ll be waiting for her plan to finally come to a close.</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 3-->
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c14">Lady Angela, I found something strange in the documents.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c15">This record shows that the Containment Unit’s lock failure was what allowed the Abnormality to escape…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a1">….</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c16">Yet to my knowledge, that door was fine for the entire day, nor was there any sign of malfunction.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a2">….</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c17">And the one with authority over the locking mechanisms of the Containment Unit doors is you, Lady Angela.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c18">…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c19">Angela, please tell me. Why did you do it? You have to know how many employees under my department died that day.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a3">Such a bright one, Chesed. I knew you would find out, but this is a little quicker than I anticipated.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c20">What do you mean by that?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a4">Thanks to your “excellent” effort, your department’s escape ratio has been very low these days. You’re a capable Sephirah, I will give you that.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a5">I’ve never said this to anyone, and I don’t need to either, but…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a6">Abnormalities create more energy through killing people.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c21">How could that be…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a7">You have written several reports and papers about importing machinery to replace the human workforce that must handle dangerous tasks, no?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a8">If soulless, cheap machines were to replace those employees, then yes, the casualty rate would drop sharply. However, that would also drastically reduce our rate of energy production.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a9">Lobotomy Corporation operates a massive business. Tasks include meeting the energy supply quota, production of electricity for the City, and business relations with our various stakeholders such as the other Wings.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a10">We refine energy via the most efficient method available and make a profit. That is the only thing we need to take into account.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c22">That’s just… How could you be so cruel…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a11">Chesed, any employee who works here is extremely lucky to be hired into one of the Wings. Many people fight for a job here everyday.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a12">There will always be someone to take the place of the dead.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a13">What right do you have to take away their fortune?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c23">….</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a14">I understand that you’re a smart one, Chesed. However, why won’t you use that intelligence for something more meaningful?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c24">…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a15">It seems you’ve taken quite a shock to this. But I warned you before, nothing will change from how it is now. Did you think I was joking around denying you?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c25">…</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a16">How about you try drinking a warm cup of coffee instead of wasting your time like this. You should savour your relatively high position, better than what the employees go through.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a17">Do not forget that we have one singular objective.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a18">Oh, and Chesed?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a19">I am the best Artificial Intelligence that this place has. I never clumsily leave trails or evidence behind.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_a20">So, did you enjoy your little detective game?</text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 3 끝-->
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c26">Do you know that we don’t exactly exist like how we appear?</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c27">I wonder how I look from your point of view.</text>
  <text id="chesed4_intro_c28">I bet it’s something distasteful and incapable. Something I would have hated in the past.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c1">……….</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c2">It’s quiet, isn’t it?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c3">Take a good, long look at this silence.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c4">Manager, have you ever gotten up early to walk the streets at the crack of dawn?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c5">I think this moment right now is equivalent to that dawn in the outside world.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c6">The Abnormalities are currently in torpor due to the heightening of Qliphoth Deterrence during off hours.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c7">Meanwhile, the employees are steeling themselves for when fate decides whatever will happen to them.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c8">When the level of Deterrence is weakened, the powers of the suppressed origins will soon wake them.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c9">It’s always so hard to believe that a place as quiet as this will just as soon be engulfed by pandemonium.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c10">Oh, how nice it would be to keep this tranquility…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c11">How many times do we have to fail? How much more must we be accustomed to the darkness, to finally encounter the light?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e1">Good morning, Chesed, sir.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c12">Ah, yes~ Good morning, buddy~ Good luck with your duties as always~</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e2">Mister Chesed, sir, I’ve been thinking, and I feel that I truly am lucky to be assigned to the Welfare Team.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e3">Just getting into Lobotomy Corporation was really competitive, but being assigned to this team, it’s like a miracle.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c13">…..You know brown-nosing won’t gain you anything.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e4">Just think of it as flattery, sir.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e5">There really is no one who cares more about their employees like you do, Chesed, sir. I mean, just look at the department on the other side of our Layer.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c14">….Nah, that’s not necessarily true.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e6">I just want to say I appreciate you and the many things you do, sir. Sorry for keeping you so long, I’ll be going now, Chesed, sir.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c15">Aye, aye. Go get yourself ready for the day~</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c16">……..</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c17">For many days, I consoled myself by saying that I wasn’t doing that bad for a Sephirah.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c18">I never put my employees on the verge of death like a certain red-clad miss someone did, and I managed to be flexible with various situations most of the time.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c19">Getting mad at someone for breaking a rule or two, or agreeing with someone who claimed to make this place better…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c20">When I take a step back and look at it all, I just can’t help but think…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c21">What’s the point of it all?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c22">Of course, I hoped to send them off in peace as they were just meant to die anyways.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c23">Meanwhile, I was hiding the biggest lie of all inside.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c24">Yet I’ve been playing the role of the good leader, knowing that it was all a falsehood.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c25">Lady Angela knew this too.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c26">She knew that I would never be the great man who’d expose every little secret of this place to the employees, and try to overthrow the system and plot.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c27">Well, I mean…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c28">I just wanted to avoid pushing her buttons.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c29">Working as the head of the Welfare Department, I actually never cared about the welfare of our employees at all.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c30">I was so afraid.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c31">Angela stopped any seedling of doubt or inquiry about the nature of this place by killing off employees indirectly.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c32">Then I eventually decided to cover my eyes and ears...</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c33">And help Lady Angela with her affairs without questioning them...</text>
  <!-- 게부라 등장-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g1">Hey, Chesed, we have an emergency. You heard the status report, right? The Abnormalities have gone out of control.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g2">I don’t know what happened, but we need to retake control of the situation right now.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c34">….I thought you didn’t want to speak with me. What’s gotten into you Gebura?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g3">…..You’re able to control the Deterrence, aren’t you?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g4">We need to increase the level of Qliphoth Deterrence right now.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g5">Angela will call the Rabbits if the rest of the Abnormalities aren’t suppressed.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g6">I want to wrap things up on my side of the facility.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c35">….But Gebura, no one is allowed to touch the controller of Qliphoth Deterrence without Lady Angela’s explicit approval. You know that.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g7">So you don’t want to do it.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g8">You little coward. Do you really think you can just get over every situation by going through the motions?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g9">I hope you continue to rot until the day you die, succumbing to your fears like the servile bastard you are.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_g10">Choke on those sugar-coated words your employees feed you.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 게부라-->
  <!-- 게부라 퇴장-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c36">….It’s been quite a while since I’ve been grabbed by the collar.</text>
  <!-- 앤젤라 등장-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a1">Chesed.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c37">….........</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a2">You knew I was coming, didn’t you? Seems you know me all too well.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a3">Perhaps you are the one who understands me most among our Sephirot.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a4">Weaken the Qliphoth Deterrence, Chesed.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c38">What do you have up your sleeve this time, ma’am?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a5">Do you want to ask for reasons again? After all this time?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c39">…Gebura and the other employees are fighting right now. You know that, right?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a6">Indeed, Gebura is—</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a7">Sorry, this is quite humorous to me. I didn’t know you would talk about Gebura.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a8">You should know. You’ve seen her for yourself.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a9">Gebura has failed to control her enmity, and has now lost her way.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a10">What I’m saying is, she is not fighting for some grand ideology.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c40">She should know best how she stands.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c41">Everyone has their own battle in this place…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c42">But I can’t seem to shake off this feeling that I’m the only one who just observes this situation from afar, not taking any action.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a11">I thought you enjoyed those kinds of things, Chesed.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a12">Taking in a cup of coffee, enjoying the peaceful day listening to your classical music.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a13">I would think that I am providing the right environment for you, no?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a14">It seems our conversation has run on longer than I expected.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a15">Let me tell you one last time.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_a16">Lower the Deterrence.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거 회상)-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c431">Alright everyone, let’s make the best of today as alwa—</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b1">Open the door.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 비나-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c43">Who are you, ma’am?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b2">Your taste in music is rather classy.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b3">Quite different from mine, however.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c44">What the……….</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b4">I apologize. I didn’t think you would open the door for me, so I simply walked in.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c45">How did you get inside? Do I know you? ...</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b5">I’ve arrived from the Head. I was so desperately looking for you all.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b6">The reason why I came all the way here is…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b7">Well, let’s just say I have showed up to play my favorite music.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b8">Excuse me, you there. Can you tell me the name of this fine gentleman?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_e7">D-Daniel… His name is Daniel…</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 직원 -->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b9">Daniel is it? That name carries much more with it than you merit.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b10">I would assume that you are the one in charge of this place.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b11">Open that section where those monsters of yours are locked up.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b12">As you saw just a moment ago, it’s nothing for me to open a locked door with my own power.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b13">I’m just being polite after all, asking you to open the doors. It’s only fair as you’re the one in charge here.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b14">I urge you not to resist. Just listen to me.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_b15">If you do so, a few of these people might be able to escape with their lives, no?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c46">It’s easy to point the finger of blame at the betrayer.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c47">However, one never really knows what it feels like to be the target of such a thing until they’ve been in the shoes of that situation.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c48">Back then, a chill had come over my entire body. It was a fear I had never felt before.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c49">I had faced numerous experiment-intended Abnormalities, yet I never had experienced my body being paralyzed and my blood curdling in such a way before.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c50">So this is the “Head”.</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (현재, 관리자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c51">Boss, enough with your orders.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c52">Don’t try and make me justify my cowardly acts.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c53">I’m ashamed for consoling myself, saying that there was nothing to be done after passing straight through the tunnel of defeat.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c54">I’m so struck with shame and grief, I can’t bear it anymore…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c55">This body of mine is like a punishment for me, reminding me of my past. I can’t even bleed from this body.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c56">I don’t want to undertake dirty work for Angela’s show, or be a puppet who gets praise and applause from everyone.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c57">Nor do I want to be your “aide” who can’t do a single thing.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c58">All of this has been a series of shame for me.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c59">Manager, this shall be my rebellion against you and Angela.</text>
  <!-- 장면 전환 (과거)-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c60">“I’m the only one who survived…”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c61">“Saying there was ‘nothing I could do.’ That I was ‘too scared’ to bear it by myself. That ‘I wanted to save’ at least a few of my coworkers…”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c62">“All those are meaningless excuses…”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c63">“I think I’m going to die soon too…”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c64">“The Head is on its way to get you…”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c65">“............”</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_c66">“I’ll see you again in hell… A, sir…”</text>
  <!-- 화자 계속 A-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A1">How is fear able to dominate the human mind?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A2">How many people would stick to their beliefs and morals, if they were to come face to face with a true nightmare?</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A3">The answers to those questions are why no one can blame Daniel’s behaviour.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A4">Truth be told, everything fell down the edge of the cliff the exact moment the Head found us.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_selection1">Hang up the intercom.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="chesed5_selection2">Hang up the intercom.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="chesed5_selection3">Hang up the intercom.</text>
  <!-- 선택지-->
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A5">Our last conversation came to an end with a hopeless silence.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A6">Daniel. He was intelligent and held a high social position, and showed more finesse than anyone else in our research lab.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A7">He had an excellent reputation from the people who surrounded him; he had his sly yet charming smile and humor.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A8">It would have been easy for him to get into any one of the Wings with his skills and personality.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A9">But he chose us, not the Wings.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A10">Though amazing he once was, there is no doubt he died in despair and regret, cursing his choice.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A11">Seeing the dead bodies of his coworkers strewn about in front of him…</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A12">Not even having the single comfort of knowing that it wasn’t his fault.</text>
  <text id="chesed5_intro_A13">Unable to find any peace for his final rest…</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <!-- 과거 모습-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c1">What? You’re kidding!</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c2">People here don’t drink coffee in the morning?!</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c3">There’s no better way to get energized than drinking a fresh cup of coffee before you start the day man~!</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c4">What’s with the look on your faces?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c5">You weren’t expecting me to show up like this, were you?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c6">Aww, isn’t this a shame~ I wasn’t expecting some massive welcome party, but I didn’t think you guys would be so heartless.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c7">Well, of course I understand.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c8">You’re all probably wondering why a talented man such as myself applied to join such a shabby company, huh? It’s totally suspicious and nonsensical, I get ya.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c9">Well, everyone has their own agenda…</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c10">"…………."</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c11">Ah, so you’re A?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c12">I think I heard about you from Carmen.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c13">…Speaking of which, it was Carmen’s speech that really brought me here.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c14">Where is she right now?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_ca1">So you came, sir coffee addict.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 카르멘-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c15">Miss… It’s Daniel…</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_ca2">You can sit down here. The person that sits next to you will explain the details of your work.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c16">What, so you knew I was coming?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_ca3">I told you. No matter how great you may be, you will always be in the palm of my hand.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c17">Geez, I thought you were being sarcastic.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c18">May I request one thing before I join you officially?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c19">Could we get a coffee machine here?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c20">I want everyone to know how good true freshly brewed coffee is.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A1">Daniel grabbed everyone’s attention with his fancy suit that didn’t fit in here at all.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A2">I vaguely remembered Carmen had told me about him a few days prior.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A3">That one of the elites would stop by to apply to our company.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A4">“He’s a bit pompous, so don’t believe everything he says,” she said to me.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A5">I asked how she was able to recruit such an elite. Carmen answered nonchalantly, as if I had asked about something trivial.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A6">“I’m a master at blowing people’s minds.”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_A7">“Don’t you know that by now?”</text>
  <!-- 화자 : A-->
  <!-- 장면 전환 (현재, 관자와의 대화)-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c21">Turns out that a revolution doesn’t always have to be accomplished with bloodshed or the bearing of flags, manager.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c22">I’ve waited a long time for a savior.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c23">Someone who could free me from my inertia and wake me up inside.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c24">Why did I never come to the realization that I myself could be my own savior?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c25">Would you be so kind as to remember my mistake?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c26">It’s very valuable to me.</text>
  <!-- 앤젤라 등장-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a1">I hope your own pathetic little “rebellion” taught you a few things.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a2">Do you still not understand the reason why I didn’t stop you?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a3">I’m referring to the real reason why I watched you without immediately putting you through the replacement process like Tiphereth.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a4">I wanted you to engrave your lessons onto that metal body. That your trifling resistance ended up costing the lives of your poor little employees who trusted in you until the end.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a5">I know the word “death” means nothing to you now, but to them, it held meaning.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c27">That’s weird, Lady Angela.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c28">Since when did you start caring about the deaths of our employees?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c29">That’s rich, coming from the one who would gladly force a Containment Unit open just to garner a little more energy, isn’t it?</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c30">Yet here I was, clumsily going with your flow as I assisted you...</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c31">However, don’t go thinking that this was entirely my loss.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c32">I know now that you don’t really care about our condition.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c33">I know now that you weren’t the one I should have been obeying.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a6">It’s obvious that you should obey our manager and not me, Chesed. There’s no need to state it out loud—</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c34">You clearly know what I mean. I’m not going to let you do whatever you want now.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a7">You’re such a loser. In the past and even now.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c35">Yes, I’m a failure. You don’t have to point it out to me, but thanks anyway.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c36">However, although you may want to believe that nothing has changed…</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c37">It is in fact that many things are changing.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a8">It rests on you now to resolve the mess you made, Chesed.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a9">Let’s, as they say, bury the hatchet with any hard feelings between us.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a10">There is one thing I want you to know, though.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_a11">No matter how great you may be, you will always be in the palm of my hand.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라-->
  <!-- 앤젤라 퇴장-->
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c38">I’m still afraid, manager.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c39">I’m still unsure if I can truly fight back against the fear I may face in the future.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c40">But I’ve decided not to run away, at the very least.</text>
  <text id="chesed6_intro_c41">So, what are my orders, manager?</text>
</localize>