<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1">You’ve returned.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2">So, did you have fun with your little journey while I was locked up here?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b3">Don’t worry, I’m not mad with you.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b4">“Oh Sorrow, you see, finally I have come to respect you, for I know you will never depart.”</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b5">It’s difficult to perceive the flow of time here.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b6">Therefore this eternity has saved me.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b7">Have you seen the turbid streams of the enormous river that crossed the whole city?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b8">If you arrive downstream, after the raging rapids and a serpentine current…</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b9">You will see a meadow that is enormously broad, but also tranquil.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b10">That land is bathed with all kinds of mud, sand, trash, and the residuals that have come from the upstream.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b11">What isn’t caught by the upstream or midstream finally ends up here, downstream…</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b12">To bear all the residues that pile up, one would need a strong back that doesn’t break easily.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b13">I have faced many Wells here.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b14">I have to draw water every single day, but it seems that the water level never lowers.</text>
  <text id="binah1_selection1">What is a Well?</text>
  <text id="binah1_selection2">What does it mean to draw water?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_1">The Well is so deep that it would be a hollow affair to reckon its depth.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_2">And it is the fount and relic of all humanity that has existed from the ancient times.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_3">The water from the Well had never flown outside, ever. There had only been the small ripples that permeated from the leaves that fall for the winds.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_1">Our labor is bringing up the water that is deep within the Well to the outside.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_2">You never know what the Bucket contains when it rises from the eternal darkness, but I always draw the water with a pulley, come what may.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_3">You must always stay cautious so that you don’t fall into the Well.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b15">Maybe it was an act of generosity towards those that are thirsty, so that they may sate themselves.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b16">It was you who made the Bucket.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b17">But you left the duty of drawing water with the Bucket to another.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b18">Don’t ask for my name.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b19">“Binah” isn’t the name of a person.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b20">It’s a sad name of the place where one finds many graves.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b21">I’m the one who draws the water.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b22">Why have you come here, and what do you wish for me to draw?</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="binah2_intro_b1">Looking at the headstones in this place are you?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2">It is only natural to find them a spectacle to see. There used to be times when I spent the whole day reading all the meaningless letters written there.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b3">These are also coffins. They’re death itself, and they represent the possibilities birth can bring at the same time.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b4">I have been guarding their coffins for countless years, carrying out consecrations for those who do not even have the privilege to depart for an afterlife.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b5">That is one of the few things I do here.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b6">You see, if one spends a long, long enough time in this graveyard…</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b7">They can hear the whispers of the dead.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b8">The sound of their words is black as pitch, it makes me feel as if I were being filled with nebulous, murky water.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b9">You must be starting to get bored, seeing that your eyes are drifting about this place.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b10">It isn’t often that I have guests here, and I’d feel bad to only show you these gravestones.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e1">Did you call me, Lady Binah?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b11">This employee once had his boundary collapsed.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b12">What’s your name?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e2">It’s... Nathan.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b13">This man had the task of extracting E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b14">During extraction, he carelessly peeked into the Well, but by luck he survived.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b15">To minimize the price he had to pay for looking into the Well, he was given the maximum dose of Enkephalin. And so, he could barely return to work.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b16">However, once one looks through the crack of the boundary, they can never return to the world that they belonged to before.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b17">Want to see something interesting?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b18">Nathan, can you describe what you saw to the manager? The scenery you witnessed with your own eyes, but had to forget at all costs?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e3">From within the tombstones… Inside them are… Those who sleep are… Sunken deep…</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b19">Those who are dreaming good dreams. At the same time, we call them the ‘Well’ in the speech of this place.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e4">We have to dredge them up… and inject them… with Cogito…</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b20">Now remember, afterwards, what? What did you see?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e5">The man… he… That… thing…</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b21">Continue.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e6">The man… he… him… he…. h...h.. heeheeh….. in… in the Well……</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b22">He passed out. Poor thing.</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection1">Why did he pass out?</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection2">What will happen to him after?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b1_1">These children cannot disobey me.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b1_2">Even though he wasn't able to complete his sentence, the way he kept trying to speak until he passed out should show you he pushed himself to the limit to obey me.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2_1">Do not worry for him. He wouldn’t last a single day with a mind as feeble as his is now.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2_2">It is much more favorable to sit still and simply watch the grains fall as the sandcastle crumbles, rather than try to reclaim the collapsing castle.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b23">I have seen what that poor sap saw, hundreds, no, thousands of times, maybe more.</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection3">How are you still fine?</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection4">Are you alright now?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b24">So you ask why I can retain enough sanity to have a friendly little conversation with you until now.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b25">It is thanks to my mechanical body that I can just barely grasp onto my mind. Yes, this strong, unbending back of mine.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b26">However, A.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b27">Did you forget that I originated from a human mind as well?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b28">......</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b29">If there is at least one thing that could be considered fortunate…</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b30">It is that if I ever were to finally lose my sanity and ran amok through the facility, attempting to bring this entire place down along with you.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b31">She will be there to shut me off once more.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b32">But if that day truly were to come, I would prefer that you terminated me with your own hands, rather than her.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b33">It’s the least you can do for a person as confined as I.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 3-->
  <text id="binah3_intro_b1">As you find them in quotidian life, fierce fights break out every day here.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b2">You’ve seen this innumerable times, no?</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b3">With enough time, Abnormalities come back to life. No matter how many fragments they’re broken into.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b4">It’s one of the facts that drove Gebura mad.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b5">She took far too much time to understand that the Abnormalities have to be exploited, not ended.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b6">Or maybe she simply couldn’t free herself from the indignation of her past.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b7">Well, that doesn’t concern me. The only thing I know is that I will never ever see what she was before.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b8">Nevertheless, I cannot help but be astonished by the potential of E.G.O each time I see her go on a rampage.</text>
  <text id="binah3_selection1">E.G.O’s potential?</text>
  <text id="binah3_selection2">What’s the reason you’re so astonished?</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b1_1">You’ll never know it. You’ve never wielded an E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b2_1">Extracting E.G.O is one of my multitudes of duties. It’s only natural that I am drawn to its potential.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b9">In fact, there are many weapons that have enormous power in this world, apart from E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b10">Artifacts from the Outskirts and from the Ruins, the singularities of the Wings or rudimentary inventions made in the Backstreets. If used correctly, they would be weapons that could fare against Abnormalities somehow.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11">But giving those weapons to employees that never even learned to fight outside of basic training is as useless as teaching a hatchling to hunt.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11_1">The Rabbits are specialized in killing. They can spot the enemy’s weakness right away and focus their firepower, given that they have enough munitions.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11_2">As opposed to our employees who cannot even wield weapons efficiently.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b12">That’s seeing as combat ability isn’t a requirement to be hired here.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b13">But our employees don’t even have to learn to use E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b14">The power of the E.G.O grows in conjunction with the heart of the wielder. One knows how to use it the moment they wield it.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b15">Nevertheless, even though they wield that power, the majority of employees can’t control it. Swayed by it, they hardly have a chance against the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b16">I haven’t seen anyone that can draw out the true potential, apart from the Red Mist.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b17">To wield E.G.O is to dress oneself in the shell of the ego of another person.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b18">The wielder is merely imitating the borrowed ego, unable to completely make the power their own.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b19">Had I known that before being locked up here, I would have done anything to get my hands on them.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b20">If I could, the circumstances may have changed dramatically.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b21">Now I’m confined here, issuing orders to extract E.G.O, forbidden from touching them myself.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b22">You must have been scared still, even though my hatred and bloodthirst are locked up inside this rusted metal cage.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b23">Don’t you worry; I no longer have anything left.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b24">But you never know. The yearning for blood could wax once again, for it is simply sealed, not uprooted.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="binah4_intro_b1">Erstwhile, the world in which you stayed was once luminous.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b2">There was the sun and the moon, and also the clouds and winds that floated around them. It was a world of light, so to speak.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b3">But you couldn’t stay there. You were robbed of innumerable things.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b4">You lived with a broken heart, clinging to the void where pieces of your heart used to be.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b5">No one could understand your pain, nor embrace you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b6">Eternal loss dominated you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b7">I was one of the thieves who robbed you of countless things.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b8">While I was at the top of the world, I watched you and looked down on your struggle.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b9">Not just you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b10">I have seen many others that struggled.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b11">Those attempts were no less futile than an insect writhing. All I had to do was simply stomp on them a couple times.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b12">But, among them, there were some who would grit their teeth and climb up, dragging their broken bodies.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b13">It seemed that this was going to be another fun little trip, so I would drink a cup of tea before leaving with light steps.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b14">But as you can see, an unexpected encounter with the Red Mist got the best of me.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b15">Huhu, and then you inflicted as much suffering upon me as I to you, did you not?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b16">You were familiar with how to break the mind without utilizing torture or violence.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b17">After everything was done, you gathered up every little bit of what was left of my humanity.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b18">And you threw them into this pit until even my spirit soured and rotted.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b19">Maybe you told yourself that I deserved worse than that.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b20">Therefore you’re an upholder of justice who has defeated the evil, no?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b21">Then I must ask, why is that grand and righteous upholder standing here making himself out as a prisoner like I?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b22">And what happened with that coward? The one who with fear averted his gaze from my dying one.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b23">Why is he down here, suffering the same punishment as I?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b24">See, there cannot be a sight more satisfying than this for me.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b25">Is this all that idealism of hers came to be?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b26">You’ve dragged down your heroine with your own hands.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b27">Do you truly believe that your duty completes itself just for shedding tears at the funeral of the innocent?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b28">While you never even let their bodies rest in peace?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b29">Ironically, you found a hope in all this misery.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b30">The raw material of the Bucket.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b31">And the path to the river of all.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b32">Out of her you made the Bucket, and you started to send it down, down into the Wells of the people.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b33">The Bucket rises from the Well of a person, filled with the water that can only be drawn by that person.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b34">An ancient fount that has been flowing at the bottom, even before the birth of the world.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b35">Now it simply is drawn, regardless of the consent of the person.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b36">When the Bucket that holds the faded ideal of hers comes in contact with the ego of another person, a certain change occurs.</text>
  <text id="binah4_selection1">&lt;i&gt;I’ll ask her about the Bucket.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="binah4_selection2">&lt;i&gt;I’ll ask her about the Change.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b37">Maybe it’s difficult to understand only by listening.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b38">How about this? I could show you one of her miracles.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b39">It’s taxing, but for you, I’ll gladly do it.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b40">The people selected long ago are awaiting their turns.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b41">I bring them here according to the register.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b42">Let me introduce one to you. This one is Nameless.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b43">He has nothing left, for he has abandoned all that he is a long time ago.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b44">For him, things like the remnants of the past or the pain of the present don’t matter.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b45">He only stares into the future.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b46">Did you dream well?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e1">……..............</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b47">Yes, you’ll finally dream for as long as you want, one that you will never wake up from.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b48">The employees will inject him with Cogito soon.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b49">What river flows in you? What world lies in you?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b50">There are as many worlds as there are people. Discovering them is rather fun.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e2">………..………..………..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e3">………..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e4">………..Grr….grrrrrrrrrrr…..ggggggggg……</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b51">No one must see this…</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b52">That is why they adjust the level of Cogito according to my orders, keeping their eyes and ears covered.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b53">…………………</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b54">……………………………..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b55">Nobody should make direct eye contact with the drawn.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b56">But I can never dare to look away from him or to close my eyes, no matter how unbearable it may be.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b57">In the eyes of the drawn there are the abysses that only I can endure, and there are the things that shouldn’t exist in this world…</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b58">This is the punishment that you’ve obligated me to endure.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b59">A normal person would have gone mad thousands of times over if they had to put up with this.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b60">Thanks to you, I cannot even be graced with insanity or lose my mind; all I can do is capture all of it in my eyes.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e5">Gggggrrr…..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b61">Now, we wait.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b62">Will it rise anew, or is it destined to be stuck in this pillar and spend eternity with me down in this place?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b63">We just need a little more time to find out.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b64">Now, do you finally realize what all these pillars contain?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b65">Well, consider yourself lucky today.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b66">At times, when the level of Cogito is adjusted inadequately, some things that shouldn’t exist come up as fragments.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b67">How funny that I say this, but they’re like an adverse reaction that has its price for doing something unspeakable to a human being.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b68">The Bucket can rise with some impurities mixed in with what we usually draw, such as the abyss within humanity, the subconscious and all kinds of possibilities.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b69">From the past, from the present, even from the future. All kinds of beings that have existed and will exist in this world.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b70">Given that they’re outside our dominion, there’s nothing we could do to govern them.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b71">They float around aimlessly, resonating with the Abnormalities and manifesting themselves in front of us when the moment comes.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b72">They are what you call the Ordeals.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b73">Thankfully, they react to the Qliphoth Deterrence, so we can put them to sleep like the Abnormalities, but that’s all we’re able to do.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b74">Yes, as you have learned, extracting Abnormalities is my job.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b75">But creating them is Carmen’s, whom you buried a long time ago.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b76">She is the mother of all Abnormalities that have existed in this facility and of all that will emerge in the future.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b77">Tell me, how do you feel now that you know that those Abnormalities that you’ve faced above were part of these pillars?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b78">It’s an agonizing sight to confront, but it doesn’t matter to you, not at all. Or am I wrong?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b79">After all, erasing your memories and running away from them as if nothing had happened is your age-old specialty.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="binah5_intro_A1">You told me to sacrifice all of your body without hesitation.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A2">Would you have made the same choice, if you knew that we would end up like this?</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A3">I always ask myself that.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b1">This is no-man’s land. The place of silence.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b2">Most employees that visit and stay here lose their mind and embrace oblivion.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b3">It has been a long while since I had a proper conversation with someone.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b4">Maybe you were confused with the idea that I’m the only resident here.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b5">But there is in fact a companion of mine that passes the eternity with me.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b6">Let me introduce her to you.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b7">You created the Bucket by reconstructing, dividing, and proliferating Carmen’s body.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b8">And you managed to extract Cogito, the so-called fluid of life and death.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b9">At first, only a small dose could be extracted. But enigmatically that fluid started to gush out infinitely and now has formed a pool.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b10">Can you see her?</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b11">She’s watching us from underneath the spring.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b12">When everything becomes too burdening, I quietly stare into the bottom.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b13">I feel as if she and I were the only two in the world when I do so.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b14">Sometimes, it feels like she’s talking to me.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b15">Even though all that’s left of her is just an amalgamation of flesh, brain, neurons and unknown tentacles, drifting beneath the spring.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b16">Someone injected herself with Cogito following her own principles, and someone else went mad for witnessing what happened.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b17">Another gave up his own body and fell into a state of limbo, unable to live or die. And the one that couldn’t persevere herself through all this ended up confessing everything to the Head…</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b18">This is the collaboration of despair that you and her created.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b19">You still aren’t qualified to look toward the bottom of the spring.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b20">To do so, you must look directly towards the path you travel.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b21">Do you seek redemption?</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b22">Or do you seek to redeem me along with all the others that are trapped here?</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b23">Whatever it is, maybe you think that saving this facility from sin as you have planned will fix everything for you.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b24">Just think for a moment. Even you, who hasn’t left this facility for such a long time…</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b25">You should be aware that people are hopelessly being killed by Abnormalities in other branches even as we speak.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b26">And it’s not just them; all the Wings have their own painful stories, repeating perpetually.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b27">In the Nests, in the Backstreets, in the Ruins, in the Outskirts…</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b28">A pain much greater than what you have seen here prevails in the world.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b29">I have observed everything conscientiously, for I didn’t obsess myself with an unreachable ideal to lock myself up in a cramped room, like you.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b30">The world you looked up at and the one I looked down upon are that much different.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b31">You captured me alive and tortured me to your heart’s content, but still we’re sunken in despair.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b32">And someone will replace me as one of the Arbiters of the Head, swinging their Claws at people like you.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b33">Even if you were to break the cycle somehow, it would be a perfectly, completely useless affair.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b34">Broken Wings will outstretch anew.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b35">The brief resistance will be forgotten soon, and people will continue living, not for a purpose nor a dream, but rather simply because they cannot die.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b36">You may think that you have brought me down.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b37">Yet as you can see, I’m still at the peak, looking down upon you lot while you writhe like insects.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b38">I eagerly wait for the moment you fall into despair after realizing that this cycle of pain will never end.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b39">I want to see you kneel before the might of destiny, resigning yourself to fate.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b40">Go on, slowly; despair and succumb to your fate.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b41">Try to resist to the very end, and ultimately break yourself.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b42">As the last bits of your resistance melt away.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_b43">We shall be the subterranean water that quietly flows underneath the earth.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A4">She was mortally wounded by Kali, but she was our only way out.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A5">It was a miracle that we captured her alive. We were too far down the road filled with remorse and regret to feel any sort of guilt.</text>
  <text id="binah5_selection1">Probe her head.</text>
  <text id="binah5_selection2">Probe her head.</text>
  <text id="binah5_selection3">Probe her head.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A6">How to avoid the Head’s pursuit; the means to join the ranks of the Wings; and the way for us, the few, to survive.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A7">It was impossible to figure those out on our own.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A8">She was hardly breathing, but her encephalon was still active. That was all we needed.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A9">We probe through her head like we did to Carmen. We search for the way out.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A10">After that, we arduously gather up every single bit of those deformed pieces.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A11">The sentinel who guards the gates of hell must always be in despair.</text>
  <text id="binah5_intro_A12">Such despair that they cannot even fall into the depths of hell.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="binah6_intro_b1">Yet another place becomes a desolate wasteland in the end.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_e1">P-Please, spare me… I did everything you told me to...</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b2">Don’t you get any impression, when the place you belonged to has been reduced to ashes and dust?</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b3">Don’t be such a buzzkill. Try to admire the view a little.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b4">Since childhood, scenery such as a myriad of stars illuminating the sky or the sun’s radiant light beating down upon the earth couldn’t impress me one bit.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b5">This, however, gives me a thrill. A thrill that makes me thirst for more.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b6">But it’s still not enough.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b7">My thirst has not been quenched just yet.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_e2">P… Please… Let me go now… You got everything you wanted…</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b8">Why are you trembling so much? Where’d the guts to betray your very own Nest go?</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b9">The plan wasn’t perfect by any means, but it wasn’t all that bad, either.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b10">Thanks to those that placed their trust in you, we get to have this magnificent view.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b11">Trust is one of my favorite weapons, you see. It leaves a great wound, no?</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b12">The Sweepers will arrive soon.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b13">Wherever there is trash, they’ll always be on time to gather it up.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_e3">N… No… Please…</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b14">It’s a symbiotic relationship, so to speak. We’re too busy to take care of all the dregs.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_e4">......... Anything but the Sweepers.. Please…</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b15">Ah yes, that face.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b16">That vivid expression on your face is the testament to life.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b17">…..</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b18">My two best companions, silence and the metallic scent of black tea.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b19">Wouldn’t you agree?</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b20">Now, the next stop… is that place.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b21">It’s rather displeasing that I have to depend on the information from some orange-haired girl...</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b22">But the weak and the vulnerable tend to yield greatly valuable information.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b23">What kind of faces will show me what it means to be alive next?</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b24">The only things that could excite me were the dying and the crumbling.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b25">Only the sound of their last breath, and the expressions they made while they cling to their fading life could satisfy me.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b26">I recognized a long time ago that you and I were no different.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b27">We are the mutants this epoch has created.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b28">No, let’s say that we are the new generation of humanity, fit better than anyone else to live through this age.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b29">That is why you could have planned all this.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b30">However, no matter what you achieve here, the world will not change at all.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b31">The Wings on the rise, the Organizations from the Backstreets, the creatures in the Outskirts, the abyss within the Ruins, Arbiters like me, the Claws, and the Eye… You’ll never have a chance against them alone.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b32">...But simply idling here won’t change the world, either.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b33">If there are no more places to run to, hide in, or rest, then I will witness everything you have to do with my own eyes.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b34">I shall not close my eyes just because my eyelids are heavy, nor shall I turn away just because the sight is painful.</text>
  <text id="binah6_intro_b35">Simply proceed like you always have. Then you may just triumph.</text>
</localize>