<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="netzach1_intro_x1">(It seems Netzach has yet to show up)</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n1">Man, why did the meeting room have to be so far away…</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n2">Uh, you already know my name, right?</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n3">……</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n4">Got anything else to say?</text>
  <text id="netzach1_selection1">I do.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1-->
  <text id="netzach1_selection2">No.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2-->
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n1_1">Could we talk later, then? Don’t really wanna be bothered right now.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1을 고른 경우-->
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n2_1">Great. I’ll see you later then. </text>
  <!-- 선택지 2를 고른 경우-->
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n5">....</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n6">You look a little dumbfounded.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n7">You know this isn’t the kind of place where we preach how we’re so honored to have you as our manager and whatever.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n8">Well, not like you were expecting that anyways.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n9">That’s right, I’ll be level with you. I don’t like my job.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n10">I really want to quit if I could.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n11">But I can’t, can I?</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n12">I’m here against my will.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n13">I don’t know what grand ambition or aim compelled you to stand where you are. Don’t care either.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n14">For me, I don’t even remember ending up at this place, yet I have to play this role I didn’t want to take.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n15">I never wanted to be responsible for keeping others alive.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n16">Whoever assigned me here, they were totally wrong giving me the job.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n17">I feel helpless.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n18">Employees die everyday.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n19">There’ll be no one to remember them.</text>
  <text id="netzach1_intro_n20">No one to honor their sacrifice...</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="netzach2_intro_x1">(Netzach’s eyes are closed)</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n1">….</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n2">When I shut my eyes, I feel like I’m in another place altogether.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n3">I see a different world, one I had belonged to.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n4">I think I remember doing something there, hoping to save someone else’s life.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n5">But here I am now.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n6">What’s the point of saving an employee’s life if you’re just gonna watch them die the very next day?</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n7">What’s the point of delaying the inevitable...</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n8">Those who work here have no future.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n9">None of those little things called plans and dreams.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n10">No self-reflections, no hopes to become a better person tomorrow. All of that’s a luxury they can’t afford.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n11">Why must I wake up and endure yet another day?</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n12">Why do I have to bear the pain and get through it all, knowing tomorrow is going to be just as dreadful?</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n13">We’re just lemmings running straight for the edge of the cliff…</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n14">Speaking of, could we get a vending machine for beer?</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n15">If we’re gonna die, might as well get wasted before we drop dead.</text>
  <text id="netzach2_selection1">I’ll order one for you.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 1-->
  <text id="netzach2_selection2">You know I can't do something like that.</text>
  <!-- 선택지 2-->
  <text id="netzach2_intro_1_a1">Manager, please try to think before you speak. You shouldn’t stoop to Netzach’s level here.</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라, 선택지 1을 고를 경우 등장-->
  <text id="netzach2_intro_1_n1">What's so low about me? I’m just trying to improve the employee welfare. </text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_2_a1">Don’t get out of line, Netzach. Consider this a friendly warning. You know what’s coming if you utter such useless nonsense one more time.  </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 앤젤라, 선택지 2를 고를 경우 등장-->
  <text id="netzach2_intro_2_n1">Oh, I’d sure love to see you make it happen to me, ma’am. </text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n16">....</text>
  <text id="netzach2_intro_n17">Yeah, just keep ignoring me all you want. How typical.</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_m1">Umm… Manager? Netzach’s not feeling too well today. He got a cold and was worried that you might catch it from him, so he told me to go in his place, so, um...</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 말쿠트-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_y1">Malkuth, friendship should not be an excuse to lie. Manager, Netzach is high as a kite on Enkephalin. He’s completely out of it. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 예소드-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_m2">You’re such a rat! What if Netzach gets punished? </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 말쿠트-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_y2">That does not concern me in the slightest, and neither should you care. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 예소드-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_m3">Please don’t punish Netzach, manager. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 말쿠트-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_y3">Netzach is neglecting his responsibilities yet again, and so are you. Shouldn’t you be participating in your team’s internal meeting right now?</text>
  <!-- 화자 : 예소드-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_m4">Oh, you’re right! Thanks, Yesod! </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 말쿠트-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_y4">I hope you don’t mind if I say this, but you should do something about Netzach before Angela finds him. He has been drunk for quite some time now. </text>
  <!-- 화자 : 예소드-->
  <text id="netzach3_intro_x1">(You managed to find Netzach)</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n1">Yo, what’s up, manager? You look really super today. So, you… uh… succeeded with something, huh? Right, far out man.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n2">Man, why’s the ground shaking like that? Is it another breach?  </text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n3">Lemme guess what you’re thinking.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n4">“Netzach’s just a pathetic junkie, he’s not at all like Miss Hardworking Malkuth or Mister Strict Yesod.”</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n5">I know, I’ve read your mind.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n6">I get that a lot from the other Sephirot.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n7">But, just think about it for a sec.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n8">This place is hell.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n9">Is it wrong to try and escape from that reality for even just a moment?</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n10">Look, I think we should be celebrating the fact that we survived another day.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n11">I don’t give a damn about the future of the company or whatever like that.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n12">There’s no tomorrow here. No hope.</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n13">What have I done wrong?</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n14">Am I being punished for my sins? Did I do something horrible enough in the past to deserve this never-ending torment?</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n15">If that’s the case, I repent, so tell whoever did this all to forgive me…</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n16">...</text>
  <text id="netzach3_intro_n17">Forget it, I just… want to see this place crumble to pieces…</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta1">Netzach’s done it again, Lady Angela!</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a1">What has he done this time?</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta2">He finally gave me the report of our joint operation just now; it was due yesterday!</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta3">I can’t even find him anywhere now. I’m sure he’s just sleeping away somewhere, drunk as a fish.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a2">The Upper Sephirot should know where he is, go ask them.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta4">I don’t want to talk to them!</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta5">Lady Angela, you must agree with me when I say that Netzach is lacking in way too many ways to be even a decent Sephirah.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a3">What is the point you are trying to make here, Tiphereth?</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta6">…I am suggesting that we should replace Netzach.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a4">Tiphereth.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a5">The replacement process is not meant to be a tool you can haphazardly abuse to remove any Sephirah you dislike.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta7">I’m not abusing it! If I were, I would have replaced a majority of our Sephirot already.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a6">The Sephirot can only be replaced when they have what we consider to be a serious flaw, and can no longer perform their duties.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta8">Netzach easily meets any condition of flaw that could be set, then; he’s not doing a single thing right…</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a7">Netzach is playing his role. Being drunk on Enkephalin, becoming lethargic... it’s all part of the play.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a8">Let me add one more thing, Tiphereth. Even if we were to replace Netzach, do you really think that the new Netzach would become a diligent, hard-working Sephirah, wholly unlike the previous one?</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta9">…………</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a9">Please refrain from talking about the replacement process in such a rash manner.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta10">…………</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_a10">I know how you feel, but Netzach is a different matter.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta11">…………</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n1">Tiphereth, I have a pounding headache. Could you not shout?</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta12">I reminded Lady Angela about the replacement process!</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta13">Your days of irresponsibility will soon be over!</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n2">You think I’d be scared of a threat like that? I hate to disappoint you…</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n3">But that’s exactly what I want, Tiphereth. Don’t you get it?</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_ta14">…Let’s see you say that when you’re crushed into a pile of scrap.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n4">…..Manager, I don’t really care whether you completed that last mission or not.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n5">I bet Miss Angela’s having regrets as well.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n6">I feel the exact same way about myself as little Tiphereth does, you see.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n7">Why haven’t I been smashed up yet? Miss Angela could get someone better than me to fill my position anytime she likes.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n8">If I was her, I’d have destroyed an AI like myself at the first chance I could get.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n9">.........</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n10">Well, this is awkward.</text>
  <text id="netzach4_intro_n11">I don’t expect you to say something nice to me. Don’t worry about it.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n1">Be honest with me, man. You’re not coming to these meetings with me for praise, are you?</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n2">Aren’t you sick and tired of this?</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n3">You’ll do something great tomorrow yet again, though it won’t be anything all that “great”, and Miss Angela and the other Sephirot will shower you with compliments.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n4">We’ll have another accident in my department, a couple will fall down and die, some will go nuts, and a pile of ‘em will get injuries they’ll never recover from.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n5">Hod will try and cheer me up. Yesod will lecture me about what “regulations” I didn’t follow. Malkuth will try to encourage me, lively as usual. “Let’s try harder tomorrow!” …</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n6">Nobody will say to my face that it’s my fault, but it’ll be clear as day that I’m responsible for all of it, surely.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n7">My day always repeats like that.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n8">Starts with death. Ends with death.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n9">Every employee here regularly receives a small dose of a certain drug. Did you know?</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n10">It helps them become desensitized to everything.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n11">Just think about it. If your good ol’ lunchmate is found dead, torn into thousands of pieces, who in the world would be able to clean up his dead body without a single drop of emotion?</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n12">Could you blame them? Would you call them cowards for depending on drugs?</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n13">Everyone’s just trying to escape from this reality in their own ways.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n14">They might look and pretend to be okay, but nobody really is.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n15">I keep thinking about how I can off myself.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n16">I know, it’s like a metaphor. Death for us is a hypothetical concept.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n17">I heard injecting substances like Enkephalin into machines will slowly but surely rust them.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n18">Then, maybe I could chug a whole bottle into my body.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n19">Give myself irreversible damage.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n20">...Funny. I just injected myself with way more Enkephalin than I usually do.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n21">Yet my mind is clearer than ever. Hell, I feel completely lucid right now.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n22">If I were to open my eyes again, maybe it’ll be somewhere without you, those other Sephirot, or that Angela.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_n23">It hasn’t been fun. Let’s never meet again.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A1">We began our research on Cogito in earnest. The most urgent issue that prevailed at the time was the correct dosage.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A2">I tried to persuade people. I told them we have to proceed with the experiment in order to save Carmen and the others.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A3">Everyone fell silent when I asked for volunteers. Then, one man quietly raised his hand.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A4">It was Giovanni, who had kept to himself for most of his time here.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A5">Giovanni was one of the patients from Carmen’s company. I heard they had known each other since childhood.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A6">There is no such thing as a noble sacrifice. The end is always miserable, no matter how justifiable a cause it may be for.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A7">My statement that this experiment could bring back Carmen must have been the strongest motivation that drove him to volunteer.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A8">An experiment to find the proper dosage of a drug is not something that can be done in just a trial or two.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A9">I never talked with him much. We had nothing in common, other than our acquaintance with Carmen.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A10">Cogito emaciates the boundary of a human.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_intro_A11">And repeated experiments will leave an indelible mark.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_selection1">Inject Cogito.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_selection2">Inject Cogito.</text>
  <text id="netzach5_selection3">Inject Cogito.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n1">If Carmen was here, she’d laugh so hard at seeing the two of us talking like this.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n2">I mean, we’ve never really talked to each other.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n3">After all, I was here because I trusted Carmen, not you.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n4">I hope this’ll bring Carmen back to life.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_A1">We couldn’t save her.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_A2">It was the result that I had been expecting since the very start.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_A3">I couldn’t answer his last words because I didn’t want to desolate the only hope he had left.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_A4">That was my selfishness, believing that he would be at least happy in a fleeting dream he could not wake from, lying in restless sleep.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n5">So, I totally failed on that Enkephalin “experiment” of mine, seeing that I’m facing you right now.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n6">I’ll have to check out another way next time.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n7">…Don’t worry, I’m just kidding. Don’t peep a word of this to Miss Angela or the other Sephirot. They’d have a field day.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n8">I heard treatment is needed for a while because my parts were full of Enkephalin.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n9">It’ll probably be tough.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n10">Bit painful, too.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n11">To be honest, I didn’t want to wake up ever again. It’s been a while since I’ve had such a long sleep.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n12">But somewhere deep in my flickering consciousness, someone called out to me.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n13">That familiar, yet unfamiliar voice said this:</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n14">“No, you cannot. Here, you must ask my permission for anything. Even for death.”</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n15">And then you saved me.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n16">Opened my eyes once again to here where we stand, sadly.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n17">This place will never be safe.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n18">It’s impossible, even if everyone tries.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n19">Well, there is something to get out of all this.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n20">It’s to try and live.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n21">Even though life is full of pain, if I have to find and hold onto even the tiniest speck of possibility, if that’s what you and the voice wished for…</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n22">I can’t help but give a shot at living up to your hopes, now can I?</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n23">From the get-go, I had no respect for you. You know that?</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n24">But for the first time, I think that maybe it was me who called you.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n25">You came to ruin me, but also to save me.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n26">I think we’re both in a similar situation.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n27">We were both caught up in the karma of the past.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n28">I’m not the one who has changed.</text>
  <text id="netzach6_intro_n29">It’s you, manager. You’re the one who’s finally starting to see clearly.</text>
</localize>