<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y1">…</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y2">Manager, you are the head of this corporation. You are supposed to set an example for others, but that outfit would warrant at least 10 penalty points in our department. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y3">The manager should be no exception. However, the rules state that a Sephirah has no authority to impose penalty points on the manager, so I must let you off for now.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y4">I am Yesod, the Sephirah of the Information Team. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y5">The Information Team is in charge of processing and archiving all the data of our company. New information is generated every day, and we need to ensure that the information is accurate, so we must concentrate and focus on our job at all times.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y6">It may be compared to a massive bibliotheca.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y7">A single bit of misinformation could lead to an uncontrollable disaster.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y8">I am sure you can understand the gravity of my work.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y9">Every sliver of the information that you read contains the despair and desperation of our employees.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y10">Please do not think lightly of that information. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y11">….</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y12">It seems you are curious about my outfit.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y13">I have an aversion to exposing any part of my body.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y14">I don’t exactly remember when I started feeling this way... </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y15">But it’s likely that I’ve been this way even before I joined the company.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n1">Yesod, do you have any spare paper? Our department could use some.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y16">Netzach, the rules state that we’re not supposed to trade resources between teams. It should be in the very first page of the Sephirah manual.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n2">Alright, alright. Stop giving me that sharp look, Mister “Viper”.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y17">....</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n3">Welp, I’m heading out. Not in the mood to get bitten today.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y18">What are you trying to say with that expression of yours? Is this entertaining to you? Does the nickname make you laugh?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y19">……My apologies. I… overreacted a bit.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y20">The other Sephirot simply use my nickname as a joke.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y21">But others use it in a more serious manner.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y22">I know there are many employees who genuinely despise me.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y23">Nicknames may be a childish thing, but there’s no better way to describe a person in such few words.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y24">I personally like my nickname.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y25">What’s your opinion, manager?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_selection1">I like the sound of it.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_selection2">Doesn’t have a nice ring to it.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y1_1">Seems we’re in agreement then. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y2_1">Is that so? Well, it may sound odd, but I’m still satisfied with it.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y26">I should get going now.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y27">I need to finish today’s work.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y28">Oh, and I must send you the next assignment. </text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1">You’ve exceeded my expectations, despite your first impression. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2">Allow me to explain your next—</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h1">Yesod! I just heard that your team had a ton of casualties!</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y3">How many times has it been now?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h2">Shouldn’t you… be at your team’s side? It looked super depressing over there.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y4">Accidents happen. I want them to understand that it’s not a big fuss. Dwelling on it only encourages them to cry more, and it will eventually tire them out.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h3">But… people have died. Maybe you should say something, like, at least some half-hearted commemorative speech to cheer the employees up…? I mean, we should lead our departments and all...</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y5">Perhaps your aim is different from mine, then. I see no point in being sentimental. Caring too much about the respect of employees or the little complaints they make will steer you away from what’s truly important. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h4">Well, I’m just saying… I guess there’s no right answer, is there? We’re both busy, so I’ll see you later!</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y6">What do you think, manager? Should I go comfort them for the sake of the department’s morale?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_selection1">Yes, you should.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_selection2">No, it’s not a necessity.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_1">I’m honestly surprised to hear that from you.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_2">Do you think it’s realistic for you to show up in every department every single time an accident occurs?  </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_3">You, the man who spends the whole day incessantly watching employees die through that shiny monitor of yours?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_4">I take it that you are only saying this because you’re inexperienced and are still clinging onto the vague sense of goodwill, manager. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_5">Such shallow sympathy does no good in the corporation, so I urge you to be rid of it.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_1">A gesture of “goodwill” without sincerity is nothing more than an act of diplomacy, after all. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_2">We're not the ones whose lives are on the line. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_3">We don’t live with the risk of every moment possibly being the last.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_4">Nor are we always so close to death’s touch as to not have any attachment to life or worldly values.  </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_5">I disagree with the way Hod copes with it. She just seeks to comfort her own mind and turns a blind eye to reality. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_6">It’d be much more helpful to work hard to find ways to minimize casualties in the future.</text>
  <!--에피소드 3-->
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_1">The letter Z… Hmm... Zoo!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_1">O… Ox!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_2">Hey, that’s cheating! That’s not a place at all! Doesn’t count.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y1">…</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_3">Oops, I didn’t know you were here, Sephirah Yesod, sir!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_2">Sorry, I know we aren’t supposed to slack during work hours… But he insisted we…</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_4">What?! You started it! You wanted to get back at me for last time, remember?</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_3">Shut it, you dork!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y2">I’ll think about the appropriate response for this case later. You two, focus on your work.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_et_1">O-Of course, Sephirah, sir! We’re sorry!</text>
  <!-- et는 직원 1,2를 의미-->
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y3">Looks like word chaining is starting to become one of the more popular pastimes here again.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y4">Do you happen to enjoy word chaining, manager?</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y5">(Yesod begins to get lost in thought.)</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y6">James, you know you can’t enter the cell for work when your mental corruption level is above 80%. It’s against the rules. </text>
  <!-- 과거 회상 시작-->
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j1">I know, I know. Just this once, please? You know what happens if I fail to finish the assigned work regime! Besides, you know how Sally went in at 82% one time and came out fine? And I’m only at 81%! Please?</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y7">....... </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j2">Come on, what are friends for? Act so strict and the employees will end up isolating you. It’ll be so lonely. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y8">.......</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j3">Just kidding! Even if all the employees were to hate you, I’ll still be your playmate!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y9">You know that the word “playmate” has no place in this corp— </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j4">Whoops! My bad, my bad! Anyway, can I please get to work now, my lord Yesod~? Don’t forget that I cut you some slack yesterday when we were playing word chain.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y10">...Fine, but just this once.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y11">And make sure to take a psychological examination right afterwards. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j5">You bet! Thank you, Yesod! See you in a bit! </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y12">At times, I see hallucinations when I change my clothes.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y13">Through the clothing, I can see my skin covered with festering boils.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y14">Of course, my body is perfectly fine when I open my eyes.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y15">It has come to a point where I’ve begun to find the sight of my normal skin strange and unnatural.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y16">I cannot help but ask myself, “Why is my body intact? Why is it not rotting?”</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y17">I’ve asked the other Sephirot about those visions, but it seems I’m the only one who experiences this.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y1">That day, James released two Abnormalities on purpose, and eventually three clerks and four agents were killed.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y2">As you may know, having two Abnormalities breach and losing four agents is a rather significant loss of manpower.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y3">Of course, it was I who ordered for James to be gunned down.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y4">I know the kind of place we work in.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y5">I am not regretful for the fact that I was unable to stop him.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y6">It’s that I regret having developed a personal relationship with him.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y7">I was careless with my position and let my subordinate exploit me.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y8">Chatting, games, yes—all of it was fun.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y9">James was a good joker too.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y10">Of course I had fun playing word chain.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y11">We grew so intimate that I would forgive his “trivial” rule violations.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y12">But the price I had to pay for the error I made was not trivial in any way.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y13">Manager, this is Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y14">We see body bags every single day.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y15">It’s a lonely place. </text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y16">Sometimes, you will feel the urge to share the distress and anxiety with someone else; to have a friend. </text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y17">But manager, whenever you feel lonely, please remember what happened to me. And try not to make the same mistake as I did.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y18">You will be able to get over the meaningless deaths that way.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y19">I envy Angela. She is truly a heartless monster.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y20">People say that I am too rational.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y21">“Yesod the Cold-blooded Machine”, “Yesod the Viper”, “Yesod the Cruel and Emotionless”. A frigid being who won’t even bat an eye at the deaths of dozens of employees...</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y22">I won’t deny that I deserve the reputation.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y23">However, whoever built this place has to be a much more cruel person than I am.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y24">Sometimes, I wish I were an AI without emotion.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y25">A vague sense of sympathy will only cloud your judgement. You are bound to make mistakes that way.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y26">Why would they place AIs with emotion to handle the facility, if they were well aware that emotion would only get in the way?</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y27">Do you know the answer?</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="yesod5_intro_h1">Yesod, do you really feel nothing about this?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_n1">Try drinking some Enkephalin. Close your eyes, and open them again.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a1">I am glad to see that you are not as feeble-minded as the other Sephirot. It is important to keep a clear mind in any situation.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A1">…....Gabriel, why are you scratching yourself so much?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y1">Seeing as we’re meeting again, you must have completed your tasks, manager.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y2">I’d give you a compliment if I didn’t have so much work to do.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y3">The Information Team has a task they must do periodically.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y4">You must have realized that there are some blanks in the Abnormality Records.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y5">Among the tremendous amount of information we gather, there are some that should remain off limits to the employees for security reasons.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y6">The names of the employees are one such thing.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y7">Any trace of them. What happened, their gruesome death, their desperate will to live, all of that has been stripped from the records on the false pretense of “expunging information.”</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y8">There is no way for me to know what the criteria for stripping the records are. They are set by another department, not us.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y9">We only manipulate the information we receive, per orders.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y10">Isn’t it funny?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y11">We’ve degenerated into a department that destroys and manipulates information as ordered, yet somehow we’re still called the “Information Team”. </text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y12">Whenever I introduce myself as the Sephirah of the Information Team…</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y13">I sometimes feel something bubbling up inside of me.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a2">Yesod, did you receive the documents to expunge?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a3">You will get the list of employees soon as well. Please do not forget to review it after you have finished expunging the documents.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y14">Ms. Angela, what do you think it means to remember someone’s name?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a4">This is a work you regularly do. Why are you so emotional about it today?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y15">Maybe names were marks atypical beings gave each other, to engrave each other upon their memories.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y16">Someone might have named you Angela following the same concept.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a5">Yesod, if you happen to be too tired, please take a break.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y17">I knew you would say that.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a6">I’m glad you know.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y18">........</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y19">Referring to employees by name is not recommended here.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y20">When employees first enter the company, each one receives their own unique identification number.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y21">This is to allow the company to identify them using the minimum amount of personal information.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y22">We have their numbers in our data storage devices.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y23">Malkuth has never called the employees by their names ever since she started working here.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y24">Maybe she is the most ideal Sephirah amongst all us Sephirot.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y25">This is not to say that Malkuth deserves to take all the pain as well.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y26">None of us do.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y27">What kind of poor taste is that, to lock us inside metal bodies, and throw us into an endless loop of days that feel just the same as yesterday?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y28">I’m talking to you. What’s with that oblivious expression?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y29">I heard you might be one of the architects responsible for our creation.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y30">The only thing I could do here is remember the names of a few forgotten employees, and eternally despair…</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y31">Feeling nauseous from even a single breath of air…</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y32">Have you had fun watching your guinea pigs run around in circles?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y33">......</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y34">See, I told you, I have been rotting from the inside for a long time…</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A2">Gabriel was more rational than anyone else.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A3">He was unmoved, even after hearing about what happened to Elijah.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A4">Some said he lacked empathy.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A5">But nobody realized that his emotions were festering on the inside.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A6">Maybe he began falling apart from long ago, ever since Carmen left this world.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A7">He slowly became expressionless. He wouldn’t allow himself to have even a paltry joy.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A8">He also couldn’t stand having even the smallest part of his body exposed.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A9">We made a monster that was not supposed to exist in this world. We went too far to ever turn back.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A10">To not let what Elijah did be in vain, instead of taking the time to grieve, everyone knew they needed to utilize this result to the fullest.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A11">He tried to maintain a facade of level-headedness, but his attempts to remain rational slowly morphed into an obsession.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A12">He started to wear long sleeved clothing that also covered his neck. Not much later, he started to scratch himself harshly.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A13">We suggested he receive a complete medical examination to see whether he was contaminated or had an infection, but he refused.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection1">Enforce the procedure.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection2">Enforce the procedure.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection3">Enforce the procedure.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A14">Health check-ups were needed to prevent further damage. Persuasion became coercion, and coercion led to the use of physical force.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A15">He was tied and bound for the check-up, but he resisted so desperately that it was hard for us to watch him.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A16">Eventually, it turned out that he wasn’t infected at all.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A17">Was that really fortunate, though?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A18">No, it wasn’t. The examination did not resolve anything. He kept scratching himself. So harshly… Even worse than before…</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A19">When I saw him last, he wasn’t lucid or cognizant to any human speech, and his body was completely covered in scratches.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A20">No one has seen him since then.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y1">....I heard about Elijah, I’m sorry.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y2">I guess now everyone should know that there are consequences to forcefully entering a laboratory with restricted access.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y3">Also, you were very careless not to put the supply room key back in its proper place.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y4">You may think I am being too strict, but I can’t help it. I’m not saying anything false.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y5">We should set up a time for when keys must be returned to prevent people like you from causing this again.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y6">"…………"</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y7">I wore this to prevent chemicals from splashing on my body.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y8">Don’t worry, I’m just a little tired.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y9">No need to show concern. I’ll go prepare for the upcoming experiment.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A1">Wounds have a way of revealing themselves, even for those who wish to keep them concealed.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A2">For Gabriel, it was the change in his clothes.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A3">Maybe it was easier on his mind to conclude that Elijah’s death was caused by a violation of the rules.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A4">He tried harder to stick to his principles. He tried to maintain his objectivity.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A5">But perhaps his excessive rationality is what destroyed him.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A6">His earnest hope to not see anyone else die couldn’t reach me.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A7">No, there is no point in lying anymore. I pretended that I didn’t hear his desperate cry.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y10">"…………"</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y11">There’s no need to ask if I’m doing alright.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y12">I heard about what you and I did yesterday.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y13">I felt like it was the first time I lost myself.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y14">It was not quite pleasant, but it was not as terrible as I expected it to be, either.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y15">Rather, I feel relieved.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y16">Not to say that all the hatred that surrounds me has completely washed away.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y17">I’ll still see that rotting hallucination, and sometimes I’ll feel disgusted, and have an unbearable anger towards you.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y18">However, if there is one aspect that has changed...</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y19">It’s that I can be in as much despair as I want to now.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y20">Someday, a hope will painfully grow out of the rotten wound.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y21">What you gave to us was a seed of hope.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y22">It seems that you’re also on the way to embracing your painful past.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y23">It’s always the beginning that’s difficult.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y24">And your outfit still isn’t up to the company standard.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y25">I suppose I should seriously consider having penalty points apply even to the manager.</text>
</localize>