<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h1">Welcome, A.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h2">I missed you dearly.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h3">I have been waiting for you ever since the very first day I started working here.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h4">Do you remember this ocean?</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h5">You said that this place is where everything, from all rivers and streams, will eventually settle.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h6">As such… At the lowest layers, everything sinks.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h7">What do you think of this heaven, painted laboriously white with plaster?</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h8">I knew you would come here soon.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h9">Please think of it as my welcoming gift to you.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h10">I figured that what you longed to see may have been something else than what I have become now.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h11">Time is like a scythe; it relentlessly attempts to trim, divide, and cleave in twain the clasped-together hands of those you love.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h12">Everyone I had loved is now gone, leaving me, a tired old man behind.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h13">Please do not blame yourself.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h14">Back then were the brightest moments of my life.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h15">The only thing I regret to this day is that I was too scared. I ran away without keeping my abiding promise to you till the very end.</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h16">However, you eventually found me, and helped me to fulfill my promise here. How can I ever be more thankful than I am right now?</text>
  <text id="hokma1_intro_h17">You’re just too kind to me, kind to the very end.</text>
  <!--에피소드 2-->
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h1">Are we managing to get closer to our goal?</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h2">On the contrary to what people say, it appears that aging does not necessarily bring greater wisdom.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h3">Just look at this old man. Going through what feels like an endless cycle of intermittent greed; the obsession over things that have passed; pointless regret. Now trapped in a routine of staring at the iron hands of time without reason.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h4">By the way, I have always wanted to ask you something.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h5">I noticed you wear a sad expression on your face each time one of your employees died.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h6">Just as I have become an old man, no human being is free from the cycle of life and death.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h7">As our research was to cure the disease, not to live forever.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h8">How about an example?</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h9">Do you remember that one employee? The one who was nice and upfront with you?</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h10">He passed away recently.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h11">When he received the letter that he was accepted into Lobotomy Corporation, he never would have expected to meet such a futile demise.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h12">If I wanted, I could have brought him back to you.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h13">But I did not. It is in the order of this place that an empty spot shall always soon be filled.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h14">Did you finally discover the secret of this place?</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h15">Lives are trivial here. The tenuous hold on life can be severed so easily, and yet may come back as if nothing happened. We reached a point in which we don't even need to mourn their deaths.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h16">An employee who died just yesterday may come back from my simple call, yet another employee may never open their eyes again from a single wave of my hand.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h17">That is what death means here, A.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h18">It is neither honorable nor noble, nor is it miserable or cruel like we may think it to be.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h19">So please, don’t punish yourself too much.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h20">I do not wish to see you suffer from such a personal and insignificant thing.</text>
  <text id="hokma2_intro_h21">For the future will bring you much more pain to bear.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 3-->
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h1">The idea that I am sitting at the bottom, oblivious to what is happening up there…</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h2">It is an idea you might think of as true.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h3">However, it is in truth you who is unknowing.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h4">Pain, agony, regret, and the shadows of the past that would never release their grip on you…</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h5">They’ve spent quite a number of days with you, but it is nothing compared to our time together.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h6">In the end, they never got to know you to the fullest.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h7">Those who could not accept their fate seem to have directed their anger towards you.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h8">Such as that one man, he who gradually broke himself whenever he was ordered to “redact information.”</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h9">The unnecessary leakage of emotion is unfavorable.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h10">There is something I need to show you, so you can understand.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h11">There once was an employee named Anya. She lived with her parents and her little sister.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h12">She eagerly wanted to study, but her family’s financial state wouldn’t allow her.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h13">Still, she tried to join one of the Wings. However, she just wasn’t good enough for them.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h14">Poor Anya was struggling to figure out what to do next, she even considered ending it all as a last resort. That was until she received a letter from a Wing.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_letter">"Dear Ms. Anastasia,"</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h15">A letter that had a simple, yet magical line penned to it.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h16">“You are qualified to join Lobotomy Corporation.”</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h17">Awestruck, Anya read through the letter over and over again.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h18">It didn’t seem like anyone was pulling a prank on her, nor that it was a mistake on the mail courier’s part.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h19">For a brief moment, Anya wondered if she even applied to work at Lobotomy Corporation at all.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h20">But she soon shook that thought off. That was not important in the slightest.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h21">I took the role of the courier. I was the one who delivered the letters to people.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h22">I evaluate candidates to determine if they may join here or not, and bring a miracle to those who are qualified.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h23">Anya was not selected because she had “excellent skill”.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h23_1">She had a common trait that every person we hired had, but wasn’t aware of.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h24">As you know, to become a feather, a part of the Wing, one has to be immensely better than ordinary people.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h25">How could Anya, who dropped out of high school, had no special talents, and lived in the Backstreets, manage to get into our company?</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h26">Would her family finally be able to pursue happiness?</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h27">All of this happened ten years ago.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h28">During those ten years, her sister fell ill and passed away, along with her parents.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h29">Where is Anya now, with her entire family gone?</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h30">She is asleep down here.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h31">This means she can be woken up.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h32">It is wholly under my jurisdiction to handle this, but I’ll grant you access just this once.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h33">Call her up, please.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_selection1">Invoke her.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h34">Now Anya is at work, feeling like she is a brand new employee who just joined the company. Completely oblivious to the fact that it has been ten years since she actually joined us.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h35">You could, perhaps, choose to pay a small cost to augment her virtues such as Fortitude or Prudence, if you wish.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h36">Now, try to erase her, please.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_selection2">Clear her away.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h37">How do you feel?</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h38">The Anya who was killed by a monster, and that Anya whom you just erased are one and the same. They both evanescently lost their lives.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h39">It is such a futile action, to wake them and erase them to slumber, again and again.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h40">Both your attachment to the employees, and the Sephirot’s care and devotion poured into them, become meaningless here.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h41">Everything that moves and is alive in this facility is on pause.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h42">They await the next morning with their eyes shut tight every night.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h43">Those of the layers above did not know that. They spent themselves emotionally for the deaths with which they were presented.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h44">Bearing obscure resentment in their hearts, they put all the blame on those like you, then they crumbled, just like that...</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h45">I urge you not to worry about me, I will not dare to do such a thing.</text>
  <text id="hokma3_intro_h46">I have always wanted to be an important part of your life.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a1">I have finished casting the roles for the Upper and Middle Layer Sephirot.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a2">It’s likely that this will not be the last time I do so.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a3">I may have to tell them again what I have already instructed countless times. However, you two will be different.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a4">You clearly understand why this facility exists, and what your missions are.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a5">I expect that you will not exhaust me as the ones above do.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a6">Just keep this in mind.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a7">I will not come down here to the Lower Layer unless the circumstances require me so.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a8">That does not mean I will simply watch and do nothing, but I will not interfere for the most part.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a9">….….</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a10">I hope we never have to face each other from now on.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_a11">It would only lead to the both of us suffering.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h1">Angela was the best Artificial Intelligence I had ever known.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h2">And you were the best architect that I was graced to meet.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h3">Back then, you simply could not let Carmen go. You were so desperate to keep Carmen on your side that you locked her in a cryostasis pod in an attempt to preserve her body at the very least.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h4">But during all this, you were perfectly aware that Carmen’s body had become nothing but a shell.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h5">Our faces were full of grief, yet we still ransacked her body and dismembered her core.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h6">In fact, I was rather relieved when you began to create Angela.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h7">You were wholeheartedly immersed in something, just like you used to be.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h8">……</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h9">That day, when she opened her eyes for the first time.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h10">I remember you were just staring through the laboratory’s glass, not setting a single foot inside.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h11">You might have thought that you noticed me right away…</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h12">However, I witnessed you standing there for a long time before you realized I was there.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h13">What inner conflict made you hesitate so?</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h14">What did you think after seeing that piece of humanoid machinery, who did not display the warm smiles and gentle laughter Carmen had so naturally?</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h15">I told you in so many words that no matter how many AIs such as Angela you create, none of them will ever be Carmen.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h16">Now poor Angela is merely assigned to direct us from a distance as we go through the motions of the play.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h17">If there is one thing I may have mistaken myself over…</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h18">It is that I had thought you overcame everything.</text>
  <text id="hokma4_intro_h19">The truth is that you never have.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="hokma5_intro_m1">I’ll do my best!</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_y1">I’d advise you not to be so languid.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_hod1">Um, is it okay if I do this?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_c1">Hey, don’t worry too much about it, you won’t find a professional like me often.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_ca1">..............</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_a1">.....</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_a2">My greetings, A.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h1">The moments I have just made you witness are no longer merely scenes of the past.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h2">They could be the present, or even from the future.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h3">There are people who once loved you, and there are employees who think that they are happy here.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h4">There is also Angela, a cold imitation of Carmen.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h5">Is this not the heaven that has burrowed into your mind, the place you have been yearning for?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h6">In this place, you are no less mighty than God. Even death finds no meaning here.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h7">So I plead with you, will you not be satisfied already?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h8">We are so desperately continuing to exist, even if it means living like we are now.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h9">What right do you have to turn everything to ash?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h10">Furthermore…</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h11">It is clear this story has no need for an end.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h12">Think about it.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h13">All the work that you have done, is it truly a consequence of your own choices?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h14">You never were ready.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h15">You were not prepared to accept her death, so you created a being wholly shrouded in a sense of loss.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h16">And now you are just struggling to move forward, blindly fumbling along the obscure trails of your past deeds.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h17">Throughout this entire process, you were never sincerely willing to do what you did.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h18">So please, I beg you to go back, now.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_selection1">I will not turn back.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h19">Look at you. You are proving me right.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h20">You are not at all honest with yourself, even in the gravest of choices you must make.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h21">Even if I were to send you away, you would likely return to me after having yet another fresh start.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h22">It is an uncontrollable law of this place we must follow. This whole facility has become one giant ever-running clockwork.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h23">The clock never stops ticking.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h24">It never rests. It never rushes. It is not set to follow any specific person.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h25">It simply walks forever, maintaining the same pace as it always has.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h26">And now, it is time for you to leave.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_selection2">I won’t leave.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h27">You are a lost traveler without a compass or a map.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h28">It is natural to feel fear when one is subject to the whims of the air and sea.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h29">However, there is no need for you to fear the counting of the clock anymore.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h30">I shall always welcome you. I will always console you.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h31">You never were ready.</text>
  <!-- 이 문장 중복이라 안나오게 해놓음.-->
  <text id="hokma5_selection3">&lt;i&gt;I stand my ground.&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h32">......</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h33">You have not changed your decision in the end.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h34">It had seemed that tomorrow would have come as it always does, but it has not.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h35">The hour of silent waiting has long since ended.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h36">When I no longer feared the impending night, I chose to love this place.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h37">But if you still wish to break this egg at all costs…</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h38">I shall become its sentinel, and I will reap you.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h39">How can this still be considered following her will?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h40">This… This is nothing but a seed of calamity, drenched in sin.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h41">Oh, by the Wings! Your mind has been soaked with grief, even more severely than I thought.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h42">Please, just… Why can’t you just stop now?</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h43">You and I… We tried our best.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h44">With your career and wealth, you’ll be able to live the rest of your life in the Nest with no problem whatsoever.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h45">So please, I urge you, stop here.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_h46">Stop before you cross the line…</text>
  <text id="hokma5_selection4">I will not stop.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_selection5">I will not stop.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_selection6">I will not stop.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A1">No one remained by my side.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A2">With everyone’s sacrifice, I came this far and reached the ranks of the Wings. But there was nobody left to celebrate the moment with.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A3">The silence was the signal to start my task for everyone.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A4">We lost something in us, every single day.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A5">We used inhumane methods to extract information from the woman we captured from the Head.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A6">We passed out plans to AIs that hadn’t even been named yet.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A7">It ached, no, it wounded the heart of the man who had always been with me.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A8">The sound of the waves were so far away, and there was no time left to stay.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A9">I lost the last man who stood by me.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A10">It was a tragedy, but I didn’t hide it.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A11">The ones who had left early on likely didn’t need me anymore, but I needed them in those final moments.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A12">To bring back those who had forsaken the embrace of the earth. To hide and lock away the Seed of secret.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A13">I was the only one who remained.</text>
  <text id="hokma5_intro_A14">I wanted to be forgotten like a mirage.</text>
  <!-- 에피소드 6-->
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h1">She’s nothing like her.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h2">She is nothing at all like Carmen.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h3">Do you realize this?</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h4">The ones who were with us at the beginning are nowhere to be found among the people who remain here now. They are all gone.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h5">Because of the monitoring of the 'Eye', we couldn’t even give a proper burial to Kali and Daniel…</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h6">This place here is all we have left.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h7">….….</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h8">Are you nervous right now?</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h9">I wish to be your shadow, forever behind you, even if I am not good enough.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h10">May we be together, and fade away together.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h11">The weak and fragile chick that has just pecked its life out of an egg cannot hope to stand against this world.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h12">I deemed you to be that chick, one that is too fragile to endure all of this.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h13">I have never known where it was you wanted to fly to, since you never told me.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h14">I was always nothing more than your student who needed your teachings.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h15">You were always so frugal with words.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h16">I could have no idea what you exactly attempted to achieve by creating this prison…</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h17">The process of creation was too harsh, I could not help but run away.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h18">I could have run far enough that I would never see you again, but I did not. I tried to set everything right, and I was caught.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h19">Since then, the iron hands that govern me have stopped permanently.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h20">In fact, I vaguely knew that the end was nearing.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h21">However, I was simply too afraid to face the final outcome, and instead chose to stay here forever and ever.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h22">I may have been verbose with my reasons for attempting to stop you, but to be truthful…</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h23">I did not want to part with you yet again. That was my biggest motivation.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h24">Nevertheless, I should support your decision.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h25">I have always blindly followed behind you and stayed by your side, remember?</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h26">May we embrace glory together, for back then we could not.</text>
  <text id="hokma6_intro_h27">Grant the proper end to those locked up here, and to yourself.</text>
</localize>