<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
=============== NOTICE ==================
Changes at 1.26
  Manual_SubCategory_27
  Manual_SubCategory_28
  
  Manual_Node_5
  
  Manual_Node_34
  
  Manual_Node_38
  Manual_Node_39
  Manual_Node_40
  Manual_Node_41
  Manual_Node_42
  
  Manual_Text_298
  Manual_Text_299
  
  Manual_Text_355
  Manual_Text_356
  
  Manual_Text_357
  Manual_Text_358
  Manual_Text_359
  
  Manual_Text_360
  Manual_Text_361
  Manual_Text_362
  Manual_Text_363
  Manual_Text_364
  Manual_Text_365
  Manual_Text_366
  Manual_Text_367
  Manual_Text_368
  
  Manual_Text_369
  Manual_Text_370
  Manual_Text_371
  Manual_Text_372
  Manual_Text_373
  Manual_Text_374
  Manual_Text_375
  Manual_Text_376
  Manual_Text_377
  
  Manual_Text_378
  Manual_Text_379
  
  Manual_Text_380
  Manual_Text_381
  Manual_Text_382
  Manual_Text_383
  Manual_Text_384
  Manual_Text_385
  Manual_Text_386
  Manual_Text_387
  
  >end of 1.26 changes
-->
<localize>
  <text id="Manual_MainCategory_0">Basic Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_MainCategory_1">Management Preparation</text>
  <text id="Manual_MainCategory_2">Management Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_MainCategory_3">Emergency Situations</text>
  <text id="Manual_MainCategory_4">Finishing Management</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_0">1. Your Goal as the Manager</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_1">2. The Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_2">3. Work Types</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_3">4. The Abnormalities </text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_4">5. Attack Types</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_5">6. E.G.O </text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_6">1. Deployment UI  </text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_7">2. Hiring and Fortifying</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_8">3. Using E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_9">4. Deploying Employees </text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_10">1. Management UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_11">2. Basic Controls</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_12">3. Agent Controls</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_13">4. Ordering Work</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_14">5. Containment UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_15">6. The Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_16">7. The Qliphoth Counter</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_17">8. Work-Count Penalties</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_18">10. Abnormality Observation</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_19">11. Tool Abnormalities</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_20">1. Possible Emergencies</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_21">2. Emergency Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_22">3. Suppressing Abnormalities</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_23">4. Managerial Bullets</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_24">1. End of the Day</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_25">2. The Memory Repository</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_26">3. Abnormality Extraction</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_27">4. Opening and Expanding</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_28">9. Department Functions</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_0">Who are the Agents?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_1">Levels and Promotion</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_2">What’s an Abnormality?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_3">Risk Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_4">The Rightside Panel</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_5">Department Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_6">Hiring Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_7">Fortifying Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_8">Opening the E.G.O List</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_9">E.G.O Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_10">E.G.O Weapons</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_11">E.G.O Suits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_12">Equipping E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_13">Viewing Agent Info </text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_14">Moving Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_15">Recalling Agents </text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_16">The Order UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_17">Orders via Left Click</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_18">Orders via Selected Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_19">Work Process Phases</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_20">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_21">Progressing the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_22">Ending the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_23">The Qliphoth Counter</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_24">The Qliphoth Meltdown</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_25">Ordeals</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_26">Qliphoth Overloads</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_27">Opening the Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_28">Observation</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_29">Production and Acquisition of E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_30">What are Tool Abnormalities?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_31">How to use Tools</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_32">Tool Observation </text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_33">Abnormality Escape</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_34">Employee Death</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_35">Suppression UI </text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_36">Orders via Left Click</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_37">Orders via Selected Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_38">The Abnormality Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_39">Reminders for moving Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_40">Clerk Benefits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_41">Continued Service Benefits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_42">Employee Panic</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_0">Your Goal as the Manager</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_1">1. You are in the role of the manager of Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_2">2. Your job is to safely manage Abnormalities and produce an energy source known as ‘Enkephalin’.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_3">3. You will have a daily quota that must be met each day in order to progress onto the next day. </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_4">Who are the Agents?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_5">The Agents are your subordinates, who follow your orders to work with Abnormalities. They are your hands, so to speak.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_6">Agent Virtues</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_7">Fortitude</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_8">The ‘HP’ of your Agents will increase as their Fortitude increases. An Agent’s Fortitude will increase any time they perform Instinct Work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_9">HP (Health Points): The physical strength and vitality of an Agent; if this drops to zero, they will die.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_10">Prudence</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_11">The ‘SP’ of your Agents will increase as their Prudence increases. An Agent’s Prudence will increase any time they perform Insight Work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_12">SP (Sanity Points): The mental strength and stability of an Agent; if this drops to zero, they will panic.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_13">Temperance</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_14">The ‘Work Speed’ and ‘Success Rate’ of your Agents will increase as their Temperance increases. An Agent’s Temperance will increase any time they perform Attachment Work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_15">Work Speed: The rate at which an Agent completes the Work Process with an Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_16">Success Rate: The ability of an Agent to succeed in their work, produce more Positive Enkephalin, and take less damage during the Work Process.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_17">Justice</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_18">The ‘Attack Speed’ and ‘Movement Speed’ of your Agents will increase as their Justice increases. An Agent’s Justice will increase any time they perform Repression Work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_19">Attack Speed: The rate at which an Agent attacks with their equipped E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_20">Movement Speed: The speed at which an Agent moves from one place to another.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_21">Levels and Promotion</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_22">Agent Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_23">Agents begin at Level 1 and can be promoted up to Level 5. The higher an Agent’s level, the greater skill and Virtues they have.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_24">Each Virtue also has a Level from 1 to 5.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_25">Agent Promotions</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_26">When stats rise to a certain threshold from working, the level of their Virtue will increase at the end of the day.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_27">The level of a Virtue corresponds to the level of the related Work the Agent can do.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_28">The Agent’s level is based on the sum of the levels of their Virtues; an Agent’s level will increase alongside their Virtues.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_29">Work Types</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_30">There are four (4) types of Work that can be performed with the Abnormalities. For each individual Abnormality, you will need to find the most appropriate type of Work, and steadily proceed to produce energy.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_31">Instinct</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_32">A work to satiate physiological needs; it requires physical contact. As it involves touching the Abnormality frequently, Agents will need to display a high level of bravery and Fortitude to perform high level Instinct Work. Employees who conduct this work will benefit from increased HP.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_33">Insight</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_34">A work to improve the Abnormality’s living conditions. As it involves realizing what environment each Abnormality favors the most and making appropriate adjustments to ensure optimal conditions, meticulous observation is required; Agents need to show a high level of intellect and Prudence to perform high level Insight Work. Employees who conduct this work will benefit from increased SP.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_35">Attachment</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_36">A work to satiate social needs. All Abnormalities carry desires and a will, and as such social needs are included. As this work involves acting as a playmate or companion, great care is required as only limited interaction is allowed; to avoid crossing the line, Agents need to show a high level of caution and Temperance to perform high level Attachment Work. Employees who conduct this work will benefit from increased Work Speed and Success Rates.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_37">Repression</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_38">A work to restrain existence. While the other works focus on handling desires, this one stifles them. As this work involves regulating various emotions and desires, careful and objective decision making as well as strong rationality is needed to control the pace of the work; Agents need to show a high level of Justice—the ability to make definite judgements—to perform high level Repression work. Employees who conduct this work will benefit from increased Attack and Movement Speed.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_39">What’s an Abnormality?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_40">Abnormalities are entities that emerge from the depths of humanity’s deep and ancient dreams: the Collective Unconscious. We can extract Enkephalin from them with careful and appropriate management.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_41">Risk Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_42">Please be aware that no Abnormality can ever truly be considered safe.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_43">Please refer to the Risk Level titles below when managing Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_44">A Containment Unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_45">The Abnormality Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_46">With little to no aggression, ZAYIN Abnormalities will cause the least harm to your Agents. Their damage tends to be minuscule, and they may have a positive effect on the employees.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_47">These Abnormalities can inflict varying degrees of injury to your employees. However, as long as your employees follow the proper managerial guidelines, they will not cause much damage.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_48">Abnormalities of this class can easily kill a number of employees. You will have to pay twice as much attention as you do for a ZAYIN or TETH. If the situation goes wrong, several employees could be lost in bloodshed. There’s no need to be concerned though; with your excellent management, they will be in control.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_49">These are high risk and carry devastating force. Most will be hostile toward employees, and the death toll could reach into the dozens.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_50">&lt;b&gt;The most dangerous.&lt;/b&gt; You should devote as much concentration and attention as possible to this Risk Level. You’ll be thankful if the Abnormality is suppressed without ravaging entire departments. &lt;i&gt;(Please do not take our warning as an exaggeration.)&lt;/i&gt;</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_51">Attack Types</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_52">The Abnormalities have four types of attacks:</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_53">RED</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_54">This type relates to physical damage. When RED damage is dealt, the HP of the receiver will be reduced.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_55">WHITE</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_56">While RED represents physical damage, WHITE represents psychological damage. When WHITE damage is dealt, the SP of the employee on the receiving end will be reduced.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_57">BLACK</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_58">A complex of physical and psychological damages. When BLACK damage is dealt, both the HP and SP of the employee on the receiving end will be reduced.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_59">PALE</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_60">Death itself. PALE shaves away the soul. Even the toughest body and wisest mind will not matter; all are equal in the face of death. When PALE damage is dealt, HP will be reduced in proportion to the maximum HP of the employee on the receiving end.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_61">E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_62">E.G.O (Extermination of Geometrical Organ) refers to the equipment produced to confront Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_63">We have E.G.O Weapons as a means of offense, and E.G.O Suits as defensive equipment.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_64">E.G.O can be extracted from Abnormalities that have been managed up to a certain Observation Level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_65">As E.G.O is forged using “archetypes” extracted from Abnormalities, they can inflict or resist RWBP damage types, which cannot be reproduced normally.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_66">Each E.G.O has a grade from ZAYIN to ALEPH. One thing you should know is that the higher the E.G.O’s grade, the more effective it becomes. E.G.O with a higher grade will have higher attack and defense power against certain attack types.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_67">The ATK - DEF Mechanism</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_68">E.G.O with a high grade will benefit from increased damage and defense against Abnormalities of a lower risk level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_69">Conversely, E.G.O with a low grade will deal less and take more damage against an Abnormality with a high risk level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_70">Deployment UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_71">The Rightside Panel</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_72">Viewing Highest Level Ordeal</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_73">Here you will be able to see the highest level of Ordeal that may appear during the current workday.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_74">Ordeals will manifest as the workday progresses.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_75">LOB Points</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_76">LOB are points you will acquire as you complete each day.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_77">LOB is used for hiring and fortifying Agents.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_78">The E.G.O List</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_79">This button will open the E.G.O List.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_80">Hiring</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_81">This button is for hiring new Agents.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_82">Department Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_83">Missions</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_84">Each department will display the missions that can be attempted for the day.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_85">If you clear a department’s mission, you will be able to conduct specialized research projects.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_86">Contained Abnormalities</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_87">Here you will see the Abnormalities currently placed within the department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_88">Abnormalities whose Encyclopedias do not yet have Basic Information unlocked will be displayed as a question mark (?).</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_89">Department Description</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_90">This button will allow you to view the description and role that pertain to the department and its team.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_91">Research</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_92">This button will allow you to view the completed research projects of the department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_93">Research will be very helpful for Abnormality management.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_94">Hiring Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_95">You can hire a new Agent by clicking the HIRE button.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_96">To hire a default random employee, simply click the HIRE button again.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_97">Default employees only require 1 LOB to be hired.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_98">Changing Virtue Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_99">You can adjust the level of each Virtue by clicking on the arrows.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_100">Additional LOB will be charged for raising a Virtue level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_101">Higher Virtue levels will require more LOB.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_102">Customizing Appearance</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_103">You can spend an additional 1 LOB to customize the appearance of a new hire.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_104">Fortifying Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_105">Agents who are already a part of your facility can be fortified using LOB by clicking this button.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_106">Deployed and undeployed Agents can be clicked on to view more information.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_107">Fortifying an already hired Agent uses the same menu as adjusting the Virtue levels of a new hire.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_108">Opening the E.G.O List</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_109">You can open the E.G.O List by simply clicking on the corresponding button.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_110">E.G.O Weapons</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_111">E.G.O Weapons are equipment that enhance one's offensive capabilities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_112">Attack Type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_113">The RWBP type of the E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_114">Damage</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_115">The range of possible damage values the E.G.O can inflict</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_116">Speed</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_117">The speed at which attacks are delivered</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_118">Attack Range</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_119">The distance necessary to land a blow with the E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_120">E.G.O Suits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_121">E.G.O Suits are equipment that enhance one's defensive capabilities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_122">The E.G.O’s defensive multiplier against each attack type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_123">If the multiplier is lower than 1.0, then the E.G.O will be effective against the corresponding attack type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_124">Likewise, if it is higher than 1.0, then the E.G.O will be vulnerable against the corresponding attack type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_125">E.G.O Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_126">E.G.O Sorting</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_127">You can view E.G.O of a specific grade by clicking on the grade’s corresponding tab.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_128">Details</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_129">This will display the detailed descriptions and any special abilities of the E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_130">Requisites</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_131">Some E.G.O may require certain Virtue levels or general Agent level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_132">E.G.O Gifts</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_133">Agents have a chance to acquire this form of E.G.O upon completion of a Work Process, or occasionally, via the fulfilment of special criteria. It will affect the various stats of an Agent.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_134">Equipping E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_135">Select the facility Layer.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_136">Select the desired Agent.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_137">Click on an E.G.O slot. The E.G.O cannot be equipped if the Agent does not meet the requirements.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_138">Here you will be able to see the E.G.O the Agent has currently equipped.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_139">Deploying Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_140">Click and hold on an Agent.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_141">Drag and drop the Agent onto the department in which you wish to deploy them.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_142">Management UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_143">PE-Box Quota</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_144">To complete the day, you must gather the specified amount of PE-Boxes. This gauge will fill each time PE-Boxes are produced after the completion of a Work Process with an Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_145">The Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_146">This gauge predicts the next upcoming Qliphoth Meltdown; it represents the passage of time through the workday’s various Qliphoth Meltdowns and Ordeals. Every time an Agent enters a Containment Unit to begin work, this gauge will increase by 1 tick. If the gauge is completely filled, a Qliphoth Meltdown will occur, or an Ordeal will manifest.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_147">Mission List</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_148">This is your list of missions that can be attempted during the workday.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_149">Speed Adjustment</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_150">These buttons can be used to pause and control the flow of time in the facility.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_151">The Work Log</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_152">This will display the history of work that has been done through the course of the day, along with casualties and panics.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_153">Department Regenerator Gauge</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_154">Whenever this gauge fills, the HP and SP of the employees in the Main Room of the department will be restored. However, this gauge will not function while an Abnormality is present in the room.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_155">Basic Controls</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_156">Camera Controls</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_157">You can use the Right Mouse Button to click and drag the camera’s position.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_158">The WASD Keys can be used to move the camera towards the corresponding positions.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_159">The camera can be zoomed in and out with the Mouse Wheel. (The F and G Keys can also be used.)</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_160">Time Controls</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_161">Slow Time: Q</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_162">Accelerate Time: E</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_163">Pause Time: SPACEBAR  </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_164">Agents can still receive orders while time is on pause, and will follow them once it resumes.    </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_165">Viewing Agent Info</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_166">You can see the relevant information of an Agent by hovering the mouse cursor over them. If you click on the Agent, the UI that displays the info will be affixed until something else is clicked on.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_167">Moving Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_168">Click on an Agent you wish to move. If you desire to move a group of Agents, click and drag to select them.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_169">With the selected Agent(s), right-click the location for them to move to.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_170">Recalling Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_171">This button will recall Agents who are not in the Main Room of the department back to it. (This function needs to be unlocked via the corresponding Control Team research.)</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_172">The Order UI  </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_173">Abnormality Risk Level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_174">The maximum number of E-Boxes that can be produced per Work with the Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_175">Different work result ranges according to PE-Box count.  </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_176">Attack type and damage range during work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_177">Department Agent List (To have employees work in departments other than their own, the corresponding Control Team research will need to be completed.)</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_178">Employee Info</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_179">The likelihood of producing PE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_180">The amount of time it will take the Agent to complete the Work Process.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_181">Orders via Left Click</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_182">Step 1: Left Click on the Containment Unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_183">Step 2: Select the Work Type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_184">Step 3: Choose an Agent</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_185">Orders via Selected Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_186">Step 1: Click and drag to select a group</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_187">Step 2: Right Click on the unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_188">Step 3: Select the Work Type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_189">Step 4: Choose from your selected group</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_190">Containment UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_191">Risk Level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_192">Qliphoth Counter</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_193">Current number of unique PE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_194">The PE-Boxes produced in the previous work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_195">Work Process Phases</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_196">As the work progresses, the Abnormality will produce a PE-Box (Positive Enkephalin Box) or a NE-Box (Negative Enkephalin Box). Only PE-Boxes can be refined and processed into energy.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_197">Your goal as the manager is to find out how to safely produce as many PE-Boxes as possible from the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_198">The manner in which we do so is quite simple:</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_199">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_200">Progressing the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_201">Ending the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_202">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_203">After receiving an order from the manager, an Agent will proceed to the designated Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_204">Each time an Agent enters a Containment Unit, the Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge will increase by 1 tick. If you need to know more about this gauge, please refer to the section about Qliphoth Meltdowns.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_205">Please make sure to keep in mind that some Abnormalities may immediately attack when an Agent enters the Containment Unit if the managerial guidelines are not complied with.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_206">Fear Damage</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_207">When an employee comes across an Abnormality, they may be struck with fear, causing some amount of mental damage.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_208">Abnormalities of higher risk levels will deal more mental damage to Agents of lower levels.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_209">This mental damage will also occur during encounters with Abnormalities that have left their Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_210">Progressing the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_211">The Success Rate</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_212">Each Abnormality will have different success rates for different Work Types. Therefore, depending on the chosen type, the outcome of the Work Process may change.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_213">The Success Rate is determined by the Virtue level corresponding to the type of work being done, along with the employee’s Success Rate stat (Temperance).</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_214">The Success Rate determines whether a PE-Box or NE-Box is produced.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_215">Success and Failure during the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_216">If there is Success…</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_217">The Abnormality will produce a PE-Box.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_218">If there is Failure…</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_219">The Abnormality will produce a NE-Box.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_220">Each time a NE-Box is produced, the Abnormality will attack the employee.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_221">If an Agent’s HP or SP hits zero during the Work Process, they will die or panic.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_222">If such an instance occurs, the Work Process will end prematurely and the remaining E-Boxes will be produced as NE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_223">Ending the Work Process</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_224">The E-Box Gauge will fill corresponding to the produced PE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_225">The final number of PE-Boxes will determine the result status of the work. There are 3 ranges of result: Bad, Normal, and Good.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_226">Produced PE-Boxes will then be stored as unique PE-Boxes for the Abnormality. Unique PE-Boxes can be used to unlock more of the Abnormality Encyclopedia and produce E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_227">The Qliphoth Counter</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_228">The Qliphoth Counter of Abnormalities may decrease if they are managed incorrectly, typically due to a Bad work result or violated managerial guideline.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_229">The Qliphoth Counter can be found on the UI of the Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_230">When the Qliphoth Counter reaches 0, the Abnormality will escape its Containment Unit or use its special abilities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_231">Please be careful as to ensure no Qliphoth Counter reaches 0.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_232">Work-Count Penalties</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_233">Qliphoth Overloads</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_234">The Success Rate of work with WAW and ALEPH Abnormalities will decrease as the count of works completed with them increases.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_235">Containment Units with Qliphoth Overloads will display the current amount of reduction in Success Rate. This reduction will also be reflected in the Order UI.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_236">Containment Units with Qliphoth Overloads will return to normal when a Qliphoth Meltdown occurs. When this Meltdown occurs, all reduced success rates will be restored to their original values.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_237">The Qliphoth Meltdown</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_238">Meltdown Level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_239">Every time a Qliphoth Meltdown occurs, this level will rise.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_240">The Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_241">Each time an Agent enters a Containment Unit, the Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge will increase by 1 tick.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_242">When the gauge is filled, a Qliphoth Meltdown will occur throughout the facility.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_243">As the Meltdown Level rises, so too does the number of affected Containment Units.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_244">Meltdown Alarms</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_245">An alarm timer will be shown on all Containment Units undergoing a Qliphoth Meltdown. This timer will gradually decrease.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_246">When this timer hits 0, the Qliphoth Counter of the Abnormality within the Containment Unit will become 0, and the unique PE-Box count will decrease.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_247">Meltdown Countermeasures</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_248">The Qliphoth Meltdown dissipates as soon as an Agent enters the Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_249">The Qliphoth Meltdown gauge will not rise when Containment Units under Meltdown are entered.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_250">However, the reduced success rate from Qliphoth Overloads will still be reflected in the work.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_251">Ordeals</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_252">At certain levels of Qliphoth Meltdowns, an Ordeal will manifest instead of Containment Unit Meltdowns occurring.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_253">‘Ordeals’ are a form of Abnormality that is unrefined. Ordeals come in four risk levels, corresponding to the times of day: Dawn, Noon, Dusk, and Midnight. As the level of Qliphoth Meltdowns increases, higher levels of Ordeals will manifest.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_254">Ordeals will hinder the management of Abnormalities in a variety of ways. However, as Ordeals are also a form of Abnormality, they can be suppressed just the same by ordering your Agents. To learn more about suppressing Ordeals and Abnormalities, please see the section ‘Suppressing Abnormalities’.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_255">Opening the Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_256">You can open the Encyclopedia window by clicking on the Containment Unit nameplate of the Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_257">The Abnormality Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_258">Abnormality Story</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_259">This section will display the story of the Abnormality. The story will be updated with each Observation Level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_260">Abnormality Information</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_261">This is the Basic Information for working with the Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_262">Managerial Guidelines</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_263">The Success Rates of each Work Type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_264">The Qliphoth Counter, and RWBP resistances if the Abnormality escapes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_265">The E.G.O that can be produced or obtained at the current Observation Level.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_266">Observation</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_267">Using your unique PE-Boxes</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_268">You can unlock more of the Encyclopedia by spending an Abnormality’s unique PE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_269">Observation Level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_270">When all the information in a category is unlocked, the Observation Level will increase.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_271">Production and Acquisition of E.G.O</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_272">E.G.O Gifts</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_273">An Agent has a low chance of acquiring an E.G.O Gift when completing the Work Process with an Abnormality after reaching a certain Observation Level. E.G.O Gifts affect an Agent’s stats.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_274">E.G.O Production</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_275">Reaching the requisite Observation Level of an Abnormality will allow the production of the Abnormality’s corresponding E.G.O. Most E.G.O production requires unique PE-Boxes.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_276">What are Tool Abnormalities?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_277">Unlike most Abnormalities, Tools are Abnormalities that emphasize a concept of “usage” instead of “management”.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_278">Tool Abnormality Classifications</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_279">1. Single Use: Agents utilize this Tool with an immediate effect.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_280">2. Equippable: Agents must equip this Tool to gain its effect.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_281">3. Channeled Use: Agents must continually use this Tool to gain its effect.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_282">Every 5 days, starting from your 4th (Day 4, Day 9, etc.), a new Tool Abnormality will be extracted.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_283">How to use Tools</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_284">1. Click the Containment Unit of the Tool Abnormality to open the Order UI, then send an Agent to use it.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_285">2. The Agent will equip or use the Tool Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_286">3. The Agent can be ordered to stop usage of a channeled use Tool or return an equippable Tool by clicking again on the Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_287">Tool Observation</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_288">The Encyclopedia of a Tool Abnormality will automatically update in accordance to the number of uses or total time used.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_289">Abnormality Escape</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_290">If the Qliphoth Counter of an Escaping Abnormality reaches 0, the Abnormality will leave its Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_291">The Qliphoth Counter can decrease not just due to a Bad work result, but also from violation of management methods.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_292">Escaping Abnormalities need to be suppressed quickly. To learn more about suppressing Abnormalities, please see the section ‘Suppressing Abnormalities’.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_293">Employee Death and Panic</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_294">Employee Death</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_295">Any employee whose HP drops to 0 due to damage from a RED, BLACK, or PALE attack will die.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_296">If an Agent dies, their equipped E.G.O will be destroyed.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_297">Employee Panic</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_298">1. Any employee whose SP drops to 0 due to damage from a WHITE or BLACK attack will panic.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_299">2. Panicking Agents can be brought back to sanity when they have recovered their SP fully from healing attacks with WHITE or BLACK E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_300">If the workday ends while an Agent is still in panic, they will be disposed of.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_301">Emergency Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_302">If an Abnormality escapes, or employees die or panic, an alarm will sound depending on the severity of the situation.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_303">First Trumpet</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_304">An Abnormality has breached and poses a minor threat to the facility and its employees.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_305">Second Trumpet</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_306">It’s not too late to improve the situation. A competent manager can handle this much. Of course, it will cost several employees.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_307">Third Trumpet</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_308">It would be a miracle if you recover from this situation. Most employees have died, and it will be nigh impossible to suppress the breaching Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_309">Suppression UI</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_310">Risk Level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_311">Attack Type</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_312">Defense Types</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_313">The defensive multipliers against attacks done to it.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_314">Using E.G.O that the Abnormality is weak to (defensive multipliers of 1.0 or more) will allow suppression to be easier.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_315">Agent Status</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_316">Your Agents’ HP, SP, and E.G.O can be checked here.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_317">Orders via Left Click</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_318">1. Click on the escaping Abnormality or its Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_319">2. Select the Agents you want to send to suppress it. Once a certain Control Team research is complete, other departments can easily aid in the suppression.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_320">3. You can cancel the suppression order of any Agent by clicking on them if they are already suppressing.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_321">Orders via Selected Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_322">1. Select the Agents who you wish to suppress by clicking (and dragging).</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_323">2. With your selected Agent(s), right-click on the escaping Abnormality.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_324">What is a Managerial Bullet?</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_325">Managerial Bullets will be unlocked by completing research in the Middle Layer’s departments.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_326">The quantity of bullets available will be influenced by the number of ticks needed to fill the Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_327">Once all bullets are expended, they will not be reloaded until a Qliphoth Meltdown has occurred. When the Qliphoth Meltdown occurs, the bullet count will be fully reloaded.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_328">Using a Bullet</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_329">1. Click on the Bullet UI or press the corresponding Number Key (1-8) to load the bullet.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_330">2. Once the bullet is loaded, the mouse cursor will change to the bullet’s corresponding crosshair.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_331">3. Aim the cursor over the target and click the mouse to fire the bullet.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_332">4. To unload the bullet, click on the Bullet UI or press the Number Key again.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_333">End of the Day</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_334">The results card will show what missions have been cleared.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_335">Increases in Virtues and levels of each Agent will be shown.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_336">Every time you end the Day, you will receive LOB in accordance to how well you did.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_337">The greater the number of Remaining Agents, the higher the rank and more LOB will be acquired.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_338">If the Day ends while an Abnormality is escaping, there will be a penalty upon the amount of LOB earned.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_339">Choosing to Proceed</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_340">After the Day is finished, you can choose whether to move on to the next Day or retry the current Day.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_341">If you choose to retry the Day, all lost Agents and E.G.O will be recovered. However, any progress toward Observations and E.G.O made that Day will be gone.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_342">The Memory Repository</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_343">The Memory Repository will be imprinted every 5 Days. (Day 1, Day 6, Day 11, and so on.)</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_344">Unlike retrying a single Day, rewinding to the Memory Repository will maintain all unlocked Observations and gained E.G.O. However, department expansion and extracted Abnormalities will regress to the state of the imprinted Day.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_345">You can elect to rewind to the Memory Repository in the ESC-Button Menu.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_346">Abnormality Extraction</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_347">Each time you advance to the next Day, you will need to choose what Abnormality to extract.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_348">Ensure you carefully read the Extraction Quote of each Abnormality before choosing.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_349">Opening and Expanding</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_350">Every time you advance to the next Day, you will need to choose what department to expand for the newly extracted Abnormality’s Containment Unit.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_351">Each time you expand a department, its Expansion Level will increase.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_352">When the Expansion Levels of all current departments reach the maximum, new departments will become available for opening.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_353">In cases where two departments can be opened at the same time, either department can be opened and expanded at your choosing without the need to maximize the Expansion Level of the other.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_354">The higher an Abnormality’s risk level, the more difficult it will be to manage.</text>
  <!--Added at 2018.01.26-->
  <text id="Manual_Text_355">Department Functions</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_356">This button will display the department’s special functions.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_357">Reminders for moving Agents</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_358">If every Agent of one department is in another department of which they do not belong, a countdown will start.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_359">For a given department, if all Agents are absent and the countdown hits zero, every Clerk in that department will panic.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_360">Clerk Benefits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_361">Clerk Benefits are applied accordingly to the current number of surviving Clerks in the departments. The benefit applied will vary for each department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_362">The effectiveness of the benefit will increase as the department expands. Higher levels will have better effects.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_363">Clerk Benefit Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_364">Level 3: 100%~80% of the department’s Clerks are alive; Expansion Level 5</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_365">Level 2: 80%~50% of the department’s Clerks are alive; Expansion Level 3+</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_366">Level 1: 50%~30% of the department’s Clerks are alive; Expansion Level 1+</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_367">As Clerks die or panic during the workday, the percentage of Clerks alive will decrease, and as a result, the Clerk Benefit Level may decrease.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_368">If the number of Clerks alive in the department reaches zero, the Clerk Benefit will be shut off for the department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_369">Continued Service Benefits</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_370">Agents gain benefits for the number of days they have been in their department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_371">Continued Service Benefits will vary for each department. Agents who have gained such a benefit are gifted with a special title and a unique signifying armband.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_372">However, if an Agent that has gained a Continued Service Benefit is transferred to another department, the effects, armband, and title will all be removed.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_373">Continued Service Benefit Levels</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_374">Level 1: 1~2 Days of Service</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_375">Level 2: 3~6 Days of Service</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_376">Level 3: 7+ Days of Service</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_377">Additionally, an even more unique armband and benefits will be granted to a single Agent in the department who has worked the longest among their peers for more than 7 days.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_378">If all Agents from a department die, the Success Rate of all Containment Units in the department will decrease by a significant degree.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_379">If all Agents die, every Clerk in that department will immediately commit suicide and the Clerk Benefit for the department will be lost.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_380">Employee Panic</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_381">3. The behaviour a panicking Agent will take is determined by the Agent’s highest Virtue. </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_382">Fortitude → Murder</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_383">Prudence → Suicide</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_384">Temperance → Wandering</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_385">Justice → Compromising Containment Units</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_386">4. The higher the level of an Agent, the more difficult it will be to bring them back to sanity. Furthermore, the damage they can cause to the facility and their coworkers will tend to be heavier.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_387">5. Please be aware that if you finish the Day with any Agents in panic, they will be immediately disposed of.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_388">Defender</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_389">Attacker</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_390">(Risk Level)</text>
</localize>