<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <!--UI-->
  <text id="Rabbit_Isolate_Prefix">Work</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Isolate_Postfix">Denied</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_SefiraSlot_Enemy">Hostile Entities</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_SefiraSlot_Select">Purification Designated</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_SefiraSlot_Agent">Agents</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_SefiraSlot_Officer">Clerks</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_SefiraSlot_LowLevel">Expansion Level Insufficient</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Info_CallbeDept">Designation Limit</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Info_Cost">Energy Cost</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Info_CostCalc">{0}% of the Facility’s current Energy.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Confirm">Authorize Call</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Title">- Rabbit Protocol Usage Manual -</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Day">1. The Rabbit Team can be called once per day.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_MaxSefira">2. The Rabbits can be called to a maximum of 4 departments at once.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_MaxCount">3. A maximum of 32 Rabbits will be called.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Cost">4. The facility must provide a percentage of its current energy in increments of 25% for each department designated.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Command">5. In whichever departments the Rabbits are called, the Rabbit Team and its captain will assume all command, not the manager.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Clear">6. The Rabbit Team will automatically withdraw when no hostile entities remain in the department.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Caution">※Caution※</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Panic">- The department to which the Rabbit Team is called will be completely sealed and blocked off; all employees currently in the department will immediately panic.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Manual_Closed">- Any employee who by chance enters the restricted area will be unable to leave.</text>
  <!--Captain-->
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Start_0">Just leave it to the Rabbits.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Start_1">The Rabbits have come to graze the grass.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Start_2">Hippity hop~ It’s time for the Rabbits to graze some fresh grass.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Start_Geburah">Cock up your ears, Rabbits. That bitch over there is the Red Mist.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Start_Binah">She isn’t actually an Arbiter, is she? If she is, please keep in mind that this goes against our contract.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Half_0">Half of the Rabbits have returned to the grasslands.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Half_1">Half of the Rabbit Team’s wiped out. Not gonna lie, the monsters in this place are a goddamn nuisance.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Half_2">Welp, that half of the Rabbits was ready to die. This amount of death is mostly seen in missions exploring the Outskirts or clearing through the Ruins.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Half_Geburah">Got half of the Rabbits eliminated. Still have some skills left in you, huh?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Half_Binah">Guess she isn’t a real Arbiter after all. But she does seem to be using some Singularities?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Almost_0">80% forever out of commission. Missions in the Outskirts would be more profitable than this.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Almost_1">80% of my Rabbit Team gone for good. Who was the madman that thought keeping these monsters in the city instead of beyond the Outskirts was a good idea?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Almost_Geburah">80% dead by her hand. She puts up a tough fight, what a monster. Though she’s still not nearly as good as she used to be.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Almost_Binah">Fairy and Key, what annoying powers… And they’re weakened too!</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Eliminated_0">All the Rabbits are wiped out. Sigh… Good luck with the rest of the situation.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Eliminated_1">The whole Rabbit Team has returned to the grasslands. This mission has failed.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Eliminated_2">They’re all dead. I’d rather take on expeditions to the Outskirts or the Ruins than be involved in this place.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Eliminated_Geburah">The Red Mist… Oh, I’ll tear you a new one with my own hands someday…</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_Eliminated_Binah">I’m sure you were aware things would go this way. We’re pulling out now.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_0">Thank you for the meal, it was satisfying.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_1">Call us again sometime, all we need is some grass.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_2">If I could, I would have participated directly myself.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_3">The mission is complete. We’ll now forget everything that has occurred here.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_Geburah">Thanks to that strange body of yours, Red Mist, your strength is much greater than before. Though your expertise seems to have rusted.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Captain_End_Binah">I never thought the day would come where we could defeat an Arbiter.</text>
  <!--Rabbit Units
      
      Rabbit_Unit_{State : one or more}_{Index}
  -->
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Name">Rabbit</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Start_0">The Rabbits have come to graze the grass.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Start_1">Commencing assignment.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Start_2">Uproot the field.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Start_3">Gnaw it all away.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Officer_0">How unlucky you must be.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Officer_1">You’re forsaken by this company.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Officer_2">Another to purify.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Agent_0">Even if you wield a fancy weapon, it will be just grass to the Rabbits.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Agent_1">You and I are fundamentally different.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Agent_2">At least your weapon seems useful.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Agent_3">Another to eliminate.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Agent_4">Seems you have some good equipment.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_TETH_0">Risk level low.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_TETH_1">Removing target immediately.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_TETH_2">This is barely a warm-up.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_HE_0">Risk level moderate.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_HE_1">Just like dealing with those kids from the Backstreets.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_HE_2">What weird monsters.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_HE_3">There are tons of creatures like this scattered around in the Ruins.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_HE_4">We could work up a bit of sweat with this one.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_WAW_0">Risk level high.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_WAW_1">It’s been a while since we fought a target as dangerous as this.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_WAW_2">Did they bring these things from the Outskirts or something?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_WAW_3">Why not use these things in the Wing Wars?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_WAW_4">God, this place is crazy.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_ALEPH_0">Maximum risk level.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_ALEPH_1">Just what the hell is this place?</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_ALEPH_2">I don’t think something like this can be handled by just us Rabbits alone.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_ALEPH_3">They’re mad to use beings from beyond the Outskirts.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Encounter_Creature_ALEPH_4">I thought these kinds of freaks were only seen in the depths of the Ruins.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Panic_0">Maximum mental corruption reached. Commencing automatic disposal.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_Panic_1">Automatic disposal to eliminate all human risk.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_SectorClear_0">Mission has been completed.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_SectorClear_1">We return now.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_SectorClear_2">There’s no more grass to eat.</text>
  <text id="Rabbit_Unit_SectorClear_3">What a rough meal.</text>
</localize>