<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="100043">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {Having someone to mourn you after you die is a blessing.}
      {Those left behind have no time to remember those who died, but prepares for the next death.}
      {$0 gazes upon #0 in silence.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {$0 dreams. The curtain is drawn on an empty faith with no exits. },
      {The huge coffin is not enough to replace the hundreds of graves.},
      {#0 watches the funeral procession of the butterflies.}
      {The burdensome fluttering wings comes closer in a familiar yet strange way.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {This place has no flowers or trees, so where are all those butterflies coming from?},
      {The employees cannot return to whence they came and have no choice but to repeat the day.},
      {The funeral procession never ends, and #0 continues to mourn.}
      {#0 thinks about the end of life.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {Returning to whence you came is a miracle that can never happen.},
      {Death in your finest hour is an unexpected blessing.},
      {In fact, most employees who died here wanted to live as long as possible.}
      {Some thought death would be a new start, but there is nothing but void after death.}
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">T-01-68</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Butterfly</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Funeral of the Dead Butterflies
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>


      <openText>What happens when people die?</openText>

    </collection>
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {What happens when people die?&#13;&#10;What happened to those who worked here?}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {- They must returned to their home, where family and warmness await.&#13;&#10;But everyone knows that the employees can’t leave the company unless they retire.&#13;&#10;-  Then they must have "retired" and returned to their homes, having earned what they wanted and full of hope.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {We are feathers of the Wing. But retiring isn't as easy as it sounds. Just like how feathers do not fall out on their own free will.&#13;&#10;- Then where did the retired employees go?&#13;&#10;They are bound to the company the moment they enter. They cannot leave even if they retire.&#13;&#10;-Long ago, in some world, people believed that they become beautiful beings with small wings when they die. What nonsense.&#13;&#10;If we have wings, can we leave here? Do we get wings after we retire?}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {The mourner with the colossal baggage on his back is said to have come here to be the savior of all.&#13;&#10;But now he is trapped like everyone else, roaming the company with only the memory of empty faith.&#13;&#10;The baggage he carries is a coffin. A large coffin to pay tribute to the employees who have nowhere else to go. But it is too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.&#13;&#10;Inside it are butterflies waiting for the time to sleep. Until then, they flutter their wings uselessly.&#13;&#10;Butterflies are supposed to pollinate flowers, but not a single flower blooms in this place.&#13;&#10;They have no choice but to wait. After all, there must be an end to the world.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="3">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">#0, an employee whose Justice is below level 3 completed the work, lowering the Qliphoth counter.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">Other employees whose Fortitude exceeds level 3 experienced the same.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="3">When the work result was bad, Qliphoth counter has decreased with a high probability.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>

  </observe>
</creature>