<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
              
    <feeling max="100" downProb="0.44" downValue="1">
      <section feelingValue="50" state="good" energy="0.5"/>
      <section feelingValue="30" state="normal" energy="0.3"/>
      <section feelingValue="0" state="bad" energy="-1.3"/>
    </feeling>

  -->
  <info id ="100103">


    <narration action="move">
      #0 designated to $0 containment room.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {#0 doesn't remember anything positive such as the sparkle of love or joy of good deeds but only reacts to things that are dying.},
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {#0's heart has been impaled by the Magical Bullet, which always hits its mark, long ago.},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {Like all pacts with the devil, #0's job won’t end peacefully.},
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="3">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">F-01-69</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="0">Sprites/Unit/creature/Freischutz</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Der Freischütz
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>

      <specialName openLevel ="3">
        
      </specialName>

      <openText>This magical bullet truly can hit anyone you say!</openText>
     
    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {The devil ultimately wanted despair.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Despair wears the mind down, making one lose the will to go forward. The moment one feels there is nothing left to go forward for, the soul dies and falls down to hell, the domain of the devil. This is why the devil enjoys watching people in despair rather than concentrating on simple work like murder. This is what we call "Having your soul sold to devil."}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {When a hunter received a gun from the devil, the devil proposed a childish contract that the last bullet would puncture the head of his beloved. The moment he heard that, he found and shot everyone he loved. Then he told the devil, "This magical bullet truly can hit anyone you say!"&#13;&#10;Having his last bullet vanish, the hunter traveled to numerous worlds. Sometimes he helped those in need or fought evil, but it was all the result of an impulse, not his goodwill. Some called him a hunter of justice, while others called him the bloody marksman.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {One day, the hunter realized the devil no longer lingered over him. He wondered why, but realized his soul had already fallen to hell. The contract had already been completed, so the devil was gone.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {The marksman, now a devil, continued to pull the trigger to gather the souls of others. Just like how the devil worked, the bullets will puncture anything you please. Forever.}
      ]
    </desc>
    


    <specialTipSize size="6">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">You can proceed with the request for $0. At the time of the request, 10% of the current energy is consumed.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">However, bullets that are fired after commissioning can penetrate all objects and cause damage. Also, The 7th bullet of $0 can't fire where you want it to, so you have to decide carefully.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">#0, an employee whose Justice is below level 3 completed the $0 work, lowering the Qliphoth counter of $0.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="3">When the work result was normal, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a normal probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="4">When the work result was bad, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a high probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="5">When Qliphoth counter reaches 0,$0 will fire a bullet by himself toward somewhere inside this facility.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>