<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id="100059">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {$0’s containment chamber is bright as if there’s an incandescent source of light.},

      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {Petals shall fall like scream when everything’s over.},

      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {When the beauty is at its peak, the ritual of end comes.},
      ]
    </narration>


    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {Everyone who looks at it in this sunless place feels pure peace.},
      ]
    </narration>



  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-04-100</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Sakura</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Grave of Cherry Blossoms
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        TETH
      </riskLevel>


      <openText>The more blood it has, the more beautiful it is. </openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {A tree standing in the middle of the containment chamber. It never withers even if it is not given any nutrient.&#13;&#10;Some employees take rest next to this tree.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Pansy: Did you see that new abnormality? I think you’re in charge of it.&#13;&#10;Xavier: Yeah, I saw it. It was just a tree with some buds along the branches. I don’t think they’re going to blossom without sunlight. &#13;&#10;Pansy: Did you start the observation yet? &#13;&#10;Xavier: Nah, I think I’ll get to it now.&#13;&#10;Pansy: Okay, take care.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Pansy: Hey, long time no see. How’s it going?&#13;&#10;Xavier: Hey, listen, that abnormality we talked about before, I don’t think it’s hostile to us. And its buds started blooming. It was strange looking at them. It felt like spring has come for the first time in this place.&#13;&#10;Pansy: Is that okay? Usually any kind of change is a bad omen of something catastrophic here.&#13;&#10;Xavier: It’s just some flowers. But thank you for worrying about me.}
      ]
    </desc>


    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Pansy: Hey again! How’s the work going?&#13;&#10;Xavier: The flowers keep blooming. I think it’s going to fill the whole containment chamber. Why don’t you come and see? It’s really beautiful. I will never get tired of it.&#13;&#10;Pansy: I’d love to, but I can’t. I’m busy lately. &#13;&#10;Xavier: Really? What a shame… It’s magnificent to look at.&#13;&#10;Pansy: Hmm…are you okay? You’ve been making a lot of mistakes these days. I’ve been also seeing you spacing out a lot. &#13;&#10;Xavier: It’s nothing. I gotta go back. I’ve been making a sketch of the tree. I’ll show you first when it’s complete. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Sound recording of the counseling session&#13;&#10;…Yes, I’ve been better. I’ve gotten better at managing abnormalities, too. I went to abnormality $0’s chamber as you said, and it made me feel weirdly amazing. I never believed about floras giving out good aura thing…but I guess it was true.&#13;&#10;But it’s a shame that I can’t see those cherry blossoms with Xavier. I saw his sketch while I was rummaging through his stuff.&#13;&#10;The actual tree was much more beautiful. It was more magnificent than how he told me about it. It’s such a tragedy that he went missing before seeing that view. If you find any abnormality suspicious, please thoroughly investigate them.&#13;&#10;… Yes, I’m fine now. I shook of the feeling.&#13;&#10;The cherry blossoms all fell after I saw.&#13;&#10;But I saw the buds coming up again last time I saw it.&#13;&#10;… Then may I oversee this abnormality?&#13;&#10;No, it’s not a big deal. I just want to see those flowers in full bloom again.&#13;&#10;Yes, thank you.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="6" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Notice&#13;&#10;We’ve been reported about an alarming increase of employees who wants to see $0.&#13;&#10;This fever is likely caused due to the absence of natural scenery in this facility. &#13;&#10;However, I don’t think we need to make a rule against it. We’ve found out that employees’ mental contamination index is decreased by looking at $0.&#13;&#10;The reason behind this is not important. It can be “floras giving out good aura” for all I care.&#13;&#10;What’s sure is that $0 captivates employees, and they don’t know what’s beneath its roots.&#13;&#10;Did you realize that its cherry blossoms are strikingly crimson, and its unmatched beauty caused by its color?&#13;&#10;The more blood it has, the more beautiful it is. Employees, who are oblivious of it, are drawn towards it again and again…&#13;&#10;Just hush hush for now. It’s how things work in this place.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">When the work result was good, Qliphoth counter has decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">When employee #0 panics in the containment room, Qliphoth counter will be reduced</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="3">When Qliphoth Counter reached 0, some random employees in the facility moved to $0’s containment unit. (This status is designated as “Captivated”.)</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="4">when a captivated employee reached the containment chamber, they were sucked into the tree. </specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="5">After continuously attempting to converse with an employee who had been enchanted by $0, the employee seemed to return to normal again. When employees were no longer captivated, Qliphoth Counter was restored to the maximum.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="6">After sucking an employee in, when another employee commenced a work on the abnormality, its Qliphoth Counter was restored to the maximum. Also, physical and mental health of every employee in the facility was healed.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>


  </observe>



</creature>