<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id ="100034">



    <narration action="move">
      #0 designated to $0 containment room.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {Employee #0 starts to feel that hair is just a burden.},
      {Employee #0 starts to think that tattoo on bald head would look really cool.}
      {Employee #0 starts taking off his/her wig because he/she feels proud of partial balding.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {You can look like Bruce Willis if you are bald!},
      {Bald people oddly look professional even if they are just doing trivial things!}
      {Bald people don’t have to worry about clogged drain!}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {And still you have your silky hair?},
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">Bald-is-awesome!</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Bald</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        You’re Bald…
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        ZAYIN
      </riskLevel>

      <specialName openLevel ="2">
        KEEP CALM AND GO BALD
      </specialName>

      <openText>You turned on your electric hair clipper..</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      { Warning: You have taken baldy-bald mental damage. If this article is read by non-bald individual, they will have privilege of getting bald. If you want to stop this from happening, you must be assigned to work on this abnormality. If you find more than 10 strands of hair on the pillow in the morning, it is recommended to read this article 3 or more times. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Bill: I had an amazing dream today. &#13;&#10;
      XX : What kind of dream? Did you win a lottery or something?&#13;&#10;
      Bill : Everyone here was bald! James, you, and everyone else in this facility! And maybe everyone outside of this facility! &#13;&#10;
      XX : Uh……I think you’ve been stressed a lot recently. Why don’t you take counseling? &#13;&#10;
      Employee Bill was sacrificed to The Singing Machine that day. Many employees mourned for him. Right after the incident, abnormality Bald-Is-Awesome! has appeared. We all cherish memories of Bald Bill.
      }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="3">
      [
      {If a person is contacted by this abnormality, for 1 hour, they talk or write about how being bald is good, and eventually, they make themselves bald. If you’re bald, you can save time because you don’t have to wash and dry your hair anymore. If a bald employee is assigned to this abnormality, it will not show any reaction. You don’t have to worry about balding if you are bald. On the other hand, if a hairy employee is assigned to this abnormality, they will start shaving their own hair. Bald people can reflect light on their smooth head and blind opponents, isn’t it amazing?! This abnormality’s final goal is to make every single human being on this earth bald. You don’t need light bulbs if there are a lot of bald people because lights reflect on their heads; you can save electricity bill! If hairy employees are not assigned to this abnormality regularly, its mood status will decrease. Do you know that nobles in middle age Europe were all bald? They changed their wig every day!  }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="4">
      [
      {And we added some new rules to the company code of behavior.&#13;&#10; EmployeesF**kers who mock their co-workers for being bald will be permanently banned from using lounge, and joining company debate club “Why don’t bald Barbies exist?”, Gourmet club “Lovely Octopus”, and environmental movement club “We are worried about decreasing number of Bald Eagle”. The ban will be lifted if the employee’s number of hair strand goes below 1. &#13;&#10; In memory of employee T.H, who is taking anti-balding medicine next to me right now. }
    ]
  </desc>


    <specialTipSize size="3">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="memeriBeam">You've got a Bald-is-awesome!Beam, because your hair is still silky.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="memeriOnly">Unless employees with the Bald-is-awesome!beam are working on the $0, all of the other employees' hair will fall out and become bald this month.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="memeriHurryUp">It's not too late. 30... 29... 28...</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>

    <max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {This abnormality is filled with dreams of bald people.}
        {Are you balding, or already bald?}
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="Yes" target="1" isAnswer="true"  message="You're BALD"/>
        <node desc="No" target="2" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>

      <desc id="1" select="0">
        [
        {Lobotomy welcomes you.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="2" select="2">
        [
        {Then do you wish to be bald?}
        ]
      </desc>

      <select id="2">
        <node desc="Yes" target="3" isAnswer="true" message="You're BALD"/>
        <node desc="No" target="4" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>

      <desc id="3" select="0">
        [
        {You turned on your electric hair clipper.}
        {Lobotomy welcomes you.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="4" select="0">
        [
        {Come back after watching 'Quick and Enraged 7' for more than five times. }
        ]
      </desc>



      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {Oh, when did you shaved your hair, manager?}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>

  </observe>
</creature>