<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
              
    <feeling max="100" downProb="0.44" downValue="1">
      <section feelingValue="50" state="good" energy="0.5"/>
      <section feelingValue="30" state="normal" energy="0.3"/>
      <section feelingValue="0" state="bad" energy="-1.3"/>
    </feeling>

  -->
  <info id ="100054" >


    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {$0 looks at #0 with its mysteriously luminous body protruding out.},
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {There hasn’t been a single employee who has seen the complete form of $0.},
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {If $0 escapes from the Containment Facility completely, our corporation may collapse.},
      ]
    </narration>



  </info>

  <observe level ="5">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-04-84</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Bunny</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Meat Lantern
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        TETH
      </riskLevel>


      <openText>That’s not a flower, order all the employees to get away immediately.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {It always stuck under the floor of the Containment Unit, only showing its eyes and mysterious luminous body above the ground. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      { Nobody knows what it actually looks like. It moves underground, not through the hallway, making it is impossible to predict its path when escaping. For the same reason, its escape won’t be detected. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {&lt;Voice Record&gt;Lloyd: Are you located nearby the Information Team? I've heard some employees went missing around that area. Would you mind checking to see if there's any Abnormality that's performing spatial interference?&#13;&#10;Paul: What? But there's no Abnormality with that ability near here. I haven't detected any escaped Abnormality neither.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Paul: Well, Lloyd, there's no sign of any Abnormality, but I do see a small flower on the ground. &#13;&#10;Lloyd: What are you talking about? What flower?&#13;&#10;Paul: The bud is glowing, it’s amazing. It's strange finding something so green here, when we don’t get sunlight here... It's so bright that some of the other employees came to look at the flower. You need to come and see it... The light is so bright and warm... I feel like something good is about to happen...&#13;&#10;Lloyd: That’s not a flower, order all the employees to get away immediately. Do not run away in a group, you have to slowly escape one by one with quiet steps...&#13;&#10;Paul: What are you talking about, I thought I told you that there's nothing nearby... Wait, I think I just felt a slight trembling underneath my feet. Is someone fixing the pipes today?&#13;&#10;Lloyd: Damn, you’re screwed. Just enjoy the flower...}
      ]
    </desc>



    <specialTipSize size="3">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">When the work result was bad, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">When the work time was under 40 seconds, its Qliphoth Counter is decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="3">When the Abnormality escapes, all employees and the facility won’t be able to detect the Abnormality, therefore the Manager needs to order suppression directly.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>


  </observe>



</creature>