<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id="100056">


    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {Employee #0 is (CENSORED) to (CENSORED).}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {Employee #0 is feeling (CENSORED) from (CENSORED). }
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {(CENSORED) doing (CENSORED) is... Oh my god, that’s disgusting.}
      ]
    </narration>


  </info>

  <observe level="4">
    <!--level은 관찰 최대 레벨-->
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-03-89</codeNo>
      <name openLevel="1">CENSORED</name>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/Censored</portrait>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">ALEPH</riskLevel>



      <openText>If any system issue deletes the blur from the Abnormality, we will have to sincerely think of how to deal with the manager.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Any recorded attempts about (CENSORED) will cause severe mental corruption to both speaker and listener. Therefore, any record about the appearance of (CENSORED) will not be tolerated. Any and all voice and written records containing descriptions will have specific parts deleted. And all of the work pertaining to this must be given to Level 5 or above employees.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Randy: I feel sorry for sending such a competent employee like you to the containment unit. Do you have any last words before proceeding? Of course, when I say last words, it's just precautionary.&#13;&#10;(CENSORED): Well, there's no other choice. I have the highest resistance level against the recognition decay. I have been apathetic towards everything ever since I was young. I was often told that I lack empathy and I wasn't normal. But when I joined here, my abnormal ability became the key to save everyone. This is something you can never experience anywhere else.&#13;&#10;Randy: I am telling you this again. Yes, you have the highest resistance level against the recognition decay, but that’s only for the human standard. If you suffer from uncontrollable thoughts, or decided to count down from 10 but have forgotten what 10 even is, or you start to puke or drool uncontrollably, or you believe that you are somewhere else and not in the company, or that you suddenly feel insignificant and think that not breathing is your only hope, then you must leave the containment unit immediately.&#13;&#10;(CENSORED): If you tell me that one more time, that'll make it 13, Randy.&#13;&#10;Randy: We won't be monitoring you in real-time. All the cameras will be turned off and your voice record will be updated after the work is finished. Needless to say, I'm worried about you. OK, please repeat everything I just told you.&#13;&#10;(CENSORED): Go inside, don’t work, and just observe the task of (CENSORED) who will be accompanying me inside. It's there where I will record everything that happens. Even if (CENSORED) is in danger, resist the urge to rescue unless ordered otherwise. Right?&#13;&#10;Ramdu : Correct. Now, I will count to 10 and you will be disconnected. Good luck and Godspeed to you.&#13;&#10;(CENSORED): I have no regrets. I consider myself very lucky compared to the others because I get to leave my "last" voice record. Well, I mean "last" only as a precaution but...&#13;&#10;Randy: All right, your record will be eternally archived and all your fellow employees will remember you. 3.. 2....1.... End of recording.&#13;&#10;(CENSORED): (omit) Randy.. that looks, just like our (CENSORED) from long time ago... I... forgot I'm the only one who can see this. (CENSORED) and (CENSORED) seem...they are able to breed... (CENSORED) who was with me became (CENSORED)... It seems to be a process of (CENSORED).... I feel a little sick, but I'm good... (CENSORED) just came out from (CENSORED)'s (CENSORED).... (CENSORED) just started to scream like (CENSORED).... the cries... can you hear them? It reminds me of (CENSORED)...&#13;&#10;Sound: (CENSORED) ----------------------------------------------------&#13;&#10;Now I get it... That is our (CENSORED), that’s why (CENSORED) exists...&#13;&#10;This is the worst than all the other scenes that I have seen. I can't move, it seems (CENSORED) has made me its next target. It’s coming towards me. I will put the recorder in my (CENSORED)... I hope this record will help everyone...&#13;&#10;}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Even after we adopted a recognition filter, many managers lost their minds. Half of the reasons were due to (CENSORED). Even if we raise the recognition filter to the highest level at the risk of having the employees or other Abnormalities be perceived as extremely simple, the managers will still become insane as soon as this Abnormality comes into sight. We can't blind the manager just because of one Abnormality. We are in a dilemma. The only solution we could come up with was a suggestion of an employee. It was to cover the Abnormality with a giant blur. If any system issue deletes the blur from the Abnormality, we will have to sincerely think of how to deal with the manager.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">Qliphoth Counter of the corresponding Abnormality can be increased by 1 through selection work. To satisfy the Abnormality, an employee must be selected from the drawing.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">employee level 4 or below immediately panicked when they encountered the Abnormality. When $0 escaped, the employees of that level did the same.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">When employee #0 panics in the containment room, Qliphoth counter will be reduced.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="4">When the work result was bad, Qliphoth counter has decreased.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>


  </observe>



</creature>
