<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="100015">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 designated to $0 containment room.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {Repented employee #0 enters the room, following the divine light.}
      {“What maketh thee hesitate? I am working miracles here.”}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {$0 looks like a fetus, but it doesn’t seem like he needs care. }
      {When the bell rang for twelve times, the facility was swallowed by blinding light. It was a light of redemption for his disciples.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {Only silence fills the air around $0}
      {$0 absorbs every sound and light around him.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {$0 came here to redeem you and lead the new world.}
      {$0 came from the end of the world. And he walks towards the beginning of the new world.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {#0, why art thou in fear? I shalt not leave you until I complete my mission.}
      {#0, do not be frightened. I am your savior and I will be with you.}
      {I heard your cry. Your heart reached me. #0, thou have called me.}
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level="5">
    <!--level은 관찰 최대 레벨-->
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">T-03-46</codeNo>
      <name openLevel="1">WhiteNight</name>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/DeathAngel</portrait>
      <riskLevel openLevel ="2">ALEPH</riskLevel>
      <openText>"Rise, my servants. Rise and serve me."</openText>
    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {The abnormality resembles new born baby. Though he looks rather grotesque to be called as a normal baby. Communication is possible, not in a normal way. Every word he says echoes through the whole room.  }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {My disciples, who I blessed, shalt leave the way of evil that once thou wert following and find me. When the time comes, I shalt forgive your sins and descend to the earth thou art living on.} <!-- 폰트!!! 바꿔야돼!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!-->
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Employees who were treated by him, 12 people will walk around the room to deliver redemption to every single employee in the facility. Wings will sprout from their back, they will wear a beak mask and carry a cross that forgives all sins on their back.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Follow my teachings as I told thee. Thou wilt abandon flesh and be born again.} <!-- 폰트!!! 바꿔야돼!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!-->
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="3">
      [
      {His disciples will be born again as a missionary, evangelizing to those who would help others. They…}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="6" openLevel="4">
      [
      {The time has come. The bell will ring. The new world will come. Rise, my servants. Rise and serve me. I am death and life. Darkness and light.}
      ]
    </desc>

   

  <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="1">If Qliphoth Counter reaches 0, $0 and his disciples will advent again.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="2">&lt;Caution&gt; $0, unlike other abnormalities, periodically decreases Qliphoth Counter. It is recommended to frequently visit $0 and check its status.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="3">When the work result was good, Qliphoth Counter increased. Also, physical and mental health of every employee in the facility was healed.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="4">When the work result was moderate, Qliphoth Counter increased by a moderate chance.Also, the physical and mental health of the employees that are stationed in the department where $0 is contained was healed.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="5">When the work result was bad, Qlihpoth Counter decreased. Also, every employee in the department where $0 is contained took White damage.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>

  
  </observe>

  <etc>
    <!--UI막는 이벤트 때 띄울 대사-->
    <param key="escape" index="0">
      Do not fear, for I am with you. You cannot leave until I allow you to.
    </param>
    <param key="time" index="1">
      Do not trust the time, for I will guide you.
    </param>
    <param key="manual0" index="2">
      Do not deny me, for I am in front of your eyes.
    </param>
    <param key="manual1" index="3">
      My story is nowhere, unknown.
    </param>
  </etc>
</creature>