<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="100017">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 designated to $0 containment room.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {$0 doesn’t even have organs formed properly.},
      {$0 sucks its own thumb and cries from time to time.	},
      {There is a long scar-looking line on abdomen of $0.},
      {If you hear the baby crying, it means one of us is going to be disappeared. }
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {Unlike other babies, $0 doesn’t wine or look for mother .},
      {Covered by unidentified slime, $0 is not like other babies which are wrapped up in warm blanket, happily dreaming. },
      {Around $0, unidentifiable objects resembling umbilical cord are messily scattered. It is a “baby’s room” but no crying is heard. Only silence.},
      {#0 just have entered the chamber but $0 is unresponsive not like other babies.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {Big, pitch-black pupils are staring at nowhere. They don’t even blink.},
      {The only thing $0 resembles other babies is that it sucks its body part which is assumed to be a thumb as if it is hungry, showing off its dismal desire.},
      {Once in a while, $0 ‘babbles’ just like any other babies. But all the employees know that this is not just a ‘babble’.}
      {$0 often makes sound just like other babies babbling. No need to worry yet because the desire is not overloading.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {While working, employee #0 makes rhythmical sound to $0 as if he/she is taking care of a baby.},
      {#0 stops the work and approaches to $0, barely making smile as it minds the employee.}
      {#0 looks back to check on $0. Luckily, $0 endures $0's work without crying.}
      {Worried about the $0, #0 checks repeatedly throughout the work. We all know what the employee is worried about.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {$0 opens its mouth and lick its lips. Pitch-black pupils secretly show its instinct desire.},
      {$0 closes its eyes. Surely it is not the act of deprivation of sleep. $0 wants only one thing.}
      {All the sudden, $0 turns its head and gazes at #0 who has almost finished the work. No ill-intention in its eyesight whatsoever, but it is surely not that of eyesight which is staring at ‘human’.}
      {$0 feels the starvation and all of a sudden, stares at #0. $0 ‘s pure evil penetrates the object.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="special_ability1">
      [
      {Endless cry of $0 fills the entire facility. #0 who is nearby the containment chamber starts to sense him/herself going insane.}
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="5">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-01-15</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/NamelessFetus</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Nameless Fetus
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>

      <specialName openLevel ="2">
        Where's mommy?
      </specialName>

      <openText>“One day, maybe you will know. The meaning of desperation in their faces when the roulette spins.”</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {The creature takes the shape of an unborn fetus. Its skin is covered with a sticky slime-like liquid and many little visible veins. The creature’s abnormally bulged eyes are usually closed. The creature always seems unsatisfied but exactly what its needs are is undetermined. It has a great obsession to being ‘fed’ and if it is not ‘fed’ regularly, its stress levels rise drastically. When it reaches a certain level of stress, it cries out loudly with a cry that mentally harms all who may be around the creature.  }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Excerpt from Interview Log #2-49#2-49 &#13;&#10;Employee F2706 : “I've never seen its smile. It always seems to want something, but we can't ever fulfill its desire. I guess the reason why its crying is destructive is because its unsatisfied needs are so strong. When I was new here, none of my colleagues would tell me exactly what the ‘feed’ was. I thought it was milk or something else that little babies consume. It is a baby after all, even with all that grossness. But that was not the case. It only eats human flesh. Can you believe it? To stop it from crying, we have to hold a draw every once in a while. Do you know what that means?"}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Observation Log 1-431 &#13;&#10;When I first heard that the ‘Nameless Fetus needed to be fed, I thought we need to feed it like with a spoon. It looked too weak to do anything and its mouth wasn’t fully developed. And when I found out that the creature eats meat, I thought it would need to be first chewed by someone so it would become soft. When I asked my colleague about that, he laughed and said ‘no that's ridiculous, we just need to leave the food and go.’ But I still wondered how that creature can eat stuff. Do we serve it the succulent kind of steak that isn’t even available for us in the cafeteria? Out of curiosity, I decided to sneak a peek of the feeding process. Only level 3 or higher employees are assigned to that process, but I was able to attend with a fake excuse that I was covering for someone. And I watched nervously. Would my lie be worth it? Some people came along with some large plastic bags. Does it eat that much? And when they opened the bags, I could only gape in horror. They were human corpses. And the child ate it. How? I don't want even want to imagine it. It had a large scar on its stomach; I really thought it was a kind of scar. Like a large flower, its stomach would open, dripping with slimy liquid. It was the greediest creature in the world. That night, I became a vegetarian. }
      ]
    </desc>


    <desc id="4" openLevel="4">
      [
      {I am Pauly. I started working for Lobotomy since two days ago. My parents are very proud of me for entering such a big company. My friends are envious of me. I’m making a lot of trouble right now. But someday, I will be as capable as my co-workers.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {There is special event in our company held only for the employees. No one knows when or why this event is being held. Even my colleague who worked for 5 years doesn’t seem to know. When this event starts, a giant roulette spins. Then, everyone stops what they were doing and stare at the roulette to see who is going to be selected. The names of every single employee are written on the said roulette. Nobody knows who will be selected. Whoever that might be, they are extremely lucky. Their family will be gifted with unimaginable fortune. They promote and transfer to another branch of the company. It’s called “Central headquarter”. In central headquarter, you don’t have to worry about being attacked by monsters, or bid farewell to your dead co-workers. My boss, &lt;REDACTED&gt; desperately hopes he is the lucky one. His father got into accident. It takes a lot of money to keep him alive and well. I sincerely hope the roulette to choose &lt;REDACTED&gt;.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="6" openLevel="4">
      [
      {When the roulette chooses &lt;REDACTED&gt;’s name, I congratulated him with all my heart. But he didn’t look so happy. People hugged &lt;REDACTED&gt; one by one. While crying, for some reason. He said goodbye to me, struggling to keep his tears from shedding and with a forced smile. I haven’t seen him since. I believe he is working under much better condition and payment. But when I try to have a conversation about him, people just stop talking and shake head. As if I said something I shouldn’t. I can’t forget what he said to me before he left. &#13;&#10; “One day, maybe you will know.” &#13;&#10;“The meaning of desperation in their faces when the roulette spins.”}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="7" openLevel="4">
      [
      {The manager has right to hold a special event for employees without specific occasion. When the event starts, a giant roulette spins and selects one of the employee’s name. Selected employee promotes, be transferred to other branch (See below for detailed information) and their family will receive yearly pension. No personnel are allowed to invade the manager’s right to hold the event. Following is information strictly forbidden to public eye.	&#13;&#10; Required condition to hold the event. &#13;&#10; - Data closed &#13;&#10; -	Data closed &#13;&#10; -	When the crying of Nameless Fetus is at its peak.  &#13;&#10; 	The roulette selects an employee that satisfies one of the conditions below. &#13;&#10; 1.	One who questions the purpose of the company.  &#13;&#10; 2.	One who conducted or planned unauthorized experiment on abnormalities.  &#13;&#10; 3.	One who has excessive curiosity about abnormalities and conducted or planned the unauthorized observation. &#13;&#10; 4.	One who became incapable of working due to physical or psychological damage. &#13;&#10; * “Unauthorized” means “Unauthorized by the company or Angela”.&#13;&#10; -	Following actions are taken on the selected employee.  &#13;&#10; 1.	Removal of the records that company has about the employee.  &#13;&#10; 2. Sacrificial ceremony of the employee to the abnormality. &#13;&#10; 3.	Informing the employee’s family that he or she has been transferred to another branch.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="teeth">When the work result was normal, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a low probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="cry">When the work result was bad, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a high probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="cryEffect">When $0's Qliphoth counter reaches zero, $0 burst into tears. Employees who heard its cry complained of a headache. Also, the Qliphoth counter of Abnormality that heard the crying gradually decreased over time.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="sacrifice">When $0 was crying, only &lt;Redacted&gt; work could be done.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="sacrifice">Employee #0 was selected for roulette for &lt;Redacted&gt; work. The He quietly walked into $0’s containment room. It stopped crying after a moment of turmoil.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
    
    <max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {The baby never cries.}
        {It kept that way forever. }
        {As lack of words doesn’t necessarily means lack of emotions,}
        {Lack of crying doesn’t mean lack of desire.}
        {Since unknown time, the baby has mouth.}
        {Instead of the baby who does not know how, it cries, expresses hunger, and causes pain for the others.}
        {You……}
        <!--계속-->
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="Called the name." target="1" isAnswer="true" message="You have succeeded to obtain final observation report on Nameless Fetus."/>
        <node desc="Didn’t call the name." target="2" isAnswer="fasle"/>
      </select>

      <desc id="1" select="0">
        [
        {No one else knows the name of fetus.}
        {But you know.}
        {You called its name.}
        {The unstoppable desire shut its mouth for a while.}
        {Even only for a short time, the desire silenced.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="2" select="0">
        [
        {The fetus is still crying.}
        {You plugged your ears silently.}
        {No sound is heard.}
        ]
      </desc>
      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {Calling its name is such a cheap price,}
        {In comparison that we had to sacrifice a life of employee in order to silence it.}
        {I think I have made an excellent choice of selecting you as the manager.}
        {..}
        {The meaning of name is important, is it not?}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>

  </observe>



</creature>