<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
              
    <feeling max="100" downProb="0.44" downValue="1">
      <section feelingValue="50" state="good" energy="0.5"/>
      <section feelingValue="30" state="normal" energy="0.3"/>
      <section feelingValue="0" state="bad" energy="-1.3"/>
    </feeling>

  -->
  <info id ="100023">


    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {"Mirror, mirror on the wall, who’s the fairest of them all?" The witch asked in a room no one would visit anymore.},
      {The mirror kept silent, but the witch heard the answer.},
      {When the day a ripe apple fell off the tree in the garden where the princess and the king stood, the witch's heart was shattered.},
      {The witch cast the most powerful spell she knew on the apple, sacrificing herself.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {#0 can see the branches covering the containment unit.},
      {$0's containment unit has some leaves and branches growing inside it.},
      {When you approach $0's containment unit, you will see the branches intertwining it.},
      {Faint sounds of rustling leaves can be heard from $0's containment unit.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {If you look closely, you can see that the branches are withered.},
      {They are dried to crisp that a single touch would reduce them to dust. They look too horrible to be called plants.},
      {Although withered, those branches and leaves are still growing.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {$0's eyes are long gone - Birds and bugs feasted on them in the past. $0 grew by consuming the carcasses nearby.},
      {$0 was by itself for a long time. Around $0, the remains of the bugs and birds that died after eating $0 are scattered about.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {$0 thought of the princess and the prince who walked down a path of flowers amidst everyone’s blessings.},
      {$0 was cursed by the witch, and the princess who collapsed because of $0 lived happily ever after. }
      {$0 grew in jealousy, wrath, and loneliness.}
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">F-04-42</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/SnowWhite</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Snow White's Apple
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>


      <openText>When the day a ripe apple fell off the tree in the garden where the princess and the king stood, the witch's heart was shattered.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {When the prince kissed the princess, she coughed up the apple bits stuck inside her throat. The dwarves cried out in happiness. Snow White and the prince walked through a path covered in flowers and headed to their kingdom. And everyone lived happily ever after.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {And there was an apple created from a witch’s wrath and curse. It was a part of herself. The apple that dropped from Snow White's hand after a single bite can never be happy. The apple, full of hatred toward the princess and feeling lonely, waited for the day when it would return to the earth.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {We don’t know if it’s the enchantment or the wrath that is bending the laws of nature. Even after plenty of time has passed for it to rot and allow its seed to bear fruit, the apple did not rot. Half of it is crushed and the other half has bug holes.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {The carcasses of birds and bugs piled up near the apple. The apple pondered about its existence in the midst of the dead. And one day, a branch grew from it. The leaves and branches were already dead, but it continued to grow.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Finally, one afternoon when the apple gained the power of mobility, it thought of the princess and the prince who were happy. Snow White had been sleeping for a long time, but a prince came and woke her up. The apple, now a princess in its own right, began her journey to find her own prince. &#13;&#10; - Excerpt from The Hidden Stories in Fairy Tales (Author Unknown)}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="Escape">When the work result was normal, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a normal probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="Escape2">When the work result was bad, $0's Qliphoth counter has decreased with a high probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="Making">After escaping from the containment unit, $0 has spread its roots in the ground, shooting up branches inside the corridor. The branches of $0 slowed down the employees, hampering their movement. </specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="NotDisappear">After the corridor was filled with branches, $0 moved on to another corridor to make more branches. &#13;&#10;$0 has been suppressed and returned to normal, but $0's branches covering the corridor didn’t disappear until the next day.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>


  </observe>



</creature>