<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="100040">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {Employee #0 can feel spores spewing out from $0.}
      {Employee #0 is feeling hazy because of $0.}
      {$0 looks revolting, yet enchanting.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {The fox said, “You know, the most important thing cannot be seen.”}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {$0 came from afar, somewhere we don’t know.}
      {Perhaps $0 is not what we are seeing with our eyes.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {The ends of employees who were tamed by $0 were always tragic.}
      {Employees that turned into monsters by $0 wander $0’s containment room.}
      {Many employees who finished working on $0 complain that they can’t eat mushroom anymore.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {Many employees who finished working on $0 complain that they can’t eat mushroom anymore.}
      {Employee #0 remembers a piece of star.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="special_ability_1">
      [
      {Dozens of tumors start growing on #0’s body. They cannot be stopped… #0’s mind is desperately yearning for consensus with $0. }
      {Employee #0 loses mind, with $0’s star kept in the body.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="special_ability_2">
      [
      {The price for searching something more than what we are, was big.}
      {Employee #0 hears the friend’s voice in fading consciousness.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <narration action="special_ability_3">
      [
      {Employee #0 saw stars in dreams. The longing for $0 is deepening…}
      {Employee #0 couldn’t belong to $0’s world. The tragic end of exiled employee #0 begins.}

      ]
    </narration>


  </info>

  <observe level="4">
    <!--level은 관찰 최대 레벨-->
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-04-66</codeNo>
      <name openLevel="1">Giant Mushroom</name>
      <name openLevel="4">The Little Prince</name>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/YoungPrince</portrait>
      
      <riskLevel openLevel ="2">WAW</riskLevel>

      <openText>
        Even if this is my curse, I will love this curse as a blessing.
      </openText>

   
    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {It’s called “Giant Mushroom” among the employees. As the nickname goes, it resembles a sizable mushroom or a colony of fungi. It continuously spreads spores, which are visible with naked eyes, into the air.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Most of the employees are not fond of this abnormality. No employee is generous enough to care about a giant mushroom spewing mysterious spores while they have other dozens of work in their hands. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="1">
      [
      {On top of that, only few employees volunteered for its observation. We could only record very little information about it. Originally, the company assigned observation work purely according as the shift system. However, after that “incidents of magical girls” few years ago, an employee’s opinion started playing role in assignment of works..}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Animate spores are created from the abnormality, flowing through the air. It mainly invades an organism via respiratory system. It is difficult to notice the initial symptoms because an employee inhaled these spores feel nothing but a light dyspnea and sandy sensation in a throat. Thus, a mask is mandatorily worn when approaching this abnormality.}
      ]
    </desc>


    <desc id="5" openLevel="1">
      [
      {If an employee inhales a certain amount of spores, tumors start developing on their body and eventually, they become a monster with their original form hardly noticeable. In this stage, they are hostile towards everything in sight. They must be terminated with extreme prejudice. The damage will be severe if the primary infection is not stopped because the spores are highly contagious. Also, it is assumed that the spores have hallucinatory components. An extreme caution is advised when working on this abnormality, since the abnormality has strong desire to reproduce and its reproduction process is fatal to employees.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="6" openLevel="2">
      [
      {&lt;Counselling session record – Employee John&gt; &#13;&#10;There was a guy, not really talkative. He was that guy who would glance sideways at us, like expecting us to talk to him.&#13;&#10; But there was something peculiar about him. He volunteered to work on Giant Mushroom. We had no idea what part of that disgusting mushroom did he like. It was kind of disturbing that he would spend unusually long time in the mushroom’s containment chamber. Who knows what kind of monstrous thing he would take out from that thing?&#13;&#10;We decided he finally went bonkers when he talked nonsense about how he became a friend with the mushroom. It was a common business, though. Lots of things happen here. One employee going insane was not a big deal. We hinted him to take some psychiatric test but he just gave us a condescending look as if he knows something that we don’t.&#13;&#10; Few days later, as we all know, he kicked the bucket. Did I tell you that it was me who found out that fungal monster was him? The birthmark on his forehead. If we couldn’t find that birthmark on that thing, we would’ve not even guessed that it was him. No one actually knew that he had a birthmark except me. He had no friends, you know.&#13;&#10; He, after becoming that monster, just wandered around Giant Mushroom’s containment chamber. We tried to lure him to somewhere not crowded, because he attacked everything on sight. But he didn’t move 10 meters away from it until the moment of his death.&#13;&#10; That’s why we decided to rename the abnormality. Because of complex reasons like pity for that guy who became a friend with a mushroom, and remembrance for his tragic death. &#13;&#10;He always said he didn’t need a friend but I knew it was a bullshit. He needed a friend. That’s the reason why he didn’t even know that he was being infected, going crazy in hallucinations, not knowing that he is becoming a monster. The mushroom just tamed the poor bastard to become its tool of reproduction. The guy whose name was not known, Alex……}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="7" openLevel="3">
      [
      {&lt;Employee Alex’s note&gt; &#13;&#10;Human mind is too fragile; it cannot contain everything a person is. Do you know that the mantis shrimps can see hundreds of colors that humans can’t? This is a simple example to illustrate my point that it is detrimental to believe and judge everything relying solely on what you see.&#13;&#10; I don’t actually have many friends. I hope you don’t misunderstand. I DON’T make friends, not CAN’T. We, as human beings, don’t understand each other. A person thinks of him or herself as a completely isolated entity, making complete sympathy impossible. But ironically, an inherent instinct of mob psychology survived over the course of our revolution. We play risky game of staying inside of the line, while vainly trying to understand, invading the others.&#13;&#10; I am long done with this game. That was the reason why I volunteered for the observation on the giant mushroom. No one wanted to get close to that abnormality. It must be because of petty reason such as how disgusting and alien it looks to their eyes.  Actually, I felt somewhat superior when everyone looked surprised at me saying that I will do the work.&#13;&#10; The mushroom didn’t do anything special. But I patiently observed and recorded its activity. The day it spread powders of enchanting color, I thought the abnormality was giving me a reward for my patient. &#13;&#10;After that, I underwent a special change. I could perceive a higher level of reality, “hyper reality”. It was a hand he stretched out for me. I took it, and was rewarded with an invite to such a special place. It was possible only for me.&#13;&#10;We talked about a lot of things. He welcomed me because I was the only one who could realize his essence. He talked me through minds. I had been imagining, yearning for the moment to have a conversation with mind. To be completed understood, the feeling of unification. It was exhilarating, I could barely hide my joy. &#13;&#10; (omitted) I wanted to get closer to him. I wanted to be a part of him. I had always been thinking about him and waiting to enter his containment chamber. I wanted to belong to him and understand his world… I can feel my heart is ready like a bud before its blossoming…. I was slowly being tamed….}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="8" openLevel="4">
      [
      {&lt;An excerpt from the record&gt; &#13;&#10;This record is a part of what surveillance camera in the abnormality’s containment chamber caught. Unfortunately, the visual feed was blocked by spores, all that could be extracted was the audio. Considering the content of this conversation, it is safe to assume that the abnormality’s spore contains hallucinatory agents. Because even after a thorough analysis of the audio, no other voice but the employee’s, could be found. After few hours, the said employee underwent severe state of frenzy and was shot to death by another employee. &#13;&#10;-	No, I don’t have any friends. Like I said before, I am not fond of such contradictory relationships. But at least, I think you can be my friend. Human language is too simple. I cannot illustrate what I would like to call this relationship but I think I have to settle for “friends”. &#13;&#10;-	Yes. I am just one friend material for you.&#13;&#10;-	I accept you. You changed my life. I had been living my whole life being depressed, not knowing what to do or talking to anyone. All I had been doing is just working. But you took me, who I trashed myself. I felt being understood as I understood something more than everything. You saw through my essence as I saw yours. It is, it is truly…a rapturous experience. I want to understand you too. I want to love you, become you. I am born human, lived tedious life and might have kept doing so until I die had it not been for you. I am so happy that I met you. &#13;&#10;-	Even if this is my curse, I will love this curse as a blessing. I will think about you to the day my mind collapses and crumbles. I will close my eyes thinking about my only friend that came from the far universe… (The abnormality makes a slight ventilating noise and goes silent).&#13;&#10;-	Even if this is my curse, I will love this curse as a blessing. I will think about you to the day my mind collapses and crumbles. I will close my eyes thinking about my only friend that came from the far universe… (The abnormality makes a slight ventilating noise and goes silent).}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">The Qliphoth counter is decreased when the work other than 'Insight' was performed consecutively three or more times. </specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="2">When the work result was bad, Qliphoth counter has decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="3">The #0 employee, who was constantly working on $0, appealed for suffering at the containment room. After that, a $0-like tissue emerged in his body, and #0 employee began to transform into $0-1.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="4">The $0 attracted the employee to its containment room  when the Qliphoth counter became 0. As the employee led by the $0 entered the containment room, the same phenomenon as in the previous case occurred.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="5">When suppressing $0-1, pay attention to the spores that occur at the time of death. The spores give sustained mental damage, which should be immediately stopped if a panicked employee is found moving into $0's containment room.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>

   



  </observe>
</creature>